<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:36:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:36:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[耐克在华困境加深，扭亏为盈停滞不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克已经没有时间来证明其在中国的策略是有效的了。这家美国运动服装巨头在中国的销售额连续第六个季度下滑，其中鞋类销售额下降了 20%，这凸显出这个曾被视为增长引擎的市场已成为其最大的压力点。【原文：Nike is running out of time to prove its China playbook works. The U.S. sportswear giant’s sixth straight quarterly sales decline in the country - including a 20% drop in footwear - underscores how a market once seen as a growth engine has become its biggest pressure point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nikes-china-conundrum-deepens-turnaround-stagnates-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WEOYT3AHOJPWLKRAIJ2244PSGI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构对澳新银行系统性不当行为处以 1.65 亿澳元罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构周五表示，澳新银行集团因在处理 140 亿澳元政府债券交易中的不当行为，以及影响纳税人和零售客户的其他行为，被联邦法院罚款 2.5 亿澳元（1.653 亿美元）。【原文：An Australian regulator said on Friday that ANZ Group was fined A$250 million ($165.3 million) by a Federal Court for misconduct in handling a A$14 billion government bond deal, as well other actions that affected taxpayers and retail customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australian-regulator-fines-anz-165-million-systemic-misconduct-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7KFUZXSHWJKMTLLCVFACF4JLKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着全球审查的加强，中国企业希望把新加坡作为家]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的中国公司希望在新加坡落户，因为他们相信，迁往这个以贸易为重点的城市国家，可以降低其业务受中美地缘政治紧张局势干扰的风险。【原文：A growing number of Chinese companies are looking to domicile in Singapore, betting a move to the trade-focused city-state would reduce risks their operations get disrupted by Sino-U.S. geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-scrutiny-grows-chinese-firms-look-call-singapore-home-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4R4U3ZSQJROCDI5BJHIR3SBX7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，墨西哥航空公司 Volaris 和 Viva Aerobus 即将达成合并协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士周四透露，Volaris 和 Viva Aerobus 接近达成合并协议。【原文：Volaris and Viva Aerobus are close to agreeing a merger, sources familiar with the matter said on Thursday, a move that would combine two of Mexico's largest airlines and create a low-cost champion in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexican-airlines-volaris-viva-aerobus-near-merger-agreement-sources-say-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7Q6HD2PAZJOQTBENHKSQ5XRJWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称美国对英伟达向中国销售先进人工智能芯片展开审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[五位消息人士称，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府已经启动了一项审查，这可能导致英伟达（Nvidia）功能第二强大的人工智能芯片首次运往中国，兑现了他允许这种有争议的销售的承诺。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has launched a review that could result in the first shipments to China of Nvidia's second-most powerful AI chips, five sources said, making good on his pledge to allow the controversial sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-launches-review-advanced-nvidia-ai-chip-sales-china-sources-say-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47FTLDKERNOABIBOZ37VDEE4FU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:39:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田计划从 2026 年起在日本销售 3 款美国制造的车型]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周五表示，该公司的目标是从明年开始在日本销售美国制造的凯美瑞轿车、汉兰达越野车和Tundra皮卡，希望以此帮助改善日美贸易关系。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Friday that it aims to begin selling its U.S.-made Camry sedan, Highlander SUV and Tundra pickup truck in Japan starting next year as it hopes to help improve Japan―U.S. trade relations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-aims-begin-selling-3-us-made-models-japan-2026-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R56IQZSWRZL7LNZY6BEU5CNLZM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油将连续第二周收低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五早盘，油价下跌，并将连续第二周收低，原因是俄乌和平协议前景的上升抵消了对委内瑞拉油轮被封锁导致供应中断的担忧。【原文：Oil prices fell in early trading on Friday and were set to close lower for a second straight week, as rising prospects of a Russia-Ukraine peace deal offset concerns over supply disruptions from a blockade of Venezuelan oil tankers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-set-close-lower-second-straight-week-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CT5BC3D5OZKGZHMAGR37HVPY7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:30:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司股东 Harris Associates 表示对派拉蒙修改后的竞购方案持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟发现公司的第五大股东哈里斯联合公司（Harris Associates）周四表示，如果派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司（Paramount Skydance）提出更高的出价并解决交易条款方面的问题，该公司将对派拉蒙天空舞蹈公司的修订报价持 "非常开放的态度"。【原文：Harris Associates, the fifth largest shareholder in Warner Bros Discovery , said on Thursday it would be "very open" to a revised offer from Paramount Skydance if the company presents a superior bid and addresses issues with deal terms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/warner-bros-discovery-shareholder-harris-associates-says-open-revised-paramount-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BPHNHZJM6ROMROZUKOPLEYEPZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[脆弱的日元在日本央行会议前惶惶不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，日元在近期低点附近震荡，交易员们在等待日本央行能否说服市场明年继续加息，而欧元在日本央行没有暗示加息后略有下滑。【原文：The yen was pinned near recent lows on Friday while traders waited to see whether the Bank of Japan can convince the market it can keep hiking interest rates into next year, while the euro slipped a bit after the central bank didn't hint at rate hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/fragile-yen-tenterhooks-ahead-boj-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YAP3X4X7NZNGNGJUZTJF7GPPEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市追随华尔街涨势，为日本央行加息做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，亚洲股市反弹，因为科技股的反弹提振了华尔街，让投资者开始期待日本央行可能加息，这可能会给货币和债券带来波澜。【原文：Asian share markets rebounded on Friday as a turnaround in tech lifted Wall Street, leaving investors counting down to a likely hike in interest rates from the Bank of Japan that could cause waves for currencies and bonds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-global-markets-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HEFHESFEEJLTJAKWGSNLCBH7HM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:36:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行调查显示，新西兰商业信心达到30年来的最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行（ANZ Bank）周五的一项调查显示，新西兰12月份的商业信心指数飙升至30年来的最高水平，前瞻性活动指标再次回升，部分指标达到数十年来的新高。【原文：New Zealand's business confidence surged in December to hit its highest level in 30 years, with forward-looking activity indicators lifting again with some reaching multi-decade highs, an ANZ Bank survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-business-confidence-hits-highest-level-30-years-anz-survey-shows-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4PHQ4MZILJM4RJ2Y6UPQ4VU2TI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cannabis companies face hurdles accessing big banks despite reclassification, experts say]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's move to relax marijuana regulations could ease some burden for cannabis companies, but will likely keep doors to access capital from big banks closed, experts said.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/cannabis-companies-face-hurdles-accessing-big-banks-despite-reclassification-2025-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATO67UKGRJKZTM2EJTLBYH32WI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan's core inflation steady in November, stays above BOJ target]]></title><description><![CDATA[Japan's core consumer prices rose 3.0% in November from a year earlier, data showed on Friday, staying above the central bank's 2% target for the 44th straight month.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/japans-core-inflation-steady-november-stays-above-boj-target-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4T7OPKEXVJIHIAMJRQXRYF6VQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wanxiang to pay $53 million to resolve US probe into imported Chinese auto parts, DOJ says]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，已与中国汽车零部件供应商万向集团的美国分公司就五年内对从中国进口的轮毂总成和其他零部件征收进口关税一事达成和解。【原文：The Justice Department said Thursday it had reached a settlement with the U.S. arm of Chinese auto parts supplier Wanxiang over import tariffs owed on wheel hub assemblies and other parts imported from China over a five-year period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/wanxiang-pay-53-million-resolve-us-probe-into-imported-chinese-auto-parts-doj-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6PCOQR76BMV7LXKS7ZM6VFIPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:21:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[黑莓因网络安全需求上调年度收入预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[黑莓公司（BlackBerry）周四上调了 2026 财年收入预期的下限，表明随着企业加大支出以应对日益复杂的网络攻击，对其网络安全软件的需求强劲。【原文：BlackBerry on Thursday raised the lower end of its fiscal 2026 revenue forecast, signalling strong demand for its cybersecurity software as companies ramp up spending to counter increasingly sophisticated cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackberry-lifts-lower-end-annual-revenue-forecast-cybersecurity-demand-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKCUZJMDBFIWHK2KTGJTS3HINM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦监督员报告后，UAW 总裁办公室主任将离开工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）的一位重要战略家和工会 2023 年汽车厂罢工的策划者即将离开该工会组织，因为负责监督 UAW 的联邦监督员在一份报告中认为他
 
 他参与了一场不当解除另一位工会领导人职务的运动。【原文：A key United Auto Workers strategist and architect of the union’s 2023 auto-factory strike is leaving the labor group, after a report by the federal monitor overseeing the UAW concluded that he
 
 was part of a campaign to improperly remove duties from another union leader.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/uaw-presidents-chief-staff-leave-union-following-federal-monitor-report-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYDDX4PSBJKN3ARJKH2AWNVS44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok signs deal to sell US unit to American investor-led venture]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份 TikTok 首席执行官的备忘录，字节跳动旗下的 TikTok 已签署协议，将其美国实体出售给一家由美国投资者控制的合资企业。【原文：ByteDance's TikTok has signed a deal to sell its U.S. entity to a joint venture controlled by American investors, according to a memo from TikTok CEO seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/american-investor-consortium-acquire-tiktok-us-entity-axios-reports-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S2RA7QD745MLRNVGHPRSIBM6OI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚桑托斯公司任命内部人士拉克兰-哈里斯为财务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[Santos said on Friday it has appointed insider Lachlan Harris as its CFO, as the Australian gas producer navigates a transition period tied to its key Barossa and Pikka projects.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/australias-santos-names-insider-lachlan-harris-finance-boss-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2OK6GE4NJPAXH3DYTRXKTILS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国主要交易所将于 12 月 24 日和 26 日继续营业]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令联邦政府在12月24日和12月26日两天关闭数小时后，美国主要证券交易所周四表示，它们将在这两天如期开市。【原文：Major U.S. stock exchanges said on Thursday they will remain open as scheduled on December 24 and December 26, hours after President Donald Trump ordered the federal government to be closed on those days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nyse-says-stock-market-remain-open-dec-24-dec-26-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AULCCDQ3IFIG5IAY6VZ3SVUYEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trading Day: Three cheers for 'whacky' inflation]]></title><description><![CDATA[这将是本年度最后一期定期 "交易日 "通讯。感谢您的支持和反馈，我们期待 2026 年同样精彩纷呈。正常服务将于 1 月 5 日星期一恢复。节日快乐【原文：This will be the last regular 'Trading Day' newsletter of the year. Thank you for all your support and feedback, and we look forward to an equally eventful and rewarding 2026. Normal service will be resumed on Monday, January 5. Happy holidays.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KDO4XNYMNJNK5KDC3HG5GPXXU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将把利率上调至 30 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五将把利率上调至三十年来的最高点，并表示准备在明年以后进一步加息，这凸显了日本央行坚信持续的工资增长将使通胀率持久地保持在2%的目标附近。【原文：The Bank of Japan is set to raise interest rates on Friday to a three-decade high and signal its readiness to eye further hikes beyond next year, underscoring its conviction that sustained wage gains will keep inflation durably around its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bank-japan-set-raise-interest-rates-30-year-high-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6P2C3IN3VNJTNDO3BQ4AK6V344</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比在接受福克斯财经采访时对最新通胀数据表示欢迎，并称可能会有更多降息举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago President Austan Goolsbee said on Thursday “there’s a lot to like” in the latest consumer price index data, and if it can be sustained, it will help open the door for more interest rate cuts next year.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-goolsbee-fox-business-interview-welcomes-latest-inflation-data-says-more-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AEH6YZMKNIQRBC3STSPQT2HGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:50:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Starbucks supplier Cuisine Solutions hires Morgan Stanley and Rothschild for potential sale, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[食品公司 Cuisine Solutions 为星巴克（Starbucks）生产鸡蛋饼，为好市多（Costco）生产草饲西冷牛肉，据熟悉内情的人士透露，该公司已聘请投资银行探讨明年的出售事宜，这家家族式私营公司的估值可能超过 20 亿美元。【原文：Food company Cuisine Solutions, which makes egg bites for Starbucks and sous vide grass-fed beef sirloin for Costco , has hired investment banks to explore a sale next year that could value the private, family-owned company at over $2 billion, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/starbucks-supplier-cuisine-solutions-hires-morgan-stanley-rothschild-potential-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4H3QTMBL5N6ZHVSDW7EJ2LPR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克利润率下滑为第二季度收入增长蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司周四的季度收入超过了华尔街的预期，但关税和这家运动服装巨头以折扣方式清理陈旧库存的努力损害了利润率。【原文：Nike on Thursday edged past Wall Street expectations for quarterly revenue, but tariffs and the sportswear giant's efforts to clear out aged inventory at discounts hurt margins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nike-edges-past-quarterly-revenue-expectations-resilient-demand-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7RFL3423EVNGZKHL4GZHFEBIQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递发布乐观季度业绩，上调 2026 年利润预期下限]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递周四公布的第二季度利润和收入均高于华尔街预期，并上调了全年盈利展望的下限，原因是旺季定价行动和成本削减努力帮助抵消了货运量的疲软。【原文：FedEx posted second-quarter profit and revenue above Wall Street's estimates on Thursday and lifted the low end of its full-year earnings outlook, as peak-season pricing actions and cost-cutting efforts helped offset softer shipment volumes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-posts-higher-quarterly-results-raises-low-end-full-year-profit-forecast-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CJYL2PJD7VJXHP5SAES4K5UXBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 21:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称，墨西哥石油公司生产部门负责人将在未来几天内下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexico's state oil company Pemex is preparing to replace the head of its exploration and production arm, just months after he returned to the post, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters, as the company struggles to stem a decline in crude output.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/head-pemexs-production-arm-step-down-coming-days-sources-say-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AMPV2LQGRJOOPCGLIKMIQQ33LA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资经理被控在 Anduril 上市前欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[A New York investment manager has been indicted for allegedly defrauding millions of dollars from investors in a sham pre-IPO scheme tied to U.S. drone-maker Anduril Industries, highlighting the risk of fraud as private tech firms grow more prominent and valuable.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-investment-manager-charged-with-anduril-pre-ipo-fraud-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JV4WHBCTTJN2JNZB4P2JTDZF54</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Finalists for top Fed job want to cut rates, but diverge from there]]></title><description><![CDATA[到目前为止，唐纳德-特朗普总统面试过的三位候选人都希望在明年 5 月接替美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔，但他们在货币政策的其他方面存在分歧，而且背景各不相同。【原文：The three candidates interviewed by President Donald Trump so far to replace Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell next May share a desire to cut interest rates, but diverge on other aspects of monetary policy and come from different backgrounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/finalists-top-fed-job-want-cut-rates-diverge-there-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YACHDOHMERMW7CCYQ43DL3VAQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Energy Department taps Big Tech for AI-powered research push]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部周四表示，它已与包括微软、谷歌和 Nvidia 等科技巨头在内的 24 家组织签署了协议，以推进创世任务。【原文：The U.S. Department of Energy said on Thursday it has signed agreements with 24 organizations, including tech giants such as Microsoft , Google and Nvidia , to advance the Genesis Mission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-energy-department-taps-big-tech-ai-powered-research-push-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FTI4GTDKT5NIPM75SVSPNGTQBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛认为到 2026 年 12 月黄金价格为 4,900 美元，预计油价将下跌；铜仍是最受欢迎的工业金属]]></title><description><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs sees gold prices climbing 14% to $4,900 per ounce by December 2026 in its base case, it said in a note on Thursday, while citing upside risks to this view due to a potential broadening of diversification to private investors.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sees-gold-4900-by-december-2026-projects-oil-price-decline-copper-2025-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQ65DRSMNVJJTFJKS4VPF25CMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>