<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:19:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:19:27 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普尚未上任，已成为全球经济政策的风云人物]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）即将上任，本周全球开始认真对待这届政府的经济问题，一些美联储官员预计通胀率将上升，利率将受到限制，加拿大官员因未来关税预算而意外辞职，比特币的潜在地位升级受到高度关注。【原文：The world's economic reckoning with the incoming administration of U.S. President-elect Donald Trump began in earnest this week, with some Federal Reserve officials penciling in estimates for higher inflation and restrictive interest rates, a surprise resignation in Canada over budgeting for prospective tariffs and a hyper focus on a potential status upgrade for bitcoin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-not-yet-office-already-figure-global-economic-policy-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2ZUQVKX4ZJKXIIUI67WUYTXPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车初创公司 TuSimple 更名为 CreateAI，转向游戏技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[TuSimple控股公司周四表示，它将重新命名为CreateAI，并从自动驾驶卡车转向人工智能游戏技术，这标志着这家曾经风光无限的自动驾驶卡车初创公司试图东山再起。【原文：TuSimple Holdings said on Thursday it would rebrand as CreateAI and pivot from autonomous trucking to AI gaming technology, marking an attempt by the once-prominent self-driving truck startup to make a comeback.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/self-driving-truck-startup-tusimple-rebrands-createai-shifts-gaming-tech-2024-12-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAYUF4G4GJOUXH6ZRBMHHOUPVY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司首席执行官告诉陪审团，收购 Nuvia 是每年节省 14 亿美元 Arm 费用的好机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周三庭审中出示的证据，高通公司的内部文件显示，这家芯片公司估计，通过在 2021 年收购一家名不见经传的初创公司 Arm ，最终每年可以节省多达 14 亿美元的付款。【原文：Internal Qualcomm documents showed the chip firm estimated it could eventually save as much as $1.4 billion a year on payments to Arm , by purchasing a little-known startup in 2021, according to evidence shown at a trial on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/qualcomm-saw-nuvia-buy-chance-save-14-billion-year-arm-fees-ceo-tells-jury-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2IT2NEMG45OSLO7KNBUJPGBDCY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:26:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索频道任命美国网络业务主管钱宁-邓吉（Channing Dungey）为主要高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟探索公司（Warner Bros Discovery）周三任命了其美国网络业务的主要管理团队成员，该团队将由华纳兄弟电视集团董事长兼首席执行官钱宁-邓吉（Channing Dungey）领导。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery on Wednesday named key members of the executive team for its U.S. Networks business, which will be headed by Channing Dungey, chairman and CEO of Warner Bros Television Group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-discovery-names-key-executives-under-us-networks-business-head-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SW3P2ULUTFJOTG5KYRBNK4UTW4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伍德赛德能源公司与雪佛龙公司合作交换多个能源项目的股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚伍德赛德能源公司（Woodside Energy）周四表示，该公司已与雪佛龙公司（Chevron）达成一项协议，双方将交换若干能源项目的股权，美国石油和天然气巨头将向伍德赛德支付高达 4 亿美元的现金。【原文：Australia's Woodside Energy said on Thursday it had entered into a deal with Chevron to exchange stakes in a number of energy projects, with the U.S. oil and gas giant making a cash payment of up to $400 million to Woodside.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/woodside-energy-partners-with-chevron-swap-stakes-various-energy-projects-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMLJZ2QSI5KJJEXXBDNAUTAB34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果抨击 Meta 提出的众多互操作性要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周三抨击 Meta Platforms 公司，称该公司多次要求将 iPhone 制造商的软件工具接入其设备，这可能会影响用户的隐私和安全，凸显了两家科技巨头之间的激烈竞争。【原文：Apple on Wednesday hit out at Meta Platforms , saying its numerous requests to access the iPhone maker's software tools to its devices could impact users' privacy and security, underscoring the intense rivalry between the two tech giants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-slams-metas-numerous-interoperability-requests-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UW77SNNBZNEXEBXIS7AYXTMVE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新日铁和双日将持有冠军铁矿加拿大项目 49% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚冠军铁矿公司（Champion Iron）周四表示，日本新日铁公司和双日株式会社将以 2.45 亿澳元（1.5239 亿美元）的价格收购该公司在加拿大卡米（Kami）项目 49% 的股份。【原文：Australia's Champion Iron said on Thursday Japanese firms Nippon Steel and Sojitz will take up a 49% stake for A$245 million ($152.39 million) in the company's Kami project in Canada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/nippon-steel-sojitz-take-49-stake-champion-irons-canada-project-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6JTDTQV2VONRJNLNOTDXS5KTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦纳公布的第四季度业绩低于预期，原因是利率上升导致成本增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率波动导致潜在购房者仍不愿购房，Lennar 公司周三第四季度利润和营收不及华尔街预期，导致其股价在盘后交易中下跌 7.5%。【原文：Lennar Corp missed Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit and revenue on Wednesday, as potential buyers remained reluctant to buy homes due to volatile mortgage rates, sending its shares down 7.5% in aftermarket trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lennar-reports-q4-results-below-estimates-increased-cost-higher-interest-rates-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWUKJQ55NJMLVKSO4EYNY6QBTM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:40:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳新银行离任首席执行官将放弃 2024 年长期浮动薪酬]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳新银行集团首席执行官谢恩-埃利奥特（Shayne Elliott）在周四的年度股东大会上投票反对 2024 年长期浮动薪酬的决议，因为大部分股东投了反对票。【原文：ANZ Group's CEO Shayne Elliott will not be taking the 2024 long-term variable remuneration after a large proportion of shareholders voted against the resolution at the annual general meeting on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/anzs-outgoing-ceo-forfeit-2024-long-term-variable-remuneration-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQCP6JNMZBMFLIILXYJTDOXOEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国不会因安全气囊问题立即召回约 5000 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，不会立即召回由13家汽车制造商组装的约5000万辆美国汽车的安全气囊气体发生器，而是将开展进一步调查。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday it will not seek an immediate recall of air bag inflators in about 50 million U.S. vehicles assembled by 13 automakers and instead will conduct further investigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-will-not-seek-immediate-recall-about-50-million-vehicles-over-air-bag-issue-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDJFC4D7ZVIDHIA5TYLQU52ZXU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[圣诞节临近，亚马逊可能面临美国罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于数千名工人威胁要在零售商繁忙的假日销售季节举行罢工，亚马逊公司面临的压力越来越大，要求它与卡车司机工会进行谈判。【原文：Pressure is building on Amazon.com to come to the bargaining table with the Teamsters Union as thousands of workers threaten to strike during the retailer’s busy holiday selling season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-faces-possible-us-strikes-christmas-looms-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TUVSZITZVI5VHEZSYYGRA6EKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:48:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：美联储 "鹰派减息 "抨击市场，下一个是日本央行]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG3QOG6IMNLT5M2EOC27VESEGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:47:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美联储发出放缓宽松政策的信号后股市下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储将利率下调四分之一个百分点，且央行的经济预测显示明年的降息步伐将放缓之后，周三美国股市大幅下挫。【原文：U.S. stocks plunged on Wednesday after the Federal Reserve cut interest rates by a quarter of a percentage point and the central bank's economic projections signaled a slower pace of cuts next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-stocks-skid-after-fed-signals-it-will-slow-down-its-easing-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MUGQMVEO2NNQDAXJTUBSJOHALQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔表示，美联储不能持有比特币，也不寻求改变这一现状]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周三表示，美国央行无意参与任何政府持有大量比特币的努力。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said on Wednesday that the U.S. central bank has no desire to be involved in any government effort to hold large amounts of bitcoin.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fed-cant-hold-bitcoin-not-seeking-change-that-powell-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7CVZRCRU6NN2XHSJ4OMQHX2WMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美光科技第二季度业绩低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美光科技（Micron Technology）周三预测第二季度业绩低于华尔街预期，原因是手机和个人电脑中使用的内存芯片价格疲软，影响了盈利，导致该公司股价在盘后交易中下跌 17.2%。【原文：Micron Technology forecast second-quarter results below Wall Street estimates on Wednesday as weakened prices of memory chips used in handsets and personal computers weigh on earnings, sending the company's shares down 17.2% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/micron-technology-expects-second-quarter-revenue-below-estimates-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V7QTTVKUTJKT3BCNYRHUPBNZQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国石墨矿商要求华盛顿对中国竞争对手征收 920% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[北美石墨矿商周三要求美国政府对中国的电池金属供应商征收高达 920% 的关税，以抵制他们所称的中国政府的 "恶意贸易行为"。【原文：North American graphite miners asked the U.S. government on Wednesday to impose a tariff as high as 920% on Chinese suppliers of the battery metal in order to counter what they describe as Beijing's "malicious trade practices."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-graphite-miners-ask-washington-impose-920-tariff-chinese-rivals-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APRU2JLOONI6XLOPF36ETEQONY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行召开今年最后一次利率审议会议，特朗普风险为前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行决策者将在今年的最后一次会议上讨论是否具备了加息的条件，全球经济增长放缓以及美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普政策的不确定性使这一决定变得更加复杂。【原文：Bank of Japan policymakers will debate whether conditions are falling in place to raise interest rates at their final meeting this year, a decision complicated by slowing global growth and uncertainty over U.S. president-elect Donald Trump's policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-meets-final-rate-review-this-year-trump-risk-clouds-outlook-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEFUTZ776JKLDE3VALHEL2KWWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部称腾讯解除 Epic Games 两名董事职务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周三表示，在美国司法部反垄断部门表示担心他们在 Epic 和腾讯董事会的职位违反美国法律后，由中国游戏和社交媒体公司腾讯控股任命的 Epic Games 的两名董事辞去了 Epic 董事会的职务。【原文：Two directors of Epic Games, who had been appointed by Chinese gaming and social media firm Tencent Holdings , resigned from Epic's board after the U.S. Justice Department's antitrust division expressed concerns that their positions on both the Epic and Tencent boards violated U.S. law, the Justice Department said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tencent-removes-two-directors-epic-games-us-justice-dept-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVBEQHQAIFPHHHWQUXPOCQQJS4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔尚未准备好就特朗普政策对经济的影响发表看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周三表示，现在断言当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出的经济政策将对经济产生什么影响，以及这可能对央行的政策选择产生什么影响还为时过早。【原文：Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Wednesday it's too soon to say what President-elect Donald Trump's proposed economic policies will do to the economy and how that might bear on the central bank's policy choices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-not-ready-say-what-trump-policies-will-do-economy-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERRP63UE5JPHDPFULQFGI6OLIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克新任首席执行官希尔有机会阐述扭亏为盈计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃利奥特-希尔（Elliott Hill）在担任耐克公司首席执行官两个月后，本周四将迎来他的第一次机会，以说服投资者他能在裁员和销售下滑的一年后拯救这家陷入困境的运动服装公司。【原文：Two months into his tenure as Nike CEO, Elliott Hill gets his first shot on Thursday to convince investors he can rescue the flailing sportswear company after a year stained by layoffs and cratering sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/new-nike-ceo-hill-gets-his-chance-lay-out-turnaround-plan-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWRYC5VWYFJ5JIKQCPCKXSC5AA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美联储降息 25 个基点，缩减 2025 年宽松政策预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）周三下调了利率，并表示鉴于失业率相对稳定，且近期通胀几乎没有改善，将放慢借贷成本进一步下降的步伐。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve cut interest rates on Wednesday and signaled it will slow the pace at which borrowing costs fall any further given a relatively stable unemployment rate and little recent improvement in inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/view-fed-cuts-25-bp-scales-back-2025-easing-projections-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCZRAEMPA5ICVPH4RJVB34AJBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国利率期货价格预计美联储 1 月按兵不动，2025 年两次降息--LSEG 预计]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦基金利率是衡量银行间无担保隔夜贷款成本的指标，在美联储于周三结束为期两天的会议并将利率下调 25 个基点后，联邦基金利率期货已计价为隔夜基准利率将在美联储 1 月份的政策会议上保持不变。【原文：Futures on the federal funds rate, which measure the cost of unsecured overnight loans between banks, have priced in that the overnight benchmark rates will remain unchanged at the Federal Reserve's January policy meeting after the Fed lowered rates by 25 basis points at the end of its two-day meeting on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-rate-futures-price-fed-hold-january-two-cuts-2025-lseg-estimates-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5M4DVMLVVNJLMYPGIDKVI67MA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监察机构建议能源部停止向绿色项目提供贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部监察长敦促该机构的贷款办公室立即停止向绿色项目发放数十亿美元的贷款，称审查这些项目的承包商可能既为能源部服务，也为潜在借款人服务。【原文：The inspector general of the U.S. Department of Energy urged the agency's loan office to immediately halt issuing billions of dollars in loans to green projects, saying contractors who vet them may be serving both the agency and potential borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-watchdog-recommends-energy-department-halt-loans-green-projects-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQNIEQ52RFJ5JDNBGLJ752BUFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道信中称，尽管修改了提案，新日铁交易仍将受阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一封信显示，尽管新日铁不断与美国官员会面和通话，并提出了三项改良方案以缓解国家安全方面的担忧，但仍未能获得负责审查其 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的强大小组的批准。【原文：Despite a steady stream of meetings and calls with U.S. officials, and three revamped proposals to assuage national security concerns, Nippon Steel has failed to garner approval from a powerful panel reviewing its $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel , a letter seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/despite-revamped-proposals-nippon-steel-deal-track-be-blocked-letter-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCPI6UMR4FMCJOZV4HARM4B3MQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构命令 USAA 联邦储蓄银行纠正不安全行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国货币监理署（OCC）周三表示，USAA 联邦储蓄银行已被责令纠正一系列长期存在的监管缺陷，这些缺陷相当于不安全和不健全的做法。【原文：USAA Federal Savings Bank has been ordered to correct a range of longstanding regulatory deficiencies amounting to unsafe and unsound practices, the U.S. Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulator-orders-usaa-federal-savings-bank-correct-unsafe-practices-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVPR5ARWG5IQNGXUPTYX6ER34A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储下调逆回购利率的幅度大于基金利率目标值]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三调整了其利率控制工具箱中的一个关键部分，下调了逆回购工具的利率，降幅超过了联邦基金利率的下调幅度。【原文：The Federal Reserve adjusted a key part of its rate control toolkit on Wednesday, lowering the rate it offers on its reverse repo facility by more than it cut the federal funds rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-cuts-reverse-repo-rate-by-wider-margin-than-funds-rate-target-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3PKUJBBN5IRHLUEFSML5DTEZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决策者预计明年降息两个季度点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国央行行长们周三发布了新的预测，呼吁在通胀率上升的情况下明年降息两个季度点，这一预测与唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）1月份开始其在白宫的第二个四年任期时采取观望态度是一致的。【原文：U.S. central bankers on Wednesday issued fresh projections calling for two quarter-point interest-rate cuts next year amid rising inflation, a forecast consistent with a wait-and-see approach come January as Donald Trump starts his second four-year stint in the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-policymakers-project-two-quarter-point-rate-cuts-next-year-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7IDWPAYWRMDPN4YNS5SF35DBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特将更换质量领导者，以降低保修成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周三证实，该公司将任命一位新的质量主管，以扭转其行业最高的召回记录并降低保修成本。【原文：Ford Motor is appointing a new head of quality, the company confirmed on Wednesday, as the automaker works to reverse its industry-topping record of recalls and reduce warranty costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-change-its-quality-leader-it-chases-lower-warranty-costs-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFR7VWNSZJPFPAGTJZIUZDGVHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BNPL 贷款公司 Sezzle 因做空机构 Hindenburg Research 的攻击而暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在兴登堡研究公司（Hindenburg Research）披露空头头寸后，Sezzle 的股价在周三暴跌，原因是该公司的借贷行为存在风险，同时客户和商户数量也在减少。【原文：Buy now, pay later firm Sezzle's shares plunged on Wednesday after Hindenburg Research disclosed a short position, citing risky lending practices alongside a decline in customers and merchants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bnpl-lender-sezzle-plunges-short-seller-hindenburg-research-takes-aim-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6VTH7LLLVJW3CK4PDSERAJLHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院共和党高层敦促最高法院驳回 TikTok 的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院共和党头号人物米奇-麦康奈尔（Mitch McConnell）周三敦促美国最高法院驳回 TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动的诉讼请求，以阻止一项旨在强制在 1 月 19 日前出售短视频应用程序的法律，否则将以国家安全为由面临禁令。【原文：Top Senate Republican Mitch McConnell on Wednesday urged the U.S. Supreme Court to reject a bid by TikTok and its China-based parent company ByteDance to block a law intended to force the sale of the short-video app by Jan. 19 or face a ban on national security grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-senate-republican-urges-supreme-court-reject-tiktok-appeal-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">462DFVRYZFOTDEYS2WDFIA42GE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>