<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:19:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:19:20 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[萨克斯全球公司解决供应商投诉后，获得法院最终批准10亿美元破产贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国破产法官周五最终批准了萨克斯全球公司的破产融资方案，该方案将为该公司提供10亿美元的新资金。此前萨克斯已与奢侈品牌供应商达成协议，这些供应商曾在该公司破产前对商品供应问题表示担忧。【原文：A U.S. bankruptcy judge on Friday gave final approval to Saks Global's bankruptcy financing, which provides $1 billion in new funding to the company, after Saks reached deals with luxury brand vendors that had raised concerns about goods to the retailer before it went bankrupt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/saks-global-gets-final-court-approval-1-billion-bankruptcy-loan-after-addressing-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">222G7OZ7KRPKJCFGUXJCD4OIO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院推翻特朗普裁决提振股市，或令债券市场恐慌情绪加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五推翻特朗普总统全面加征关税的裁决，虽使股价小幅回升，但可能重新引发所谓债券市场监督者对政府财政状况的担忧，从而引发国债抛售潮，推高债券收益率。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court's Friday ruling striking down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs lifted stock prices a bit but could revive worries about government finances among so-called bond vigilantes, sparking a Treasury selloff that could push yields higher.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-supreme-court-ruling-overturning-trump-nudges-up-stocks-could-spook-bond-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZHWMAHWZJOF3KQFWOELUH32KI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员博斯蒂克：GDP"相当强劲"的增长引发通胀担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联储主席拉斐尔·博斯蒂克周五表示，全年2.2%的经济增长率"是个相当强劲的数字"，其高位足以引发对持续通胀的担忧，并可能需要采取紧缩的货币政策来抑制经济增长。【原文：Full-year economic growth at 2.2% is "a pretty strong number" that is high enough to raise concerns about persistent inflation and likely require tight monetary policy to hold back the economy, Atlanta Fed President Raphael Bostic said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-bostic-pretty-strong-gdp-growth-raises-inflation-concerns-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALP4724O45MJPPYHF6BI3FJTDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回特朗普的关税后，企业将如何获得退款？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五裁定，特朗普总统依据经济紧急状态法征收的关税属非法行为。法院未说明政府应如何退还这笔非法关税，其金额估计达1750亿美元。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court said on Friday that tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump under an economic emergency law were illegal. The court did not say how the government should refund the illegal tariffs, worth an estimated $175 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/how-will-companies-get-refunds-now-that-us-supreme-court-has-rejected-trumps-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWPQ346WYBM4NFEKQNNSG2R5AI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid为提升盈利能力裁员12%]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lucid周五宣布将裁减12%的美国员工，这家电动汽车制造商正致力于提升毛利率并实现长期增长。【原文：Lucid said on Friday it was laying off 12% of its U.S. workforce as the electric-vehicle maker seeks to improve gross margin and long-term growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/lucid-trims-12-workforce-profitability-push-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P775BW5GQFNGHCLZIOZH6EYA3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国预计最高法院裁决后将与美国保持良好贸易关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国政府周五表示，在特朗普总统的大规模关税政策被美国最高法院推翻后，英国预计其与美国的特殊贸易地位将得以延续。【原文：Britain expects its privileged trading position with the United States to continue after the U.S. Supreme Court struck down President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, the government said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/uk-expects-continued-favourable-trade-with-us-after-supreme-court-ruling-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OJRHXMWHMJLMLN2GDCOVRT7Y3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业庆贺战胜特朗普关税，但退税仍需时日]]></title><description><![CDATA[当美国最高法院裁定推翻白宫紧急关税时，数千家企业赢得了一场艰苦卓绝的胜利。而退税流程才刚刚启动。【原文：Thousands of businesses won a hard-fought victory when the U.S. Supreme Court ruled to overturn the White House's emergency tariffs. The process of getting refunds has only just begun.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/business-celebrates-win-over-trump-tariffs-refunds-will-take-time-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W2AOWTMUYRKCLPB73Y463PBJ6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将于3月31日至4月2日访华，此行正值中美贸易紧张局势之际。]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫官员周五表示，美国总统唐纳德·特朗普将于3月31日至4月2日访华。在世界两大经济体关系紧张之际，这场备受瞩目的会晤日期就此敲定。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will travel to China from March 31 to April 2, a White House official said on Friday, setting dates for a highly anticipated encounter amid tension between the world's biggest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/trump-travel-china-march-31-april-2-amid-trade-tensions-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLVPQBETDFI4RLFHEV6TSDUWFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:36:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙称美国反垄断机构对华纳兄弟收购案的等待期已到期]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙影业周五表示，其以1084亿美元全现金收购华纳兄弟探索公司的美国反垄断审查等待期已于2月19日结束，这标志着收购HBO Max母公司的潜在交易迈出了重要一步。【原文：Paramount said on Friday the U.S. antitrust waiting period for its $108.4 billion all-cash bid for Warner Bros Discovery expired on February 19, marking a milestone on the road to a potential deal to acquire the owner of HBO Max.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/paramount-says-us-antitrust-waiting-period-warner-bros-bid-has-expired-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EA2BR74PPFNBVLMOGUUP6MOR7E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月新屋销售下滑；库存减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月新独栋住宅销量下滑，但开发商在缩减库存膨胀方面取得进展，这可能使他们能够启动更多新住房项目。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell in December, but builders made progress in reducing an inventory bloat, potentially allowing them to break ground on more new housing projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-new-home-sales-fall-december-inventory-declines-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MEQGOYNR2FM2REW5BPCJC65B7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:35:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股大涨，因美国最高法院驳回特朗普关税案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和欧洲股市周五大幅上涨，此前美国最高法院推翻了特朗普总统的关税政策——该政策是本届政府经济纲领的重要支柱。【原文：Stock markets in the United States and Europe jumped on Friday after the Supreme Court struck down U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs, a key pillar of the adminstration's economic platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-stocks-jump-after-us-supreme-court-rejects-trumps-tariffs-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H2JGS56FIVIQ5NX4KDS6IOY6Z4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普在GDP数据公布前于社交媒体发文暗示数据低迷，归咎于政府停摆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普似乎在数据公布前就预判了美国经济增长的年末表现令人失望，他批评民主党在去年秋季政府停摆期间扮演的角色拖累了经济总产出数据。【原文：President Donald Trump seemingly flagged a disappointing end-of-year reading on U.S. economic growth before it was made public, criticizing the role Democrats played in an extended government shutdown last fall that pulled down the economy's headline output numbers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-nodded-low-gdp-numbers-social-post-ahead-public-release-blaming-shutdown-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQQ3Q3P6FNKTXE5G6XCRV5VDO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:27:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从"买美国货"到"再见美国"，华尔街出逃潮加速蔓延]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国投资者正以至少16年来最快的速度撤出本国股市资金，因科技巨头回报率下滑，而表现更佳的海外市场显得更具吸引力。【原文：U.S. investors are pulling money out of their own stock market at the fastest pace in at least 16 years as Big Tech returns fade and better-performing overseas markets look more attractive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/buy-america-bye-america-wall-street-exodus-gathers-pace-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TQNHI4JGSBOMJOK4BUCM57BSR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《The Information》报道，OpenAI正在开发包括智能音箱在内的人工智能设备。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《信息报》周五援引知情人士报道，OpenAI正投入逾200人研发一系列人工智能设备，产品线将包含智能音箱，可能还包括智能眼镜和智能灯具。【原文：OpenAI has more than 200 people working on a family of AI-powered devices that will include a smart speaker and possibly smart glasses and a smart lamp, the Information reported on Friday, citing a person with knowledge of the plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-developing-ai-devices-including-smart-speaker-information-reports-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR6INNIVNNP5NPONW5SXODUI3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:08:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院驳回特朗普的全球关税案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五推翻了特朗普总统依据国家紧急状态法实施的广泛关税措施，驳回了其最具争议的权力主张之一。该裁决对全球经济产生重大影响。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court struck down on Friday President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs that he pursued under a law meant for use in national emergencies, rejecting one of his most contentious assertions of his authority in a ruling with major implications for the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-rejects-trumps-global-tariffs-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">476VJ5VCSJKCHC5RVHPMDDICBI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦监管机构批评联邦航空管理局对美联航维修操作的监管不力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局对美联航维护操作的监管因人员短缺、员工培训不力以及获取航空公司数据的障碍而受阻，联邦监管机构周五表示。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration's oversight of United Airlines’ maintenance practices is hindered by low staffing, ineffective workforce training and hurdles to accessing air carrier data, a federal watchdog said Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/federal-watchdog-faults-faa-oversight-united-airlines-maintenance-practices-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLFD3WCYLVPH5DVENTDBUBIBXQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:55:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普全球称美国2月商业活动增速放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一项调查显示，2月份美国商业活动扩张速度创10个月来最低水平，工厂订单减少，服务业新业务增长放缓，就业增长全面停滞。【原文：U.S. business activity expanded in February at the slowest rate in 10 months as orders receded at factories, new business growth slackened for services firms and employment growth stalled across the board, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-business-activity-growth-slows-february-sp-global-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTO7VO2DKFKXHFVNYHCURQ54K4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官维持对特斯拉自动驾驶致死事故的2.43亿美元判决]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官驳回了特斯拉支付2.43亿美元赔偿金的请求，该赔偿金本拟用于补偿2019年一起致命车祸的受害者——该事故涉及一辆配备自动驾驶功能的Model S车型。【原文：A federal judge rejected Tesla's request to pay $243 million to victims of a 2019 fatal crash of an Autopilot-equipped Model S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-judge-upholds-243-million-verdict-against-tesla-over-fatal-autopilot-crash-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VC4X6VK4WFNCVAN4Q5VDSWUAPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽柯钢铁公司任命内部人士杰克·沙利文为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国钢铁制造商纽柯公司周五宣布，任命内部人士杰克·沙利文为新任首席财务官，任命将于3月1日生效。【原文：U.S. steelmaker Nucor said on Friday it has appointed insider Jack Sullivan as its new finance chief, effective March 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nucor-promotes-insider-jack-sullivan-cfo-role-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCHA5JYMDZOUJCANPSD4TSQ6FM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[玩具制造商Funko在投资者Pleasant Lake的推动下，正探索战略选择。]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周四提交的监管文件显示，愉悦湖合伙公司披露其持有玩具制造商Funko约10%的股权，并表示该公司应考虑包括出售在内的战略选择方案。【原文：Pleasant Lake Partners disclosed a roughly 10% stake in toymaker Funko and said the company should consider strategic alternatives, including the possibility of a sale, according to a regulatory filing from Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/toymaker-funko-pushed-by-investor-pleasant-lake-explore-strategic-options-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3IK3HS6UIRORZKW6SUY53SENBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国个人消费支出通胀在12月升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[种种迹象表明，1月份经济增长将进一步加速，这将强化市场预期——美联储在6月之前不会降息。【原文：Signs are pointing to a further acceleration in January, which would strengthen expectations that the Federal Reserve would not cut interest rates before June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-pce-inflation-heats-up-december-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WKM2J6VXXRKJLD7C4SIZNGHR2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:46:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所新私募股权交易平台首笔交易启动]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦证券交易所周五启动了英国金融监管机构新推出的PISCES框架下的首笔交易，该框架允许投资者买卖私营公司股票。【原文：London Stock Exchange on Friday launched its first transaction under the UK financial regulator's new PISCES framework that allows investors to trade shares in private companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/london-stock-exchange-launches-first-transaction-under-new-private-share-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WORTVYOXRVP4BCWMSLJQQDIPHE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:44:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第四季度经济增速大幅放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部表示，上季度国内生产总值按年率计算增长1.4%。路透社调查的经济学家此前预测GDP增速为3%。【原文：Gross domestic product increased at a 1.4% annualized rate last quarter, said the Commerce Department.  Economists polled by Reuters had forecast GDP rising at a 3% pace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economic-growth-slows-sharply-fourth-quarter-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN6L4L4NDVN6BBBDIKXSYXMBIU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蓝猫股价再度下跌，投资者消化债务基金调整影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[蓝猫资本周五盘前交易中股价下跌约4%，延续了前一交易日的跌势。此前这家另类资产管理公司公布了最新计划，拟从一只小型债务基金中返还资本，该消息令投资者惊慌，并拖累同行股价下挫。【原文：Blue Owl Capital shares fell about 4% in pre-market trading on Friday, extending the previous session's slide, after the alternative asset manager unveiled its latest plan to return capital from a small debt fund that spooked investors and dragged peers lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blue-owl-drops-again-investors-digest-debt-fund-changes-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQX5AWW6ERJXVFBISWMZMPSPGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 13:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员称，尽管面临阻力，欧盟仍应准备好实施与南方共同市场的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员马罗什·谢夫乔维奇周五表示，尽管法国反对且面临法律挑战，欧盟仍应准备在未来数月内启动其与南美洲南方共同市场集团的争议性自由贸易协定。【原文：The European Union should be ready to put into force its contentious free trade agreement with South America's Mercosur bloc in the coming months despite opposition from France and a legal challenge, EU trade chief Maros Sefcovic said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-should-be-ready-enact-mercosur-deal-despite-resistance-trade-chief-says-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7VVI55UCJISBHV3CCENGKYGYM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:09:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利安德巴塞尔大幅削减季度股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[石化巨头利安德巴塞尔公司周五宣布削减第一季度股息，称这是化工行业遭遇的最长期低迷之一。【原文：Petrochemical maker LyondellBasell cut its first-quarter dividend on Friday, citing one of the longest downturns in the chemicals industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lyondellbasell-slashes-quarterly-dividend-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI3XDUGYNZOHPOPFRHRKEUTXWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市期货在经济数据公布前表现平淡]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市期货周五持平，投资者正等待关键经济数据以判断今年货币政策宽松的走向，同时密切关注与德黑兰的紧张局势以及美国最高法院对特朗普关税政策的潜在裁决。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were flat on Friday as investors awaited key economic data to gauge the path of monetary policy easing for the year while monitoring tensions with Tehran and a potential U.S. Supreme Court decision on Trump's tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-muted-ahead-economic-data-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4STPQE3MHNN3LMLBUP235ASXB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:52:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：原油被吞没]]></title><description><![CDATA[迈克·多兰和ROI团队本周末最期待阅读、观看和收听的内容。【原文：Everything Mike Dolan and the ROI team are excited to read, watch and listen to over the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCEZV6UV6BKNPHTQVWG3HFREOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金吸引五周来最大资金流入，因人工智能相关担忧缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至2月18日的七天内，全球股票基金迎来五周来最强劲的资金流入。人工智能股票担忧情绪缓解，投资者转向其他板块支撑了需求，而美联储降息预期重燃提振了市场对美国经济增长的信心。【原文：Global equity funds received their strongest inflows in five weeks in the seven days to February 18, as easing concerns over artificial intelligence stocks and investor rotation into other sectors supported demand, while renewed hopes for Federal Reserve rate cuts lifted sentiment toward U.S. growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-pix-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DG7HV76KXRMNBL3PRAH4GDCZTY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:31:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼-美国贸易协定要点]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚与美国周四敲定了一项贸易协议，将美国对东南亚最大经济体出口商品的关税从32%降至19%，此前双方进行了近一年的谈判。【原文：Indonesia and the United States finalised a trade deal on Thursday that cut U.S. levies to 19% from 32% on goods shipped from Southeast Asia's biggest economy, following nearly a year of negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/key-points-indonesia-us-trade-agreement-2026-02-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DPUVC3OF25LNXJZHWZE7CNNJTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>