<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:33:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:33:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普将终止对部分液化天然气出口许可证的延期要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划取消一些液化天然气（LNG）生产商申请出口许可证延期的要求。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump plans to abolish the requirement for some producers of liquefied natural gas (LNG) to seek export permit renewals, according to two sources with knowledge of the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/trump-end-need-some-lng-export-permit-renewals-sources-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF6DAZLKFRPZPLMQHQVNFLVGHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国防承包商告诉马斯克小组，五角大楼的官僚主义是问题所在]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的国防承包商之一 L3Harris Technologies 公司的首席执行官周三在一封信中告诉美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府效率小组，五角大楼庞大的承包系统过于缓慢和官僚，无法应对中国和伊朗构成的威胁，需要进行改革。【原文：The CEO of one of the world's biggest defense contractors, L3Harris Technologies, told President-elect Donald Trump's government efficiency panel in a letter on Wednesday that the Pentagon's huge contracting system is too slow and bureaucratic to meet threats posed by China and Iran and needs to be reformed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-defense-contractor-tells-musk-panel-that-pentagon-bureaucracy-is-problem-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUQ7RHNUDRI2TJGZP4XAXKS4T4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[殖民地管道公司的美国汽油大动脉可能关闭至周五]]></title><description><![CDATA[Colonial 管道公司在周三的一份声明中表示，由于该公司继续在佐治亚州保定县寻找疑似泄漏源，其美国汽油主干道预计将关闭至周五。【原文：Colonial Pipeline's main U.S. gasoline artery is expected to be shut through Friday as the company continues to search for the source of a suspected leak in Paulding County, Georgia, the company said in a statement on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/colonial-pipelines-main-us-gasoline-artery-likely-shut-until-friday-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRNW5FRDOFJV3E22KGJXW4E42A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的美国交通部官员称将继续调查特斯拉安全问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的交通部负责人表示，他将允许政府继续对特斯拉的高级驾驶辅助系统进行调查。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's nominee to head the Transportation Department said he would allow an ongoing government probe into Tesla's advanced driver assistance system to continue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-usdot-nominee-says-tesla-safety-probe-will-continue-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DN3DDFMUCBPJPCPBHX2UBU3ML4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[注释 BOX 投资者对加沙停火协议的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位了解谈判情况的官员说，谈判代表周三达成了一项分阶段协议，以结束以色列和哈马斯之间的加沙战争，在此之前，15 个月的冲突已造成数万巴勒斯坦人死亡，并激化了中东局势。【原文：Negotiators reached a phased deal on Wednesday to end the war in Gaza between Israel and Hamas, an official briefed on the negotiations said, after 15 months of conflict that has killed tens of thousands of Palestinians and inflamed the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/quote-box-investor-reactions-gaza-ceasefire-deal-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEXIXQV6RFNKXMDBJW3VLN57EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国经济持续疲软，奢侈品集团寄希望于美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于预计中国市场将更加疲软，全球奢侈品公司今年将使出浑身解数，说服美国购物者在钻石手镯、绗缝皮手袋和其他名牌时装上挥金如土。【原文：Global luxury goods companies are expected to pull out all the stops this year to persuade U.S. shoppers to splash out on diamond bracelets, quilted leather handbags and other designer fashions, given forecasts for more market weakness in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/luxury-groups-pin-hopes-us-china-weakness-persists-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7XF7BCTANI4RCLBTAWD4QJKDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州公用事业公司面临数十亿美元的火灾损失索赔，即使它没有做错任何事]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛杉矶野火可能是美国历史上损失最惨重的一场大火，这场大火的受害者正在利用加州独特的法律原则，如果电力公司的设备导致了大火，即使电力公司没有做错任何事，他们也可以向电力公司索赔。【原文：Victims of the Los Angeles wildfires, likely the costliest in U.S. history, are seizing upon a unique California legal doctrine that allows them to collect from their power utility if its equipment caused the blaze -- even if the company did nothing wrong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/california-utility-faces-billions-claims-fire-damage-even-if-it-did-nothing-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYB5L2AIJFMDNNRI6BXQXLATCU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田旗下日野汽车公司被控柴油排放造假]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车旗下日野汽车公司周三在底特律美国地区法院被指控欺诈，罪名是在美国非法销售 10.5 万台不符合排放标准的重型柴油发动机。【原文：Toyota Motor unit Hino Motors on Wednesday was charged with fraud in U.S. District Court in Detroit for unlawfully selling 105,000 heavy-duty diesel engines in the United States that did not meet emissions standards.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/toyota-unit-hino-motors-charged-with-diesel-emissions-fraud-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KX5OY7ZG6RMCBKOKMN4RZNTVSE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席财务官：削减成本协议之后，生产率必须提高]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周三看到，大众汽车首席财务官在向投资者发表的评论中说，要使其德国工厂具有竞争力，下一步就是要提高生产率，增加每个工人生产的汽车数量。【原文：Volkswagen's chief financial officer said in comments to investors seen by Reuters on Wednesday that the next step to making its German plants competitive was to improve productivity, increasing the number of cars produced per worker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-cfo-after-cost-cutting-deal-productivity-must-go-up-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ELPIFA65VFLZ5NNR7QZ5Y2DCPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英格兰银行泰勒称是时候降息了]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行最近任命的利率制定者艾伦-泰勒（Alan Taylor）周三表示，鉴于英国经济出现放缓迹象，英国央行应迅速采取行动降低利率。【原文：The Bank of England should move quickly to bring down interest rates given signs of a slowdown in Britain's economy, Alan Taylor, the BoE's most recently appointed interest rate setter, said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-englands-taylor-says-its-time-cut-interest-rates-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKTERES5IJOW5P5M3ORT266SEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易强劲，交易反弹，华尔街银行利润大增]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着交易量的回升以及股市走强对交易的提振，一些美国最大的贷款机构第四季度的利润出现增长，从而引发了周三银行股的反弹。【原文：Profits at some of the biggest U.S. lenders rose in the fourth quarter as dealmaking picked up and trading was boosted by strong equity markets, sparking a rally in banking stocks on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wrapup-profits-wall-street-banks-jump-with-trading-strength-dealmaking-rebound-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJM7O5DOAZKLFCCOIGEE2OEIWM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官称欧洲两大战斗机项目可能合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官纪尧姆-福里（Guillaume Faury）说，他可以预见，这两个独立的欧洲新型战斗机和作战航空系统项目将来会合并，或至少在设计上可以协同工作。【原文：Airbus CEO Guillaume Faury said he could see the two separate European programmes working on new fighter jets and combat air systems being combined in future or at least designed to work together.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-says-europes-two-fighter-jet-programmes-could-combine-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AU4MPCBO3RK7FHKM3PNFF722EQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛首席执行官称苹果卡合作可能在 2030 年前结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团首席执行官大卫-所罗门（David Solomon）周三表示，高盛与苹果公司的信用卡合作关系可能会在 2030 年合同到期前终止。【原文：Goldman Sachs' credit-card partnership with Apple may end before its contract runs out in 2030, Goldman CEO David Solomon said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-ceo-says-apple-card-partnership-may-end-before-2030-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWVU3TGWBRIAHAWWIPNCGIJNKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯称政策数据取决于非常不确定的环境]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周三表示，未来的货币政策行动将由经济数据驱动，因为该央行面临着很大程度上由政府潜在政策变化所导致的高度不确定性。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Wednesday that future monetary policy actions will be driven by economic data as the central bank confronts a high level of uncertainty in large part driven by potential government policy changes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-williams-says-policy-data-dependent-very-uncertain-environment-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWWUEDIXAVJVXAIXQYRE2ISSZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名人称电动汽车应付费使用道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美国交通部部长人选周三表示，电动汽车使用道路应付费。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's nominee to head the U.S. Transportation Department said Wednesday electric vehicles should pay to use roads.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-nominee-says-electric-vehicles-should-pay-use-roads-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RKUKG7SF5RN4JLS5KTTHEWOTOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会就设备维修限制起诉迪尔公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周三起诉农用设备制造商迪尔（Deere），称其迫使农民依赖其授权经销商网络，从而非法抬高了维修成本。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Wednesday sued farm equipment maker Deere , alleging it illegally drives up repair costs by forcing farmers to rely on its authorized dealer network.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-ftc-sues-deere-over-equipment-repair-restrictions-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E5RRRZRL4BJRTE4GBRUMW72MAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[密歇根州州长警告特朗普对墨西哥和加拿大征收关税可能损害美国汽车业]]></title><description><![CDATA[密歇根州州长格雷琴-惠特默（Gretchen Whitmer）周三警告说，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）建议对从墨西哥和加拿大进口的商品征收25%的关税，这可能会损害美国汽车行业，提高汽车价格，并使中国受益。【原文：Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer on Wednesday warned that potential 25% tariffs on imports from Mexico and Canada suggested by President-elect Donald Trump could harm the U.S. auto sector, boost vehicle prices and benefit China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/michigan-governor-warns-trump-tariffs-mexico-canada-could-harm-us-auto-sector-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JSGYEYZJ75PMDEF7DQF2BE2EWI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Novo Banco 所有者将在银行首次分红时收到 13.4 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国私募股权基金 Lone Star 和葡萄牙政府将在未来几个月 Novo Banco 首次派息时分享 13 亿欧元（13.4 亿美元）。【原文：U.S. private equity fund Lone Star and Portuguese authorities are set to share 1.3 billion euros ($1.34 billion) when Novo Banco makes its first dividend payout in the coming months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/novo-banco-owners-receive-134-bln-when-bank-makes-first-dividend-payment-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBO5G5IQZ5IR5JDRY3NUFBJK2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金称最新 CPI 数据显示物价压力继续缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周三表示，美国12月份的通胀数据表明，物价上涨压力正在继续缓解，此前一份政府报告显示，衡量物价上涨的一个重要基本指标上个月有所放缓。【原文：U.S. inflation data for December indicates price pressures are continuing to ease, Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said on Wednesday after a government report showed that an important underlying measure of price increases had slowed last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-says-latest-cpi-data-shows-price-pressures-continue-ease-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LS6ABABSCFLPROQ6MJLTVHYZG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:26:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[车队工会称本周将恢复与美国联合航空公司的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国联合航空公司 1 万多名维修技术人员的卡车司机工会周三表示，将在本周恢复与航空公司的谈判。【原文：The Teamsters union, which represents more than 10,000 United Airlines maintenance technicians, said on Wednesday it will resume negotiations with the carrier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/teamsters-says-negotiations-with-united-airlines-resume-this-week-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5HRWWEU3MZMUZAOV2QP2JQFOAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将命令汉莎航空恢复 Condor 进入其短途网络的权利]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周三告诉汉莎航空，它将命令这家德国国旗航空公司恢复 Condor 包机航空公司使用汉莎航空短途网络的权利，以便为 Condor 的法兰克福-纽约航线提供航班。【原文：The European Commission told Lufthansa on Wednesday it would order the German flag carrier to reinstate charter airline Condor's access to Lufthansa's short-haul network to feed Condor's Frankfurt-New York route.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-order-lufthansa-restore-condors-access-its-short-haul-network-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7LCQONFYFPR5JHO5BRTEX6Q6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加强对先进计算芯片的限制，防止其流入中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部表示，美国周三加强了对先进计算半导体的限制，以防止高端芯片流入中国。【原文：The United States strengthened restrictions on advanced computing semiconductors on Wednesday to prevent the diversion to China of high-end chips, the Commerce Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-strengthens-restrictions-advanced-computing-chips-prevent-diversion-china-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXI35E75TNORHLOFZCOSTJ7A5M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:05:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普新任证交会领导层准备启动加密货币全面改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士表示，美国证券交易委员会的共和党高官准备开始全面修订该机构的加密货币政策，最早可能在下周当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）上台后进行。【原文：Top Republican officials at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission are poised to begin overhauling the agency's cryptocurrency policies potentially as early as next week when President-elect Donald Trump takes power, said three people briefed on the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-new-sec-leadership-poised-kick-start-crypto-overhaul-sources-say-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6J54LRY3RJ35FYMSKEWTC3GGI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beacon Roofing 拒绝 QXO 的 110 亿美元收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[Beacon Roofing Supply 公司周三拒绝了建筑产品分销业新贵 QXO 公司价值 110 亿美元的收购要约，称其提议 "大大低估了 "这家屋顶材料供应商的价值。【原文：Beacon Roofing Supply on Wednesday rejected a $11 billion takeover offer from QXO , a new player in the building products distribution industry, saying its proposal "significantly undervalues" the roofing material supplier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/qxo-goes-public-with-11-bln-bid-beacon-roofing-threatens-proxy-fight-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KO5GHZBY7FJR7ILDDMUO2UDVNA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将 16 家实体列入贸易黑名单，其中 14 家在中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周三将 16 家实体列入贸易黑名单，其中包括一家中国公司，该公司生产的台积电芯片被非法集成到华为人工智能处理器中。【原文：The Biden administration added 16 entities to its trade blacklist on Wednesday, including a Chinese company whose TSMC-made chip was illegally incorporated into a Huawei artificial intelligence processor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-adds-16-entities-its-trade-blacklist-14-china-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FS5MJEHD6FMVJA6U2KOUOSFPVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官对每月 75 架飞机的目标充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官周三表示，他 "仍然有信心 "在2027年实现每月生产75架单通道飞机的目标。【原文：The chief executive of Airbus on Wednesday said he was "still confident" the company could reach its target of manufacturing 75 single-aisle aircraft a month in 2027.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-is-confident-about-75-aircraft-month-target-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U2KZNS36Y5NJTLTPRCZISSVXYQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软为企业推出 Copilot Chat，促进人工智能的应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软周三推出了一项聊天服务，允许企业按需使用人工智能代理执行日常任务，并押注于 "即用即付 "模式将推动该技术的应用。【原文：Microsoft on Wednesday rolled out a chat service allowing businesses to use on-demand AI agents for routine tasks, betting on the pay-as-you-go model to drive up the adoption of the technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/microsoft-launches-copilot-chat-businesses-boost-ai-adoption-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKASRQ2N7NOOFOPC2Z2XNEWQ7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对生物技术设备实施新的出口管制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周三表示，出于与人工智能和数据科学相关的国家安全考虑，将对生物技术设备和相关技术实施新的出口管制。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Wednesday it is imposing new export controls on biotechnology equipment and related technology because of national security concerns tied to artificial intelligence and data science.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-imposing-new-export-controls-biotechnology-equipment-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEAWCNNU7ZLPVOERDV7WBWY5U4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:12:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商恩智浦从欧洲投资银行获得 10 亿欧元贷款用于欧洲项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于荷兰的计算机芯片制造商恩智浦（NXP）周三表示，该公司已从欧洲投资银行（EIB）获得10亿欧元（10.3亿美元）贷款，用于支持欧洲五国的研发项目。【原文：Netherlands-based computer chip maker NXP said on Wednesday it has secured a 1 billion euro ($1.03 billion)loan from the European Investment Bank (EIB) to support research and development projects in five European countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmaker-nxp-gets-1-bln-euro-loan-eib-european-projects-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S5MC423ZDZNIHIE4FMDVGQE57Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:10:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 12 月 CPI 升幅略高于预期，美联储继续按计划行事]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于能源成本上涨，11 月份美国消费者物价涨幅略高于预期，这表明通胀趋势与美联储今年放缓降息步伐的观点一致。【原文：U.S. consumer prices increased slightly more than expected in November as energy costs rose, pointing to an inflation trend that lines up with the Federal Reserve's view for a slower path of rate cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-dec-cpi-rises-touch-above-expectations-keeps-fed-track-2025-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFATXCFIEZOTTIDVYGE2JOPNO4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 13:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>