<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:24:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 03:24:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[文件称，华纳兄弟缺乏回应助长了派拉蒙的恶意竞购]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一提交的一份证券文件显示，派拉蒙 Skydance 在第 11 个小时以 1,084 亿美元的价格恶意竞购华纳兄弟 Discovery 公司，其根本原因是该公司认为华纳兄弟公司对其上周晚些时候的热情示好缺乏回应。【原文：Paramount Skydance's 11th-hour, hostile $108.4 billion bid for Warner Bros Discovery was rooted in what it considered a lack of responsiveness from Warner Bros to its ardent overtures late last week, a securities filing on Monday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-lack-response-fueled-paramounts-hostile-bid-filing-says-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5W4K3YZO3ZMFVPLZX22ZZKDNYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 02:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市下滑，市场紧张等待美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市下跌，美元持稳，投资者为本周晚些时候的美国降息做准备，而日元在日本东北部地区发生强烈地震后表现平静，但影响有限。【原文：Asian stocks fell and the dollar was steady on Tuesday as investors braced for a cut in U.S. interest rates later this week while the yen was calm after a powerful earthquake rocked Japan's northeast region though the impact was limited.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHEM2NBLRZIYPJOKWEGIU52XII</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 02:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[估值飙升，Aware 超级首席信息官警告人工智能融资将亮起 "橙色 "灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚养老基金 Aware Super 的首席投资官表示，全球人工智能行业的一些资金安排闪烁着 "橙色 "灯光，但盈利增长支持了该行业目前的估值。【原文：The chief investment officer of Australian pension fund Aware Super says there are flashing "orange" lights in some funding arrangements in the global artificial intelligence industry but earnings growth is backing up the sector's current valuations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/aware-super-cio-warns-orange-lights-ai-financing-valuations-soar-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4IDKUZT4BLARLJP374VKFTDCI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 01:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓与 GIP 就 WAIO 电网达成 20 亿美元基础设施融资协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[必和必拓集团（BHP Group）周二表示，贝莱德（BlackRock）旗下的全球基础设施基金（GIP）将向西澳大利亚铁矿公司（WAIO）的内陆电力网络投资 20 亿澳元，获得少数股权。【原文：BHP Group said on Tuesday that BlackRock -owned Global Infrastructure Fund (GIP) would invest $2 billion in Western Australia Iron Ore's (WAIO) inland power network for a minority stake.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/bhp-strikes-2-bln-infrastructure-funding-deal-with-gip-waio-power-network-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BJRJQGRAJLOHNJ7H4AG7VCY24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 01:38:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油价格稳定，乌克兰和谈与美国利率决议成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场参与者密切关注结束俄罗斯乌克兰战争的和平谈判以及迫在眉睫的美国利率决定，油价在上一交易日下跌2%后于周二企稳。【原文：Oil prices steadied on Tuesday after slipping 2% in the previous session, as market participants kept a close eye on peace talks to end Russia’s war in Ukraine and a looming decision on U.S. interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-steadies-ukraine-peace-talks-us-rate-decision-spotlight-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SVMIFBJDA5NUJGTAQPTTZJU4OI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 01:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部指控两名中国男子试图走私 Nvidia 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周一表示，两名中国男子因涉嫌向中国走私英伟达（Nvidia）H100 和 H200 芯片而被拘留，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）为英伟达（Nvidia）向中国出口 H200 芯片开了绿灯。【原文：Two Chinese men are in custody for allegedly smuggling Nvidia H100 and H200 chips to China, the U.S. Justice Department said on Monday, as President Donald Trump gave the green light for Nvidia to export its H200 chips to Beijing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-justice-department-accuses-two-chinese-men-trying-smuggle-nvidia-chips-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6A6V3NWO5FMO7OZD7W2VYVTWRY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 01:19:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元在日本地震后表现坚挺，美联储和澳大利亚央行备受关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[隔夜日本东北部发生 7.5 级强烈地震后，日元在亚洲早盘交易中持稳，在包括美联储在内的几家央行做出政策决定之前，风险情绪进一步升温。【原文：The yen held steady in early Asian trading after a powerful 7.5-magnitude earthquake struck Japan's northeast overnight, adding to a risk-off mood ahead of several policy decisions from central banks including the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-resilient-after-earthquake-hits-japan-fed-rba-view-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DA6ABNGKGRPBJA3PERPOVB6NVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 01:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准首个人工智能工具用于加速肝病药物开发]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局（U.S. Food and Drug Administration）周一表示，该机构已对首个人工智能工具进行了鉴定，该工具旨在帮助医生在药物试验中评估一种严重的脂肪肝。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has qualified the first artificial intelligence tool designed to help doctors assess a severe form of fatty liver disease in drug trials, the agency said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-qualifies-first-ai-tool-help-speed-liver-disease-drug-development-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YZUS5OUP2FMEXEXYZEEL7IRSJU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[易观国际称，内燃机汽车在全球重新受到欢迎]]></title><description><![CDATA[专业服务集团安永（EY）周二发布的一份报告显示，由于政策逆转、贸易战以及对电动汽车基础设施和成本的日益怀疑，全球汽车买家正在回归内燃机。【原文：Car buyers worldwide are returning to combustion engines as a result of policy reversals, trade wars and growing skepticism about EV infrastructure and costs, a report by professional services group EY showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/combustion-engine-cars-regain-popularity-worldwide-ey-says-2025-12-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOGOECDG3JMFRHXSRSGPK4QS2A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大空头 "投资者伯利称拥有房利美和房地美，并认为潜在 IPO 有上升空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[因《大空头》而闻名的投资者迈克尔-伯里周一表示，他在房利美和房地美持有相当大的仓位，如果这两家美国抵押贷款融资巨头再次通过首次公开募股上市，他预计这两家公司的仓位将大幅上升。【原文：Investor Michael Burry, known for "The Big Short," said on Monday he owns sizable positions in Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac and expects them to rise materially if the U.S. mortgage finance giants are taken public again through initial public offerings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/big-short-investor-burry-says-he-owns-fannie-freddie-sees-upside-potential-ipos-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMFIF2PMMZO4NFBJLF3C4VE4R4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法院建议分两个阶段拍卖桑托斯大型港口码头，这对马士基公司是个打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西联邦审计法院（TCU）周一以六票对三票的结果建议，巴西计划在桑托斯港拍卖的超大型集装箱码头禁止当地其他此类码头的运营商参与第一阶段的竞标，理由是可能出现市场集中。【原文：Brazil's Federal Audit Court (TCU) on Monday recommended, by six votes to three, that the auction of Brazil's planned mega container terminal at the Santos port ban operators of other such terminals there from participating in the first phase of bidding, citing possible market concentration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-court-recommends-two-stage-auction-of-mega-santos-port-terminal-blow-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EW2IMBJAGJLFRBECGKVLUOWOJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HashKey 在香港首次公开募股，募集资金高达 2.147 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据本周二提交的招股说明书，香港最大的持牌加密货币交易所HashKey集团计划在其首次公开募股中筹集高达16.7亿港元（约合2.1466亿美元）的资金。【原文：HashKey Group , Hong Kong's largest licensed crypto exchange, is aiming to raise up to HK$1.67 billion ($214.66 million) in its initial public offering in the city, according to a prospectus lodged on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/hashkey-launches-hong-kong-ipo-seeking-up-2147-million-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GXXFW4VL5N3FDH2F6AUOTXFZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国初创公司寻求收回被马斯克的 X 公司 "遗弃 "的 Twitter 商标]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家新兴的社交媒体平台要求美国专利商标局取消 Twitter 的商标，以便将其据为己有，理由是亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 X 公司已经放弃了这些商标。【原文：A fledgling social media platform has asked the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office to cancel trademarks for Twitter so it can take them for itself, contending that billionaire Elon Musk’s X Corp has abandoned them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-startup-seeks-reclaim-twitter-trademarks-abandoned-by-musks-x-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BGVXA42VJLPRGFZ3LT64KARX4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[百事公司宣布与埃利奥特管理公司谈判，审查北美供应链]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事公司周一宣布对其北美供应链进行审查，并表示在与激进投资者埃利奥特投资管理公司（Elliott Investment Management）进行了数周的讨论后，将积极降低成本以推动增长。【原文：PepsiCo on Monday announced a review of its North America supply chain, and said it would aggressively reduce costs to drive growth after weeks of discussions with activist investor Elliott Investment Management.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/pepsico-announces-review-n-america-supply-chain-amid-talks-with-elliott-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPIGCIW4KRPLVNYQTBWWKJRYEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称，库什纳在华纳兄弟竞购中的角色引发道德问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[贾里德-库什纳（Jared Kushner）在派拉蒙公司以 1,080 亿美元竞购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）的过程中扮演了资助者的角色，这将特朗普家族的利益注入了多年来最大的媒体争夺战之一，引发了人们对总统的影响力是否会使天平倾斜的担忧。【原文：Jared Kushner's financing role in Paramount's $108 billion bid for Warner Bros Discovery injects Trump-family interests into one of the biggest media battles in years, raising concerns over whether the president's influence could tip the scales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/kushner-role-bid-warner-bros-raises-ethical-questions-experts-say-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFPHHRYABFPJ3KEBHFHKCZA2H4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:09:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普说，钱应该给人民，而不是给医疗保险公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一批评了保险公司，同时呼吁将资金直接提供给个人而不是保险公司，因为民主党人正在推动将即将到期的《平价医疗法案》医疗计划补贴延长三年。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday criticized insurance companies while calling for funds to go directly to individuals rather than insurers, as Democrats push for a three-year extension of expiring subsidies for Affordable Care Act health plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-money-should-go-people-not-health-insurers-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5FJFQHVK5LDPC4SGQYM7T6S4I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日 美联储不确定性打击股票和债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[对美联储本周晚些时候政策决定的担忧周一对华尔街构成了压力，而美国国债的持续抛售则将30年期国债收益率推升至三个月来的最高点。【原文：Apprehension ahead of the Federal Reserve's policy decision later this week weighed on Wall Street on Monday, while continued selling in U.S. Treasuries pushed the 30-year yield to its highest in three months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WZ4E3ZWANFOK5JSEEX2PQP64AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[餐厅运营商 Alsea 将在墨西哥开设 Raising Cane's 餐厅]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥餐厅运营商 Alsea 周一表示，该公司已与美国连锁鸡柳连锁店 Raising Cane's 签订开发协议，将在墨西哥开设餐厅。【原文：Mexican restaurant operator Alsea said on Monday it has signed a development agreement with U.S. chicken-finger chain Raising Cane's to open eateries in Mexico.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/restaurant-operator-alsea-open-raising-canes-mexico-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P4ZOCADLL5MPBH4P6LBTZ6MJWQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 和派拉蒙在好莱坞权力角逐中争夺华纳兄弟的发现权]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞公司对华纳兄弟发现公司发起了价值 1,084 亿美元的恶意收购，挑战竞争对手 Netflix 的出价，为好莱坞历史悠久的媒体公司的未来注入了不确定性。【原文：Paramount Skydance launched a hostile bid worth $108.4 billion for Warner Bros Discovery , challenging a rival offer from Netflix and injecting uncertainty into the future of Hollywood's storied media company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflix-paramount-fight-warner-bros-discovery-hollywood-power-tussle-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTLDRVAVUZIVPFC472RO4JVKZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:43:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将允许英伟达向中国运送 H200 芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，他将允许英伟达（Nvidia）向中国和其他国家的获批客户运送其 H200 芯片，但条件是必须继续确保国家安全。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday that he will allow Nvidia to ship its H200 chips to approved customers in China and other countries, under conditions that allow for continued strong national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-allow-nvida-ship-h200-chips-china-trump-says-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LJ62JDVOJN3NKBQ24MPO5X3EI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债券投资者押注温和宽松周期，坚守曲线中段]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储为 2025 年最后一次政策会议做准备之际，债券投资者正在为美联储的浅度宽松周期做准备，减少对长期国债的投资，转而投资中期国债，以获取更丰厚的回报。【原文：Bond investors are positioning for a shallow easing cycle from the Federal Reserve as it gears up for its final policy meeting of 2025, reducing exposure to long-duration Treasuries and rotating into intermediate maturities for juicier returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-bond-investors-bet-mild-easing-cycle-stick-middle-curve-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GINFQYDMMNME7GWSFG6QQXTUJU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府希望航空公司和机场提供更健康的食品和运动选择]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周一表示，希望航空公司和机场为旅客提供更健康的食品选择、锻炼设备以及家庭友好型设施，如游戏空间和护理设施。【原文：The Trump administration said on Monday it wants airlines and airports to offer travelers healthier food options, exercise equipment and family-friendly features like playspaces and nursing facilities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/trump-administration-wants-airlines-airports-offer-healthier-food-exercise-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMNNM5ZHHNOGLGAB7AMB35VF3M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称欧盟对 X 的罚款 "令人讨厌"，称欧洲正朝着 "错误的方向 "发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一称，欧盟技术监管机构对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的社交媒体公司 X 处以 1.2 亿欧元的罚款 "令人讨厌"，并表示他不理解欧洲监管机构如何证明此举是合理的。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday called a 120-million-euro fine imposed on Elon Musk's social media company X by EU tech regulators "a nasty one" and said he did not understand how European regulators could justify the move.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-calls-eu-fine-x-nasty-one-says-europe-going-bad-directions-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UW567OPSXVIXXAWH6JFQL5GQII</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 Netflix 和派拉蒙不是他的朋友，华纳兄弟之争白热化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，在 Netflix 和派拉蒙 Skydance 竞购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）之后，这两家公司都不是他的好朋友。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday that neither Netflix nor Paramount Skydance are great friends of his after both companies bid for Warner Bros Discovery .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-says-netflix-paramount-are-not-his-friends-warner-bros-fight-heats-up-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AL7SO4SCY5ME5MLZ57K3KXVLMU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府因移除跟踪移民特工行踪的应用程序而被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[在苹果公司将 ICEBlock 从其在线商店下架后，这款用于分享联邦移民特工目击信息的最流行应用程序的开发商周一起诉了特朗普政府，称其侵犯了言论自由。【原文：The developer of the most popular app used to share information about sightings of federal immigration agents sued the Trump administration on Monday, alleging free speech violations after Apple removed ICEBlock from its online store.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-administration-sued-over-removal-app-tracking-immigration-agents-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTXOZENGJNJIRJDG3HOH52BRYY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warby Parker 与谷歌将于 2026 年推出人工智能智能眼镜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Warby Parker 周一表示，它正在与 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌合作开发轻型人工智能眼镜，首款产品预计将于 2026 年推出。【原文：Warby Parker said on Monday it is collaborating with Alphabet's Google to develop lightweight AI-powered glasses, with the first product expected to launch in 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warby-parker-google-launch-ai-powered-smart-glasses-2026-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSGSMUQX5JPQLHF5I32RLEGKFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:21:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司以 3,000 万美元将芝加哥机场登机口转让给美国航空公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国纽约南区破产法院法官周一批准了美国精神航空公司的请求，该公司将以 3,000 万美元的价格向美国航空公司转让两个机场登机口。【原文：Spirit Aviation will transfer two airport gates to American Airlines for $30 million after a judge at the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York approved the company's request on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-transfers-chicago-airport-gates-american-airlines-30-million-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DITPLCPE4NNU3HA26NWYRW7XVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[医疗用品公司 Medline 拟在美国首次公开募股中筹资 54 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由私募股权投资支持的医疗用品供应商 Medline 公司周一表示，该公司计划在美国首次公开募股中筹集高达 53.7 亿美元的资金。【原文：Private equity-backed Medline is aiming to raise as much as $5.37 billion in its initial public offering in the United States, the medical supplies provider said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/medical-supply-firm-medline-aims-raise-54-billion-us-ipo-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM7JH4HHM5NEJDNU6KBYDQONRQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普：将通过取消环境限制来帮助拖拉机企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，农用设备已经变得过于昂贵，他的政府将通过取消一些影响拖拉机公司的环保规定来帮助它们。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday that farming equipment has gotten too expensive and his administration would help tractor companies by removing some environmental rules that affect them.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-will-help-tractor-companies-by-removing-environmental-restrictions-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXCGI43Z7ZINRLPZNCTPUANMBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:03:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大称七国集团财长在通话中讨论了出口管制和关键矿产问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大财政部长弗朗索瓦-菲利普-尚帕涅（Francois-Philippe Champagne）在一份声明中说，加拿大财政部长周一主持了七国集团（G7）财政部长虚拟会议，讨论出口管制和关键矿产问题。【原文：Canadian Finance Minister Francois-Philippe Champagne chaired a virtual meeting of G7 finance ministers on Monday to discuss export controls and critical minerals, the finance ministry said in a statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/g7-finance-ministers-discussed-export-controls-critical-minerals-call-canada-2025-12-08/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UF5HDM2ZQFLFHIMZGZYACEDSRI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>