<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:35:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:35:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英镑兑美元升至两年多来最高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，英镑兑美元汇率升至两年多来的高点，因为在美国预计很快将开始一系列降息之际，投资者从英国经济强劲的迹象中得到了安慰。【原文：Sterling rose to a more than two-year high versus the dollar on Friday, as investors took comfort from signs of strength in the British economy at a time when the United States is expected to soon embark on a series of interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/sterling-rises-highest-over-two-years-versus-dollar-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QGMOA53TMBJJFIGPVUODUCK2L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼亚 Safaricom 公司敦促对 Starlink 等卫星供应商提出新要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯尼亚最大的电信公司 Safaricom 已敦促监管机构考虑要求卫星互联网提供商（如埃隆-马斯克的 Starlink 公司）与当地移动网络运营商合作。【原文：Kenya's biggest telecoms company Safaricom has urged regulators to consider requiring satellite internet providers such as Elon Musk's Starlink to partner with local mobile network operators.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kenyas-safaricom-urges-new-requirements-satellite-providers-like-starlink-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNBABFRG3RKYTODIBYILWGKFYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:24:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国新屋销售升至一年多来最高水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于抵押贷款利率下降刺激了需求，7 月份美国新建独户住宅的销量升至一年多来的最高水平，为房地产市场的复苏提供了更多证据。【原文：Sales of new U.S. single-family homes rose to their highest level in more than a year in July as a drop in mortgage rates boosted demand, offering more evidence that the housing market is recovering.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-new-home-sales-rise-more-than-expected-july-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCFJ7JEJOZMZZDYXEZWBG35SJI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Third Point 信中称苹果股价仍有上升空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁对冲基金经理丹尼尔-勒布（Daniel Loeb）认为，苹果公司的股价还有攀升的空间，尤其是如果这家科技公司成功地将人工智能用于其 iOS 移动操作系统的话。【原文：Billionaire hedge fund manager Daniel Loeb sees room for Apple's stock price to climb, especially if the technology company successfully harnesses artificial intelligence for its iOS mobile operating system.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/third-point-sees-room-apple-stock-price-climb-letter-says-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R45SVHVSABI2DGUZ6RZL3IBIQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔在美联储杰克逊霍尔会议上的讲话要点摘录]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周五在怀俄明州杰克逊霍尔举行的堪萨斯城联储年度经济会议上的讲话要点：【原文：Here are key quotes from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's speech on Friday to the Kansas City Fed's annual economic conference in Jackson Hole, Wyoming:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/key-quotes-powells-speech-feds-jackson-hole-conference-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KO6AJX4A4FKSXKW6U7XASPQCWA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:06:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国间谍机构在多样性方面落后于文职人员队伍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家情报总监办公室周五发布的一份报告称，与美国文职人员相比，少数族裔、妇女和残疾人在美国间谍机构中的任职人数仍然偏低。【原文：Minorities, women and disabled persons are still underrepresented in U.S. spy agencies compared with the U.S. civilian workforce, said a report released on Friday by the Office of the Director of National Intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-spy-agencies-lag-civilian-workforce-diversity-says-report-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L3IIM54HSJLW7CCRJGMHEMAWJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 14:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杰克逊霍尔现场直播：美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）在堪萨斯城联储杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）年度研究会议上发表主题演讲，对降息充满期待。【原文：With eyes on a rate cut, Fed Chair Jerome Powell gives his keynote speech to the Kansas City Fed's annual Jackson Hole research conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jackson-hole-live-fed-chair-jerome-powell-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ANURS6LF6NC55KYTZINOLMZK3M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:37:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国因105家俄罗斯和中国公司援助俄罗斯军方而将其列为目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周五将105家俄罗斯和中国公司列入贸易限制名单，原因是这些公司被指控支持俄罗斯军方，而华盛顿正试图继续对莫斯科在乌克兰的战争努力施加压力。【原文：The United States on Friday added 105 Russian and Chinese firms to a trade restriction list over their alleged support of the Russian military as Washington seeks to keep up pressure on Moscow's war effort in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-adds-123-entities-entity-list-including-63-russia-42-china-federal-register-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3ZVXBL2EBJOROUERAWXSLYL3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称欧洲央行决策者对 9 月降息的看法趋于一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[越来越多的欧洲央行政策制定者支持 9 月份再次降息，只有未来几周出现重大数据意外才可能推迟降息。【原文：A growing number of European Central Bank policymakers are lining up behind another interest rate cut in September and only major data surprises in the coming weeks could delay the move, on and off record conversations with seven sources indicate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ecb-policymakers-views-converging-sept-rate-cut-sources-say-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25K2XII7UJJRHLEEYT6GTBLSTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:20:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的华尔街中间人为潜在的政府职位挖掘关系网]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国共和党总统提名人唐纳德-特朗普刚刚组建的过渡团队的联合主席已经开始利用他在华尔街工作时建立的关系网，为可能的政府建立一份数千名候选人的名册。【原文：The co-chair of U.S. Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump's freshly minted transition team has begun tapping his network from a career on Wall Street to build a roster of thousands of candidates to serve in a potential administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-wall-street-middleman-taps-network-potential-administration-roles-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGX6I5PKPJO7XD5HBD4TTKDFSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 6 月零售销售因利率影响下降 0.3%；7 月预计增长 0.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于消费者继续感受到高利率的影响，并减少了自由支配的购买，加拿大6月份的零售销售额有所下降。【原文：Canada's retail sales dropped in June, data showed on Friday, as consumers continued to feel the impact of high interest rates and cut back on discretionary purchases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-june-retail-sales-down-03-rates-weigh-seen-up-06-july-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7J55LOGP5PLNO6XMDX3K6DXWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:16:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，达美航空首席运营官迈克-斯帕诺斯将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五援引一份给员工的备忘录报道，达美航空公司首席运营官迈克-斯帕诺斯（Mike Spanos）将于下月离职，到另一家公司担任新职务。【原文：Delta Air's chief operating officer, Mike Spanos, will leave the airline next month to take on a new role at another company, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing a memo to employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/delta-air-coo-mike-spanos-leave-carrier-wsj-reports-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LSPB5OJWOFIHPNWDCVXIYU7KLQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[券商预测 9 月降息，市场为鲍威尔讲话做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多数券商预测美国联邦储备委员会将在 9 月份降息 25 个基点，尽管金融市场正密切关注美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五在杰克逊霍尔（Jackson Hole）发表的演讲。【原文：Most brokerages have forecast a 25 basis points interest rate cut by the U.S. Federal Reserve in September, even as financial markets strap in for clearer cues from Chair Jerome Powell's Jackson Hole speech on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/brokerages-predict-september-rate-cut-market-braces-powell-speech-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47MH2KIIF5MM5BTPFKBBNUBNSI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 6 月零售销售因汽车销售下降 0.3%；预计 7 月增长 0.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[8月23日（路透社）--加拿大统计局周五表示，受机动车和零部件经销商销售额下降的影响，加拿大6月份零售销售额为657.3亿加元（483.7亿美元），比5月份下降0.3%。该机构在一份速报估计中说，7月份的销售额可能增长了0.6%。【原文：Aug 23 (Reuters) - Canadian retail sales fell by 0.3% in June from May at C$65.73 billion ($48.37 billion), led by lower sales at motor vehicle and parts dealers, Statistics Canada said on Friday. Sales were likely up 0.6% in July, the agency said in a flash estimate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-june-retail-sales-down-03-autos-seen-up-06-july-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6KAKJNEL5JLAJEHAP374OVTEBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 12:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 7 月工厂销售额很可能增长 1.1%--Statscan 预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[8月23日（路透社）--加拿大统计局（Statistics Canada）在周五的一项速报估计中称，加拿大7月份的工厂销售额很可能比6月份增长1.1%，这主要是受石油和煤炭产品以及化工子行业销售额增长的推动。【原文：Aug 23 (Reuters) - Canadian factory sales most likely rose 1.1% in July from June, largely driven by higher sales in petroleum and coal product as well as chemical subsectors, Statistics Canada said in a flash estimate on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-july-factory-sales-most-likely-up-11-statscan-flash-estimate-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCM3XTDNLNPBHGNVYVBFQ7IN3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 12:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ozempic 上榜华尔街 2027 年医疗保险药品谈判名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在，美国政府已经就 2026 年生效的部分医疗保险计划药品价格进行了谈判，华尔街分析师们正押注 2027 年的药品清单，其中将包括诺和诺德公司治疗糖尿病的大片 Ozempic，这对大药厂的影响有限。【原文：Now that the U.S. government has negotiated prices for some Medicare program drugs effective in 2026, Wall Street analysts are betting on a 2027 list that will include Novo Nordisk's blockbuster Ozempic for diabetes and have a limited impact on Big Pharma.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/ozempic-wall-streets-list-2027-medicare-drug-negotiations-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2QTQQREFJK3REBRP2SPXW6KM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 12:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，雀巢首席执行官施奈德下台，为老将弗莱克西铺平道路]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士周五告诉路透社，雀巢首席执行官马克-施耐德（Mark Schneider）因集团业绩不佳而被这家全球最大的食品制造商突然解雇。【原文：Nestle CEO Mark Schneider was ousted in a sudden move by the world's biggest foodmaker as a result of the group's underperformance, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nestle-ceo-schneider-was-ousted-paving-way-veteran-freixe-sources-say-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRD2YS54H5PDZI37ZCN7VNEDMY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 11:23:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所期货上涨，美联储主席鲍威尔的讲话令人期待]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于原油和金属价格上涨，与加拿大主要股指挂钩的期货周五上涨，而投资者则在等待美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔当天晚些时候的讲话。【原文：Futures linked to Canada's main stock index rose on Friday as crude and metal prices gained, while investors awaited U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's address later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tsx-futures-rise-fed-chair-powells-speech-anticipated-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52H7W7KYHRI2RFAD4MPRNKWKXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电池主管告诉美国联邦科学院：大众汽车的电池目标并非 "一成不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司电池主管周五告诉德国《金融时报》，该公司到2030年建设200千兆瓦时电池产能的目标并非 "一成不变"，该公司将密切关注电动汽车（EV）需求的发展。【原文：Volkswagen's goal of building 200 gigawatt hours of battery capacity by 2030 is not "set in stone" and the carmaker will monitor how demand for electric vehicles (EVs) develops, its batteries chief told German newspaper FAS on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagens-battery-targets-not-set-stone-battery-chief-tells-fas-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2I4F24ZJZO4JNYXTIFS5VR5JA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雀巢首席执行官施耐德因公司业绩不佳而下台 - 三位消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的消息人士周五告诉路透社，雀巢首席执行官马克-施耐德（Mark Schneider）因集团业绩不佳而被这家全球最大的食品制造商突然解雇。【原文：Nestle CEO Mark Schneider was ousted in a sudden move by the world's biggest foodmaker as a result of the group's underperformance, three sources familiar with the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nestle-ceo-schneider-was-ousted-due-companys-underperformance-three-sources-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCDKVTKEW5JPFJPCHZPI66ZQUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hugo Boss 股东 Frasers 申请购买更多股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份提交给德国竞争管理机构的文件显示，Hugo Boss 的第二大股东、英国体育和时装零售商 Frasers 已申请收购这家德国公司的更多股份。【原文：Hugo Boss' second-biggest shareholder, British sports and fashion retailer Frasers , has filed a request to acquire more shares in the German company, according to a filing with the German competition authority seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/hugo-boss-shareholder-frasers-files-request-buy-more-shares-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUD4PRKLU5I6BN47TLUNIUT4IU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国兴业银行放弃伦敦金属交易所环形交易会员资格]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦金属交易所（LME）周五表示，法国兴业银行（Societe Generale International）从 8 月 27 日起将不再是该交易所的环形交易会员。【原文：Societe Generale International will no longer be a ring-dealing member of the London Metal Exchange (LME) as of Aug. 27, the exchange said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/societe-generale-drops-ring-dealing-membership-lme-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASCJNUCTHJOS7OB4GGHPHBQPAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈利伯顿公司证实某些系统遭到网络攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[油田服务公司哈里伯顿（Halliburton）周五表示，有未经授权的第三方进入了该公司的某些系统。【原文：Oilfield services firm Halliburton said on Friday that an unauthorized third party had gained access to certain of its systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/halliburton-confirms-cyber-attack-certain-systems-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BQMYN265BJCBDF2PJM3ZK42VI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息押注和经济增长担忧缓解影响，美国股票基金吸引大量资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至8月21日的七天里，美国股票基金吸引了大量资金流入，这主要是受到对美联储9月份降息的押注以及对经济增长可能下滑的担忧缓解的推动。【原文：U.S. equity funds attracted significant inflows in the seven days to Aug. 21, bolstered by bets of a Federal Reserve rate cut in September and easing worries about a potential downturn in economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-equity-funds-draw-large-inflows-rate-cut-bets-easing-growth-concerns-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYK7WU3Z6VNCNC5MZPOVIIFF6U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杂货店增加政治捐款，民主党人也不甘示弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对联邦选举委员会（Federal Election Commission）数据的分析表明，在本轮国会选举中，民主党议员从大型食品公司获得的政治捐款水平有所上升，尽管许多民主党议员指责美国顶级食品连锁店及其供应商以消费者为代价抬高价格。【原文：The level of political donations from major food companies accepted by Democratic lawmakers has ticked higher this congressional election cycle, even as many Democrats have accused the top U.S. grocery chains and their suppliers of pushing prices higher at consumers' expense, a Reuters analysis of Federal Election Commission data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/grocery-stores-boost-donations-democrats-criticize-their-business-practices-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRLH7Y4TPFMFJHQONIXQZ6UVIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克的 SpaceX 公司在危险的太空行走中测试突破性技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[SpaceX 下周将尝试首次私人太空行走，这将是对埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空公司迄今为止最冒险的任务之一--包括超薄宇航服和无气闸舱在内的开创性设备的一次测试。【原文：SpaceX's attempt at the first ever private spacewalk next week will be a test of trailblazing equipment, including slim spacesuits and a cabin with no airlock, in one of the riskiest missions yet for Elon Musk's space company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/musks-spacex-testing-breakthrough-tech-risky-spacewalk-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FXPROVQDNNSDKDLWLVPAGK5RU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:05:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：鲍威尔发表讲话，美元陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHWQOYQ6TJLNTB2KBZ4AVZ6HOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金因美联储降息希望而大幅流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至8月21日的一周内，全球投资者受到美联储9月降息预期和美国经济担忧缓解的鼓舞，纷纷将资金投入股票基金。【原文：Global investors ploughed money into equity funds in the week to Aug. 21, encouraged by expectations of a Federal Reserve rate cut in September and easing concerns about the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2CCS2V4PBOINMWJPFQOCXVOCU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:46:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔将成为杰克逊霍尔会议的焦点，期货价格坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周五走高，投资者在等待美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔在杰克逊霍尔经济研讨会上的讲话，以寻找全球最大经济体降息的线索。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Friday with investors awaiting Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's comments at the Jackson Hole Economic Symposium for clues on interest-rate cuts in the world's biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-firm-powell-set-take-center-stage-jackson-hole-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK574TK4YJLX3PRB7SSFNGX5UQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，CVC、DSV 为德国铁路申克公司提交了约 1560 亿美元的最终出价]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉内情的人士告诉路透社，德国铁路的物流部门全球国际货运已收到由 CVC Capital Partners 和丹麦运输公司 DSV 牵头的财团的最终出价，该财团对该业务的估值约为 140 亿欧元（约合 155.7 亿美元）。【原文：Deutsche Bahn's logistics unit Schenker has collected final bids from a consortium led by CVC Capital Partners and Danish transport firm DSV that value the business at around 14 billion euros ($15.57 billion), two people familiar with the matter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/cvc-dsv-submit-final-bids-around-156bln-deutsche-bahns-schenker-sources-say-2024-08-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIABHFUXTRKUTDSEVRSFWDA764</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>