<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:09:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:09:18 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构就Grok平台的性化图像问题对X平台展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国媒体监管机构通信管理局（Ofcom）周一启动对埃隆·马斯克旗下X平台的调查，以确定该平台是否履行了保护英国民众免受可能在英国构成违法内容侵害的职责。【原文：Britain's media regulator Ofcom on Monday launched an investigation into Elon Musk's X to determine whether it has complied with its duties to protect people in the UK from content that could be illegal in the UK.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/uk-regulator-launches-investigation-into-x-over-grok-sexualised-imagery-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQOKPJQEUVOVFMDCKLIG4EDE5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步在亚利桑那州面临性侵诉讼，其安全记录受到审视]]></title><description><![CDATA[优步本周将在亚利桑那州凤凰城面临庭审，一名女性指控通过该应用预约的司机对其实施性侵，并就此提起诉讼。【原文：Uber is set to face trial this week in Phoenix, Arizona, in a lawsuit brought by a woman who says she was sexually assaulted by a driver she booked through the app.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/uber-faces-sexual-assault-trial-arizona-that-puts-its-safety-record-under-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6Q2DQC3KRJWNJBUHPX4UBLHRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:03:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度TCS季度营收超预期，人工智能需求推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度最大软件服务公司塔塔咨询服务公司周一公布的第三季度营收超出预期，人工智能驱动的需求持续攀升。【原文：Tata Consultancy Services , India's largest software services firm, posted a bigger-than-expected third-quarter revenue on Monday as artificial intelligence-led demand ramped up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/indias-tcs-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimate-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DDG4KPB6WNKBNC4A675BFKWYIQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:35:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车在中国销量跌至第三，快速增长的吉利汽车实现反超]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业数据显示，大众汽车去年在中国市场的销量被吉利汽车超越，跌至第三位。此前在2024年，大众汽车已将其在世界最大汽车市场长达十年的霸主地位让给了比亚迪。【原文：Volkswagen was overtaken by Geely Auto in sales in China last year, dropping to third place after losing its decade-long dominance in the world's largest auto market to BYD in 2024, industry data showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-drops-third-china-sales-fast-growing-geely-auto-overtakes-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPB4B4ZKXFNNNLIEKJSKKUXBKY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街对特朗普提出的信用卡利率上限提案能否推进持怀疑态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普提出的将信用卡利率上限设为10%的提案虽引发广泛关注，但华尔街分析师指出，该提案需通过立法程序，且获批可能性微乎其微。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's proposal to cap credit card interest rates at 10% has grabbed headlines but would require legislation and has slim odds of passing, Wall Street analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-skeptical-trumps-proposed-credit-card-rate-cap-will-advance-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTBR7GCDUVMPPNOCTD6SH363AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普呼吁限制信用卡利率后，美国金融股下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一美国金融股在盘前交易中下跌，此前总统特朗普呼吁对信用卡利率实施为期一年的上限，此举威胁到银行及其他贷款机构的关键收入来源。【原文：U.S. financial stocks fell in premarket trading on Monday after President Donald Trump called for a one-year cap on credit card interest rates, threatening a key revenue stream for banks and other lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-financial-stocks-fall-after-trump-calls-credit-card-rate-cap-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEWFBUIFSFI2JF2WK4CDORJAD4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达索航空投资法国国防人工智能独角兽哈玛坦公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国航空航天集团达索航空正牵头对初创企业哈玛丹人工智能公司进行2亿美元融资，随着地缘政治竞争加剧，国防领域正竞相利用人工智能技术。【原文：French aerospace group Dassault Aviation is leading a $200 million funding round in startup Harmattan AI as the defence sector races to leverage artificial intelligence amid intensifying geopolitical competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/dassault-aviation-invests-french-defence-ai-unicorn-harmattan-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YTUYXCXCBVK3XPSUUOIKPKS4I4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[依维柯与PlusAI扩大合作，在西班牙开展自动驾驶卡车测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动驾驶卡车初创企业PlusAI周一宣布，将启动南欧首个重型自动驾驶卡车测试项目，并扩大与依维柯集团旗下品牌IVECO的合作。【原文：Self-driving truck startup PlusAI said on Monday it would launch Southern Europe's first programme to test heavy-duty autonomous trucks, expanding its partnership with Iveco Group brand IVECO.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/iveco-plusai-expand-partnership-with-autonomous-truck-tests-spain-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLZ3JEGQIBLCTGDLFVFZSOEQDA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛首席经济学家称美联储决策不会受鲍威尔面临刑事调查威胁影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛首席经济学家扬·哈齐乌斯周一表示，美联储主席面临刑事起诉威胁将加剧市场对央行独立性的担忧，但他预计美联储将继续基于数据作出决策。【原文：Goldman Sachs’ chief economist Jan Hatzius said on Monday that a criminal indictment threat facing the Federal Reserve chairman would reinforce central bank independence worries, but he expected the Fed to continue to make decisions based on data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-chief-economist-says-fed-decisions-will-not-be-swayed-by-powell-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PWIOABTS5NJJBAXRDYZ7SN7NU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:58:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁格陵兰引发黄金之外避风港的追寻，国防领域亦然]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者纷纷加码黄金和欧洲防务类股票，以应对美国总统特朗普威胁要控制格陵兰岛的言论。他们担忧由此引发的地缘政治裂痕可能导致北约解体、全球秩序崩溃并损害美元价值。【原文：Investors have piled fresh bets on gold and European defence stocks in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's threats to take control of Greenland, fearing a geopolitical rift that could end NATO, shatter the global order and damage the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-greenland-threat-triggers-search-shelter-beyond-gold-defence-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYTB54K7UFNETCXOBGM36VCGVY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星链竞争对手欧洲卫星通信公司向空客订购340颗OneWeb卫星]]></title><description><![CDATA[由法国和英国政府支持的卫星运营商欧洲卫星通信公司（Eutelsat）已向空客公司订购340颗卫星，用于更新和扩展其OneWeb低轨道卫星网络。两家公司周一宣布了这一消息。【原文：Eutelsat , the satellite operator backed by the French and the British governments, has placed an order with Airbus for 340 satellites to refresh and extend its OneWeb low-Earth-orbit network, the two companies said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/starlink-rival-eutelsat-orders-340-oneweb-satellites-airbus-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TUY7IEELJO3HAB5EOMOSMXK7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国JD Sports在美国核心市场推出人工智能商业服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国运动服饰零售商JD Sports Fashion周一宣布，其最大市场美国地区的顾客将能够使用人工智能平台搜索并购买其产品。【原文：British sportswear retailer JD Sports Fashion said on Monday customers in the United States, its largest market, will be able to use AI platforms to search for and purchase its products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/britains-jd-sports-launches-ai-commerce-key-us-market-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6EYCIN26BORRK42YACQWRZFK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银拒绝瑞士银行新规提案，提议成本更低的替代方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银周一驳回了政府为加强银行监管而提出的方案，这些方案是在瑞信倒闭后提出的。瑞银表示这些方案将削弱瑞士的竞争力，并主张采取成本更低的替代方案。【原文：UBS on Monday rejected government proposals to strengthen regulations for the bank in the wake of the collapse of Credit Suisse, saying they would make Switzerland uncompetitive and arguing instead for less costly alternatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-rejects-proposed-swiss-bank-rules-moots-less-costly-alternatives-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOHENEM7BROX7F3NT6A3Q5BPWI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者对美联储生死攸关的决战感到焦虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者表示，全球最具影响力的中央银行的独立性正面临公开考验。【原文：The independence of the world's most powerful central bank is openly on the line, investors said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-anxious-over-make-or-break-fight-fed-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQE4XIG6ANKCRALDBLVNBXQM6Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 08:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国IQE公司预测2025年国防与人工智能需求将推动盈利增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国IQE公司周一表示，2025财年营收和调整后核心利润预计将达到预测区间的上限，需求主要来自军工国防、人工智能、数据中心及手机等领域。【原文：Britain's IQE expects revenue and adjusted core profit for fiscal 2025 at the upper end of its forecasts, the semiconductor wafer maker said on Monday, with demand driven by the military and defence, AI, data centres, and handset sectors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uks-iqe-forecasts-2025-earnings-boost-defence-ai-demand-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PCU6FJYT2JNPJA2KT24QEGNLJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BESI报告显示第四季度初步订单价值达2.5亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[BE半导体工业公司——欧洲最大的芯片封装设备供应商之一——周一初步报告称，其第四季度订单环比增长。【原文：BE Semiconductor Industries , one of Europe largest suppliers of chip assembly equipment, preliminarily reported a sequential rise in fourt-quarter orders on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/besi-reports-preliminary-orders-worth-250-million-euros-q4-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z544KJ27FBPGNL65ZND2TIBTXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[海尼根首席执行官因销售疲软且投资者不满而辞职]]></title><description><![CDATA[海尼根首席执行官多尔夫·范登布林克周一意外辞职。此前他领导这家荷兰啤酒巨头六年，并在制定新战略仅数月后便卸任。当前啤酒行业正竭力刺激消费者增加啤酒购买量。【原文：Heineken's CEO Dolf van den Brink resigned unexpectedly on Monday after six years of leading the Dutch brewer and only a few months after setting its new strategy, as the industry battles to get drinkers buying more beer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/heinekens-van-den-brink-step-down-ceo-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77GYE4DRUJL4BLBENNZGTMLW3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Counterpoint报告称，2025年苹果将以20%的市场份额领跑全球智能手机市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Counterpoint Research周一表示，2025年全球智能手机出货量同比增长2%，这得益于新兴市场需求和经济动能的增强。【原文：Global smartphone shipments rose 2% year-on-year in 2025, lifted by stronger demand and economic momentum in emerging markets, Counterpoint Research said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/apple-leads-global-smartphone-market-with-20-share-2025-says-counterpoint-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LECK5T4WQBLBVBNQC3KNCZ5LLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:44:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[招聘机构称，人工智能和科技专家需求推动英国金融业职位空缺增长12%]]></title><description><![CDATA[招聘公司摩根麦金莱周一表示，随着企业竞相参与技术军备竞赛，对人工智能、监管、数据报告及其他专业技能人才的需求推动英国金融业职位空缺在2025年增长12%。【原文：Demand for workers in AI, regulation, data reporting and other specialist skills drove vacancies in Britain's financial sector up 12% in 2025, recruiting firm Morgan McKinley said on Monday, as companies sought to keep up in a technology arms race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/demand-ai-tech-experts-pushes-uk-financial-sector-vacancies-up-12-recruiter-says-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCFQWF4VYFLHRKTOSKP3UBZUQE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早盘竞价：鲍威尔反击令市场震荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[安库尔·班纳吉带您展望欧洲及全球市场今日走势【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Ankur Banerjee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KVOJ647UNOXZE2UGAQC3YPKQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:33:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者将目光投向意大利房地产丑闻之外]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利房地产市场在2026年可能超越其他欧洲国家，因为政治稳定以及米兰建筑许可丑闻后监管整顿提振了投资者信心——尽管供应限制迫在眉睫。【原文：Italy's property market could outpace other European countries in 2026 as political stability and a regulatory clean-up after a Milan building permits scandal boost investor confidence - even as supply constraints loom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/investors-look-beyond-italys-real-estate-scandal-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M65YFVDJJZPWHMT27DBLZDYQ2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 05:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛预测2026年油价将走低，因供应激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛周日在一份报告中表示，尽管与俄罗斯、委内瑞拉和伊朗相关的地缘政治风险将继续推动市场波动，但今年油价可能因供应激增导致市场过剩而走低。【原文：Oil prices are likely to drift lower this year as a wave of supply creates a market surplus, although geopolitical risks tied to Russia, Venezuela and Iran will continue to drive volatility, Goldman Sachs said in a note on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/goldman-projects-lower-oil-prices-2026-supply-swells-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N65LL6B3KJO27PUFTRERSMAQ7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛下调美联储降息预期，因就业数据疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛周日推迟了对美联储降息的预测，目前预计将在2026年6月和9月各降息25个基点，而非此前预期的3月和6月。【原文：Goldman Sachs pushed back its forecast for U.S. Federal Reserve rate cuts on Sunday, now expecting two 25-basis-point reductions in June and September 2026 instead of the previously anticipated moves in March and June.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-sachs-pushes-back-us-fed-rate-cut-forecast-after-soft-jobs-data-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HIDNQWPPZRLPRPV27VQMSPZI5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普团队加紧对美联储主席鲍威尔的攻击，威胁以刑事指控相逼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔称此举是特朗普为大幅降息而获取更多利率控制权的"借口"。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell called the action a "pretext" to gain more influence over interest rates Trump wants cut dramatically.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-team-ramps-up-attack-feds-powell-with-criminal-indictment-threat-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHPCXYSMPVN5ZFYWYPSRAOXCJY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电第四季度利润有望飙升27%，人工智能需求推动增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的人工智能芯片制造商台积电预计，第四季度净利润将跃升27%至创纪录水平，这得益于人工智能基础设施看似永无止境的需求。【原文：TSMC, the world's largest manufacturer of advanced artificial intelligence chips, is expected to post a 27% jump in fourth-quarter net profit to a record due to the seemingly insatiable demand for AI infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tsmc-q4-profit-poised-soar-27-ai-demand-drives-growth-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YOPJC6TWG5IHTHMMH2RHBNBG7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[股市震荡，美元走软，特朗普与美联储的争端加剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔表示特朗普政府曾威胁要对他提起刑事指控，引发投资者对央行独立性的担忧，美元走低，美国股指期货下跌。
标普500指数期货下跌0.5%，欧洲期货在亚洲早盘下跌0.1%，美元兑多数主要货币下跌约0.2%，跌破158日元关口，兑欧元汇率跌至1.1660美元。交易员表示，该消息令人不安，但对利率的直接影响尚不明确。
基准10年期国债期货上涨3个基点，隐含收益率为4.15%，较上周五现货市场收盘水平低约1个基点。联邦基金期货显示今年降息预期增加约3个基点，虽幅度有限但暗示美联储可能被迫采取更激进政策。
金价触及每盎司4600美元以上历史新高，伊朗局势动荡推升贵金属价格并支撑油价。鲍威尔周日称，特朗普政府曾威胁对他提起刑事指控，并就其去年夏天在国会作证时涉及美联储大楼翻修项目一事发出大陪审团传票，他称此举是迫使央行降息的"借口"。
这些事态发展标志着鲍威尔与美国总统唐纳德·特朗普之间斗争的戏剧性升级，这场斗争可追溯至2018年鲍威尔担任美联储主席初期。悉尼投资银行Barrenjoey首席利率策略师安德鲁·利利表示："特朗普正在扯动央行独立性的松散线头。"
"他采取这些举措的唯一原因，是意识到无法掌控美联储，因此试图施加最大程度的不当压力。投资者对此不会感到高兴，但这恰恰表明特朗普已无其他手段可施。现金利率将维持在美联储公开市场委员会多数成员期望的水平。"
美元反应最为剧烈，甚至对澳元、纽元等典型风险敏感货币也出现下跌，并助推日元摆脱158日元兑1美元的干预风险区间。澳大利亚国民银行外汇策略主管雷·阿特里尔表示："美联储与美国政府之间的公开对抗...显然对美元不利。"
此外，特朗普威胁干预伊朗局势——该国针对神职阶层的抗议活动似乎正在加剧——这支撑了油价近期涨幅，并凸显了未来一年地缘政治风险的持续发酵。在连续几个交易日大幅上涨后，基准布伦特原油期货下跌约40美分，至每桶62.90美元。
MSCI亚太地区（除日本外）最广泛的股票指数小幅上涨0.5%，而日本市场因假日休市。新年第二周将公布美国通胀数据、中国贸易数据，以及从周二摩根大通和纽约联邦银行开始的一系列美国企业财报。【原文：The dollar fell and U.S. equity futures slid after Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said the Trump administration threatened him with a criminal indictment, stoking investor worries about the central bank's independence.
S&amp;P 500 futures were down 0.5%, while European futures slipped 0.1% in the Asia morning and the dollar was roughly 0.2% lower against most major peers, sending it below 158 yen and to $1.1660 per euro . 
Traders said the news was unsettling, though the immediate implication for interest rates was not clear.
Benchmark 10-year Treasury futures rose 3 ticks for an implied yield of 4.15%, which is about a basis point below Friday's cash market close. Fed fund futures have added in about three basis points more in cuts this year, which is small but points to the risk that the Fed gets pushed into being more aggressive.
Gold struck a record high of more than $4,600 an ounce, as unrest in Iran lifted precious metal prices and supported oil. 
On Sunday, Powell said the Trump administration had threatened him with a criminal indictment and served grand jury subpoenas over Congressional testimony he gave last summer regarding a Fed building renovation project, an action he called a "pretext" aimed at pressuring the central bank to cut interest rates.
The developments amount to a dramatic escalation in the fight between Powell and U.S. President Donald Trump, which dates back to the banker's first years as chair in 2018.
"Trump is pulling at the loose threads of central bank independence," said Andrew Lilley, chief rates strategist at Barrenjoey, an investment bank based in Sydney.
"The only reason that he's taking these steps is that he knows that he's not going to take control of the Fed, so he wants to exert as much undue pressure as he can.
"Investors won't be happy about it, but it shows actually Trump has no other levers to pull. The cash rate will stay what the majority of the FOMC wants them to be."
The dollar had the sharpest reaction, falling even against typically risk-sensitive currencies like the Australian and New Zealand dollars and helping the yen to escape from intervention-risk territory on the weak side of 158 per dollar.
"This open warfare between the Fed and the U.S. administration ... it's clearly not a good look for the U.S. dollar," said National Australia Bank's head of currency strategy Ray Attrill.
Elsewhere, Trump's threats to intervene in Iran, where protests against the clerical establishment appear to be intensifying, helped oil prices hold recent gains and underlined the swirling geopolitical risks for the year ahead.
After sharp gains in recent sessions, benchmark Brent crude futures were down about 40 cents to $62.90 a barrel.
MSCI's broadest index of Asia-Pacific shares outside Japan crept 0.5% higher, while Japanese markets were closed for a holiday.
The second full week of the New Year will include U.S. inflation data, trade figures from China and a slew of U.S. earnings beginning with JPMorgan Chase and BNY on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ARHY2QG25ZLN3MZAEY27QTRBIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚限制访问Grok AI，因性化图像引发的反响持续扩大]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚周日暂时封禁了Grok的访问权限，成为继该生成式人工智能聊天机器人因允许用户创建并发布色情图像引发全球强烈反对后，采取行动的又一国家。【原文：Malaysia on Sunday temporarily blocked access to Grok, joining a growing list of countries taking action after the generative artificial intelligence chatbot sparked a global backlash by allowing users to create and publish sexualised images.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/malaysia-restricts-access-grok-ai-backlash-over-sexualised-images-widens-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7ZPERLACVOG3MVWWCHSQBIUTQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观察：特朗普与美联储矛盾升级，投资者反应激烈]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫与美国中央银行之间的紧张关系在周末急剧升级，美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔表示，政府曾威胁要以美联储总部翻修项目相关罪名对他提起刑事指控。【原文：Tension between the White House and the U.S. central bank sharply escalated over the weekend, with U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell saying the administration had threatened him with a criminal indictment related to the Fed headquarters renovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-investors-react-trump-fed-feud-escalates-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ATZC3BVQDZMATDBVDST75SB5PI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:38:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国奥维通在香港上市首日开盘小幅走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国半导体设计公司奥维通集成电路的股票在香港交易所首日上市时将小幅高开，此前该公司通过在香港二次上市筹集了48亿港元（6.1591亿美元）。【原文：Shares of Chinese semiconductor design company OmniVision Integrated Circuits are set to open slightly higher on their first day of trading on the Hong Kong bourse after having raised HK$4.8 billion ($615.91 million) from a second listing in the city.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-omnivision-open-slightly-higher-hong-kong-trading-debut-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KYLWH4PHJRPNZKUD2FA25NATVE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元因美联储主席鲍威尔涉刑事调查而剧烈波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑欧元汇率周一早盘从一个月高位回落，因美国检方对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔启动刑事调查，加剧了与特朗普政府的紧张关系。【原文：The U.S. dollar retreated from its strongest in a month early on Monday, as U.S. prosecutors opened a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, adding to tensions with the Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-reels-criminal-probe-into-fed-chair-powell-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDMGFCO5CVKFDCBNDQ7X3RCE7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>