<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:34:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会就投资模型漏洞对美国对冲基金的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周四就对冲基金 Two Sigma 未能解决其投资模型中已知漏洞的指控达成和解。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Thursday settled charges against hedge fund Two Sigma over failure to address known vulnerabilities in its investment models, the regulatory agency said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/sec-settles-charges-against-us-hedge-fund-over-investment-model-vulnerabilities-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZWJLABAKPZJ5JE5X7EDJAYLIN4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:26:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部人选称废除债务限额问题 "细致入微]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）选择的财政部负责人斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，取消美国债务限额的问题 "有细微差别"，但他表示，如果特朗普希望取消债务限额，他将与特朗普和国会合作完成这项工作。【原文：Scott Bessent, U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's choice to head the Treasury Department, on Thursday said the question of eliminating the U.S. debt limit is "nuanced," but said if Trump wants to do so he will work with him and with Congress to get it done.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-us-treasury-pick-says-question-debt-limit-repeal-is-nuanced-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XPSAWSKFXZKEFBNUMTPHC2MRCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft 赢得股东对财报错误诉讼的驳回]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官周四驳回了一起指控 Lyft 欺骗股东的诉讼，该诉讼指控 Lyft 过久才纠正财报中关于一项关键利润指标的错误，这一错误导致这家共享单车公司的股价大幅波动。【原文：A federal judge on Thursday dismissed a lawsuit accusing Lyft of defrauding shareholders by waiting too long to correct a mistake in an earnings release about a key profit metric, an error that caused the ride-sharing company's stock price to gyrate wildly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/lyft-wins-dismissal-shareholder-lawsuit-over-earnings-report-error-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTNNOIQZQNM75JXE2APS5VJVKA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：等待中国数据，美国收益率走低]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WCU3CYZWYJLZZJ7JLBBLJWURV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克首席独立董事梅洛迪-霍布森将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[咖啡巨头星巴克周四表示，公司董事会首席独立董事梅洛迪-霍布森（Mellody Hobson）将离职。【原文：Coffee giant Starbucks said on Thursday that Mellody Hobson, the lead independent director of the company's board, will depart.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-lead-independent-director-mellody-hobson-depart-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPRC4P34HJML7BBASWBYXWSNDQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部研究发现：在气候风险地区，美国房屋保险费用涨幅更大]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四发布的一份研究报告显示，在最有可能遭受飓风、野火和其他气候灾害破坏的地区，房主支付的保险费用远远高于那些居住在风险最小地区的房主。【原文：Homeowners in areas most at risk of damage from hurricanes, wildfires and other climate perils pay far more for insurance than those who live in the least exposed areas, according to a U.S. Treasury Department study released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-home-insurance-costs-rose-more-steeply-areas-climate-risk-us-treasury-dept-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XUHXQ5WQ5OSNHZZNHILROLOQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美泰首席财务官 DiSilvestro 将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[芭比娃娃母公司美泰公司周四表示，首席财务官 Anthony DiSilvestro 将于 5 月 15 日退休。【原文：Barbie parent Mattel said on Thursday Chief Financial Officer Anthony DiSilvestro will retire on May 15.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mattel-cfo-disilvestro-retire-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWIA3HQOU5KS3JNJCC6FZVJS5U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:17:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会禁止通用汽车向消费者报告机构披露驾驶员和消费者数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周四在一份声明中表示，将禁止美国通用汽车公司在五年内向消费者报告机构披露消费者的敏感地理位置和驾驶员行为数据。【原文：U.S. automaker General Motors will be banned for five years from disclosing consumers' sensitive geolocation and driver behavior data to consumer reporting agencies, the Federal Trade Commission said in a statement on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ftc-bans-gm-disclosing-driver-consumer-data-consumer-reporting-agencies-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVIHRVIBAVJ7FIGCARG7ZFQOUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:13:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院解除对诺华仿制药 Entresto 的禁令]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国上诉法院结束了对 MSN 推出其仿制版诺华大片心脏衰竭药物 Entresto 的临时禁令后，制药商 MSN 制药公司在推出其仿制版诺华大片心脏衰竭药物 Entresto 的道路上又扫清了一个障碍。【原文：Drugmaker MSN Pharmaceuticals cleared another hurdle on Thursday toward launching its generic version of Novartis' blockbuster heart-failure drug Entresto after a U.S. appeals court ended a temporary pause on MSN's launch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-appeals-court-lifts-pause-generic-version-novartis-entresto-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQVG6CU7JFMONFNMXYD4P6UNIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:08:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，施罗德公司将裁员 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引一位熟知内情的人士的话报道称，施罗德公司正计划裁员约 3%。【原文：Schroders is planning to lay off about 3% of its workforce, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a person familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/schroders-cut-3-workforce-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHFKARJQRRL3TD6KVID5P6QNI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:34:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会将Snapchat有关人工智能聊天机器人的投诉移交给司法部]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）周四表示，已将针对 Snap 公司的投诉移交给司法部，该投诉称 Snapchat 的信息应用 Snapchat 使用了人工智能聊天框，对年轻用户造成了伤害。【原文：U.S. Federal Trade Commission said on Thursday it has referred to the Justice Department a complaint against Snap, Inc., that alleges its messaging app Snapchat used an artificial intelligence chatbox that harmed young users.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-ftc-refers-snapchat-complaint-over-ai-chatbot-justice-dept-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2LZSISYLEFIATMVF3GMN37G2EI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:22:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会和科罗拉多州起诉房地产公司 Greystar，称租房者被隐性收费欺骗]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（FTC）周四表示，美国联邦贸易委员会和科罗拉多州已对一家多户租赁物业管理公司 Greystar 提起诉讼，指控该公司在租赁费用方面以隐藏费用欺骗消费者。
"联邦贸易委员会主席莉娜-M-汗（Lina M. Khan）在声明中说："联邦贸易委员会起诉 Greystar 公司欺骗性地宣传低月租，但随后却向租户收取数百美元的隐藏垃圾费。
Greystar 在周四的一份声明中否认了这一指控。
"Greystar 发言人在声明中说："联邦贸易委员会非但没有与 Greystar 合作，帮助推动住房租赁行业对消费者有意义的改善，反而在本届政府任期的最后几天选择了抢头条的诉讼。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission and the State of Colorado have filed a complaint against Greystar, a multi-family rental property manager, alleging that it deceived consumers about rental costs with hidden fees, the FTC said on Thursday.
"The FTC is suing Greystar for deceptively advertising low monthly rents only to later saddle tenants with hundreds of dollars of hidden junk fees,” FTC Chair Lina M. Khan said in the statement.
Greystar denied the allegations in a statement on Thursday.
"Rather than working with Greystar to help drive meaningful improvements for consumers in the rental housing industry, the FTC has opted for headline-grabbing litigation in the waning days of the current administration," a Greystar spokesperson said in the statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-ftc-colorado-sue-property-firm-greystar-alleging-renters-deceived-by-hidden-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ABAXNYPREVNMFK7GAL6DJHCLLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁麦考特对在任何 TikTok 交易中保留原始投资者持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国亿万富翁弗兰克-麦考特周四告诉路透社，他对TikTok收购中国短视频应用TikTok美国业务的任何交易保持 "开放态度"，包括创始人在内的TikTok现有投资者将继续参与。【原文：Businessman Frank McCourt is "open-minded" to keeping TikTok's existing investors, including the founder, involved after any deal to buy the U.S. operations of the Chinese-owned short-form video app, the U.S. billionaire told Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/billionaire-mccourt-open-keeping-original-investors-any-tiktok-deal-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WJLUTZ5ZQZIRXCV3ARA3RYSLPM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:46:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德控股希望将康泰伦特的规模扩大一倍，着眼于特朗普对美国制造业的关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德（Novo Nordisk）的控股股东诺和诺德控股公司（Novo Holdings）的一位投资公司高级合伙人表示，该公司希望在五年内将其最近收购的合同药品制造商康泰伦特（Catalent）的规模扩大一倍，以应对美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）可能对美国制造业的关注。【原文：Novo Holdings, the controlling shareholder of Novo Nordisk , hopes to double the size of its recently acquired contract drugmaker Catalent over five years, a senior partner at the investment firm said, as it prepares for a likely focus on U.S. manufacturing by President-elect Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-holdings-looks-double-catalent-size-with-eye-trump-us-manufacturing-focus-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7ZMF3NU3NKSPEMHXWUZKCMKTI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:24:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，花旗集团裁减更多职位]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，花旗集团本周将裁减更多职位，以实现首席执行官简-弗雷泽（Jane Fraser）的开支目标。【原文：Citigroup is cutting more jobs this week to meet CEO Jane Fraser's expense goals, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citigroup-axes-more-jobs-bloomberg-reports-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T7GHCKXXIRNG5E5TMUPW7TRB7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软将在面向消费者的 Microsoft 365 中加入 Copilot 功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[微软公司周四表示，在推出面向企业的按需人工智能代理一天后，它已将Copilot人工智能功能纳入面向个人消费者的Microsoft 365套件。【原文：Microsoft said on Thursday that it is now including Copilot AI features to its Microsoft 365 suite for individual consumers, a day after it rolled out on-demand AI agents for businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-now-include-copilot-microsoft-365-consumers-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIPGMAT3KFO4JJQHVYPF2WNXME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国亿万富翁莱昂-布莱克击败强奸指控者的诽谤上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州一家上诉法院周四作出有利于亿万富翁投资者莱昂-布莱克的裁决，驳回了一名妇女提出的诽谤指控，这名妇女还指控这位阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）的联合创始人犯有强奸和性虐待罪。【原文：A New York state appeals court ruled in favor of billionaire investor Leon Black on Thursday, rejecting a defamation claim by a woman who also accused the Apollo Global Management co-founder of rape and sexual abuse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-billionaire-leon-black-defeats-rape-accusers-defamation-appeal-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JV3DG3CIOFLF5DQOAOUAZUZED4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行警告美国关税可能降低全球经济增长前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行周四警告说，如果美国的贸易伙伴以关税作为报复，美国征收10%的全面关税可能会使本已乏善可陈的2025年2.7%的全球经济增长率下降0.3个百分点。【原文：The World Bank on Thursday warned that U.S. across-the-board tariffs of 10% could reduce already lackluster global economic growth of 2.7% in 2025 by 0.3 percentage point if America's trading partners retaliate with tariffs of their own.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/world-bank-warns-that-us-tariffs-could-reduce-global-growth-outlook-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVXBUQGI2RMA3HT6PK7PGM5RFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际清算银行警告：关税推动的美元升值带来全球滞胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[央行伞式组织国际清算银行的工作人员警告说，如果即将上任的美国总统唐纳德-特朗普承诺的贸易关税继续推高美元，全球将出现滞胀。【原文：Staff at central bank umbrella group, the Bank for International Settlements, have warned of a global bout of stagflation if trade tariffs promised by soon-to-be-U.S. President Donald Trump continue to drive up the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tariff-fuelled-dollar-gains-pose-global-stagflation-risks-bis-warns-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSV4ZVRXHJPVBP4IHXQZFC7XRA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部部长人选称美联储应保持独立]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部长人选周四在参议院小组会议上表示，美联储应保持独立。【原文：The Federal Reserve should stay independent, Trump's pick to be U.S. Treasury Secretary told a Senate panel on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/fed-should-stay-independent-trumps-pick-us-treasury-secty-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A452K4EFCFIYBMZISO3MM3D5HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部称，美国运通将支付 1.087 亿美元和解欺骗性营销指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，信用卡公司美国运通已同意支付 1.087 亿美元，以了结对其从事欺骗性营销行为的指控。【原文：Credit card company American Express has agreed to pay $108.7 million to settle allegations that it engaged in deceptive marketing practices, the U.S. Justice Department said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/american-express-pay-1087-mln-settle-deceptive-marketing-allegations-justice-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XVB7QKOT6ZJKTMWN7TYBMQN5AA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:34:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪称洛杉矶大火可能给南加州爱迪生公司带来风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪评级公司（Moody's Ratings）在周四的一份报告中称，洛杉矶县中部的伊顿大火给电力供应商南加州爱迪生公司（Southern California Edison）带来了潜在的信用风险，该公司在大火最初引发的地区运营电力线路。【原文：The Eaton Fire in central Los Angeles County poses a potential credit risk to power provider Southern California Edison, which operates electrical lines in the area where the destructive blaze first started, Moody's Ratings said in a report on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/moodys-says-la-fire-may-pose-risk-southern-california-edison-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCVBACWHPZNTRLRWDVJP2QE5XQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通预测，2025-2026 年数据中心支出可将美国国内生产总值提高 20 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通（J.P.Morgan）估计，随着科技公司竞相从人工智能热潮中获益，数据中心的支出可能会在 2025-2026 年间为美国经济增长贡献 10-20 个基点。【原文：J.P.Morgan estimated spending on data centers could contribute between 10-20 basis points to U.S. economic growth in 2025-2026 as technology companies race to benefit from the artificial intelligence boom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/jpmorgan-forecasts-spending-data-centers-could-boost-us-gdp-by-20-basis-points-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGF5XG6LBJIPTASDV26ZNY6LBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着 "TikTok 难民 "在禁令发布前加入，中国应用程序 RedNote 本周获得数百万美国用户]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析公司 Similarweb 的最新数据显示，随着大量自称为 "TikTok 难民 "的用户加入，中国社交媒体应用红笔记（RedNote，在中国被称为小红书）在本周早些时候的一天内增加了近 300 万美国用户。【原文：Chinese social media app RedNote, known in China as Xiaohongshu, gained nearly 3 million U.S. users in one day earlier this week as a flood of self-proclaimed "TikTok Refugees" joined, according to new data from analytics firm Similarweb.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-app-rednote-gained-millions-us-users-this-week-tiktok-refugees-joined-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A2X6RROMBJ2PEWQVRUC7WIV64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示，瑞银获得新的美国养老金许可证，纠正了文书工作中的错误]]></title><description><![CDATA[文件显示，美国劳工部批准了瑞银继续管理美国退休计划所需的豁免权，此前的文书工作错误曾使这家瑞士银行所监管的 110 亿美元资产面临风险。【原文：The U.S. Department of Labor granted UBS a waiver the Swiss bank needs to continue managing U.S. retirement plans after a paperwork error had put the $11 billion of assets the lender oversees at risk, documents show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-gets-fresh-us-pensions-licence-fixing-paperwork-error-filings-show-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHVA4EV2H5PXTPHK5W3EGXDL5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的美国财政部人选贝森特表示延长减税是首要任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）选择的财政部负责人斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周四表示，延长特朗普将于今年年底到期的 2017 年减税政策是 "当前最重要的经济问题"。【原文：Scott Bessent, U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's choice to head the Treasury Department, on Thursday said that extending Trump's 2017 tax cuts that are set to expire at the end of this year is "the single most important economic issue of the day."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-us-treasury-pick-bessent-says-extending-tax-cuts-top-priority-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ER3EGQYIKFLVHJZ3NTS2OM32QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊在开普敦开设随身携带中心，努力争取市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国电子商务巨头亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周四在南非开设了一个随身购物中心，该中心将帮助其独立卖家吸引更多客户并拓展业务，同时亚马逊公司也在努力争取市场份额。【原文：U.S. e-commerce giant Amazon.com opened on Thursday a walk-in centre in South Africa that it says will help its independent sellers attract more customers and expand their businesses, while it also seeks to gain market share.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-opens-cape-town-walk-in-centre-strives-market-share-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKXILXL5LBPT5DSXDCJPE3ROA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技团体起诉美国联邦金融业委员会，要求阻止有关支付应用程序和数字钱包的规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，两个技术贸易团体起诉美国消费者金融保护局，要求阻止一项新规定，该规定赋予监管机构对大型非银行支付应用和数字钱包的监管权。【原文：Two technology trade groups sued the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau on Thursday to block a new rule giving the regulator supervisory authority over payment apps and digital wallets from large non-banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tech-groups-sue-us-cfpb-block-rule-payment-apps-digital-wallets-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNZYBZVUFJKPZLQVUV5ZZRITTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顾问称，如果达成协议，特朗普将阻止 TikTok "消失]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的新任国家安全顾问周四表示，如果有可行的协议，新政府将让 TikTok 在美国继续存在。【原文：President-elect Donald Trump's incoming national security adviser said Thursday the new administration will keep TikTok alive in the United States if there is a viable deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-will-keep-tiktok-going-dark-if-deal-is-table-adviser-says-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRJCSOG2LZNDPBIZDDQ3R7JUXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:35:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的沃勒：如果通货紧缩符合预期，美联储可能很快就会减息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事克里斯-沃勒（Chris Waller）周四发表评论称，通胀可能继续缓解，并可能允许美联储比预期更早、更快地降息，这与近期市场预期美联储降息路径较浅的走势背道而驰。【原文：Inflation is likely to continue to ease and possibly allow the Federal Reserve to cut rates sooner and faster than expected, Fed governor Chris Waller said Thursday in comments that pushed against recent market moves that anticipated a shallower Fed rate path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-waller-cuts-could-come-sooner-than-later-if-disinflation-meets-expectations-2025-01-16/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBBNPXPOXBLVHK2Y2CXUA74R4Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>