<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:06:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:06:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国不顾反对，批准为马斯克的 "星链 "提供更高功率的手机服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会周五表示，将允许埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的 SpaceX 旗下公司 Starlink 以更高的功率水平与 T-Mobile 运营直达蜂窝服务，尽管竞争对手公司提出了反对意见。【原文：The U.S. Federal Communications Commission on Friday said it would allow Starlink, a unit of Elon Musk's SpaceX, to operate a direct-to-cell service with T-Mobile at higher power levels despite objections by rival companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-okays-higher-power-cellphone-service-musks-starlink-despite-objections-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2OYT35D7FP3DIC2F2VCLQ2UQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空飞机与公务机险些相撞后，美国联邦航空局将加强对小型飞机的检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周五表示，在2月25日芝加哥发生一起严重的险些失事事件后，该局将采取措施解决涉及通用航空和公务喷气机的安全问题。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said Friday it taking steps to address safety issues involving general aviation and business jets after a serious Feb. 25 near-miss incident in Chicago.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/faa-step-up-small-plane-scrutiny-after-close-call-between-southwest-plane-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFJLHVXIRNONDNDHZ6KYUCD24I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普发动贸易战，美国和加拿大农民面临化肥价格飙升问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[距离边境两侧的春播只有几周时间了，已经面临谷物价格低迷的加拿大和美国农民正准备迎接另一个经济打击：在北美贸易战的背景下，化肥账单将更加庞大。【原文：With only weeks until spring planting on both sides of the border gets underway, Canadian and U.S. farmers, already facing low grain prices, are bracing for another economic blow: even bigger fertilizer bills amid a North American trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-canadian-farmers-face-soaring-fertilizer-prices-amid-trump-trade-war-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">56JNDV4S7VP55MS3PA5CQQIJVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒就经济面临的不确定性和关税风险发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周五表示，在此类政策可能导致通胀压力上升的情况下，要掌握特朗普关税制度的影响仍然是一项挑战。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said Friday it still remains challenging getting a handle on the impact of the Trump tariff regime, in a climate where these sorts of policies could lead to higher inflation pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-warns-uncertainty-tariff-risks-economy-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMCA2VXIRVMZ7FKXDZXDVQDVQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷 SE 预计大众汽车股权减值税后亏损 217 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车的最大股东保时捷公司（Porsche SE）周五表示，预计 2024 年将出现约 200 亿欧元（约合 217 亿美元）的税后亏损，理由是此前披露的其在欧洲顶级汽车制造商所持股份的减值。【原文：Porsche SE , Volkswagen's largest shareholder, expects a 2024 loss after tax of around 20 billion euros ($21.7 billion), it said on Friday, citing previously disclosed impairments on its holding in Europe's top carmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-se-expects-217-bln-loss-after-tax-volkswagen-stake-impairment-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LMX5MPAHOFO7JC3RFPC72EG2JE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FAA 称 SpaceX 星际飞船爆炸中断近 240 次飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）称，SpaceX 公司的 "星际飞船"（Starship）爆炸导致周四约 240 架航班中断，包括二十多架飞机因担心太空碎片而改道。【原文：The Federal Aviation Administration said the explosion of SpaceX's Starship spacecraft disrupted about 240 flights Thursday, including requiring more two dozen airplanes to divert over space debris concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-says-spacex-starship-explosion-disrupted-nearly-240-flights-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5COENNUWBVND7LUKH4XBDZG2KI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达飞轮船公司首席执行官告诉《回声报》，该公司正在与美国船厂谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国达飞海运集团首席执行官鲁道夫-萨德（Rodolphe Saade）告诉《回声报》，该集团正在与造船厂商谈在美国建造中型集装箱船的可能性。【原文：CMA CGM is in talks with shipyards about the possibility of having medium-sized container vessels built in the United States, the French shipping group's CEO Rodolphe Saade told Les Echos newspaper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cma-cgm-talks-with-us-shipyards-ceo-tells-les-echos-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SEK2EDDOBMCVFKEXUMNJU4WVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIE 鲍威尔称美联储正等待观察特朗普政策对经济的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔周五在纽约市的一个经济论坛上表示，美国央行将不急于降息，同时等待特朗普新政府的政策对经济的影响更加明朗。【原文：The U.S. central bank will be in no rush to cut interest rates while it waits for more clarity on how the policies of the new Trump administration affect the economy, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said at an economic forum in New York City on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-powell-says-fed-marking-time-see-economic-impact-trump-policies-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HLSE2NTFBPOVMEQ2OZQQDLJSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:23:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将就中国推动半导体产业发展的努力举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国贸易代表办公室将于周二就中国制造的老式 "传统 "半导体举行听证会，美国可能会对来自中国的芯片征收更多关税，这些芯片为从汽车、洗衣机到电信设备等日常用品提供动力。【原文：The U.S. Trade Representative's Office will hold a hearing on Tuesday into older Chinese-made "legacy" semiconductors that could heap more U.S. tariffs on chips from China that power everyday goods from autos to washing machines to telecoms gear.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-hold-hearing-chinas-efforts-boost-semiconductor-industry-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIDSIHNAVJIC3EEQFTVOL6FSFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利因关税担忧下调美国 2025 年经济增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利周五下调了对美国2025年经济增长的预期，理由是关税带来的影响更大，以及劳动力市场仍然紧张导致通胀率上升。【原文：Morgan Stanley lowered its 2025 economic growth forecast for the United States on Friday, citing greater impact from tariffs and a still-tight labor market resulting in higher inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/morgan-stanley-cuts-us-growth-forecast-2025-tariff-concerns-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJL24IV4MRPT3D6J5AZZU3EY44</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司称 Siri 的部分人工智能改进将推迟到 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周五表示，对语音助手 Siri 的一些人工智能改进将推迟到 2026 年。【原文：Some artificial intelligence improvements to Apple's voice assistant Siri will be delayed until 2026, the company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-says-some-ai-improvements-siri-delayed-2026-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J32VZ2ZHLVNHJO6N5RMUCQS3GY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称利率政策可能维持一段时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周五表示，不断上升的通胀风险表明，央行应在更长时期内采取稳定的利率政策。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Friday that rising inflation risks argue for an extended period of steady central bank interest rate policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-kugler-says-rate-policy-likely-hold-some-time-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMBMRLW7ZJMAVEAHAX6IZRWUNQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 17:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，加拿大皇家银行因收购汇丰银行而解雇部分员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位直接了解裁员情况的消息人士告诉路透社，加拿大最大的贷款机构加拿大皇家银行在去年斥资 135 亿加元收购汇丰银行国内业务后，由于业务部门发生变化而裁减了一些员工。
这两位要求匿名的消息人士称，部分裁员是在技术和运营团队，裁员于本周早些时候开始。【原文：Canada's largest lender Royal Bank of Canada laid off some employees as a result of changes at its business segments following the C$13.5 billion acquisition of HSBC's domestic business last year, two sources with direct knowledge of the layoffs told Reuters.
Some of the layoffs were at the technology and operations teams and began earlier this week, the sources said, requesting anonymity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canadas-rbc-lays-off-some-employees-related-hsbc-acquisition-sources-say-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UAO2UN6VY5PW5MT7TP5NG4JCVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据亮起潜在红灯，美联储有望在 6 月降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储将于 3 月 18-19 日召开政策会议，届时劳动力市场总体强劲，但可能会出现一些疲软的早期迹象，如果通胀率居高不下，而特朗普政府的关税又增加了物价压力，那么美国央行可能会陷入困境。【原文：The Federal Reserve will head into its March 18-19 policy meeting with the labor market strong overall but showing some potential early signs of weakening, a development that could put the U.S. central bank in a tough spot if inflation remains high and the Trump administration's tariffs add to price pressures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-expected-cut-rates-june-jobs-data-raises-potential-red-flags-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LZ73WUARZBOY3EKRTPRAG4KY2M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:29:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克计划 24 小时交易，全球对美股的兴趣与日俱增]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳斯达克公司（Nasdaq Inc）一位高级管理人员周五在社交媒体上发帖称，该公司计划在其旗舰美国交易所推出 24 小时交易，以利用全球对美国股票日益增长的需求。【原文：Nasdaq Inc plans to introduce 24-hour trading on its flagship U.S. exchange to capitalize on growing global demand for U.S. equities, a senior executive said in a social media post on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/nasdaq-plans-24-hour-trading-tap-into-growing-international-demand-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYLPOY4KY5IGPBHHSGEMWUP5L4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[房地产行业复苏乏力，Blackstone 最新房地产债务基金融资 80 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的另类资产管理公司 Blackstone 周五表示，其最新的房地产债务基金已募集到 80 亿美元，这表明房地产行业在经历了几年的动荡后正在复苏。【原文：Blackstone has raised $8 billion in its most recent real estate debt fund, the world's largest alternative asset manager said on Friday, a sign that the property sector is seeing a recovery after a couple of tumultuous years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstone-raises-8-bln-latest-real-estate-debt-fund-amid-nascent-sector-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X62GZ6CVCJM55OI3GW6PY4ZMLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:37:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政策不确定性考验美国劳动力市场韧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国的就业增长在二月份有所回升，但在混乱的贸易政策和联邦政府大幅削减开支有可能扰乱今年经济增长的情况下，曾经充满活力的劳动力市场正在出现裂痕。【原文：U.S. job growth picked up in February, but cracks are emerging in the once-resilient labor market amid a chaotic trade policy and deep federal government spending cuts that threaten to disrupt economic growth this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-picks-up-february-unemployment-rate-rises-41-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONE5ER5HBJOUFOJZ4NNAFU47B4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者评估鲍威尔言论，华尔街减少损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[在特朗普政府关税政策引发经济不确定性的背景下，投资者对美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的评论进行了评估，华尔街主要股指周五脱离盘中低点。【原文：Wall Street's main indexes traded off session lows on Friday as investors assessed comments from Fed Chair Jerome Powell amid economic uncertainty fanned by the Trump administration's tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-up-with-payrolls-data-powells-remarks-tap-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BQ3ZJLUKFOPBJXZOKG2YXJ4U4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币领导人将出席特朗普峰会，战略储备成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币行业精英将于周五在白宫与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普会面，讨论政府将如何实现特朗普将美国打造为 "世界加密货币之都 "的愿景。【原文：Cryptocurrency industry elite are set to meet with U.S. President Donald Trump at the White House on Friday to discuss how the government will enact Trump's vision of making the country the "crypto capital of the world."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-leaders-meet-trumps-summit-strategic-reserve-focus-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REKKTDLOFNLNNOOTNJKUSK2EDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者寻求特朗普白宫澄清关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA["锯齿状 "的关税公告令华尔街感到不安，因为投资者称，特朗普政府在削减对贸易伙伴的征税方面翻来覆去的举动造成了混乱，而不是带来了宽慰。【原文：Seesaw tariff announcements have unnerved Wall Street, as investors said flip-flopping moves by the Trump administration to roll back levies on trading partners were causing confusion rather than bringing relief.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-seek-clarity-tariffs-trump-white-house-2025-03-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGLB3NQAWRKVBICMIAIHFQCQPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 11:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[凯雷将加快首次公开募股（IPO）步伐，计划在 2025 年实现高达 50 亿美元的退出规模]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯雷投资集团（Carlyle Group）的私募股权主管告诉路透社，该集团预计今年将有更多的投资组合公司上市，而且不会回避大型杠杆收购，押注今年美国交易的反弹。【原文：Carlyle Group expects to take more of its portfolio companies public this year and will not shy away from large leveraged buyouts, betting on a rebound in U.S. dealmaking this year, its heads of private equity told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-ramp-up-pace-ipos-it-eyes-up-5-billion-exits-2025-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NM3BS7D57ZLZLHA36PVCJVNOY4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利以 "最佳选择 "支持人工智能和机器人技术，特斯拉上涨 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利（Morgan Stanley）重新将电动汽车制造商特斯拉列为美国汽车行业的首选，称即使在主力汽车业务陷入困境的情况下，该公司的人工智能和机器人技术仍能推动增长，特斯拉股价周一上涨了 2%。【原文：Tesla shares rose 2% on Monday after Morgan Stanley reinstated the electric-vehicle maker as its top U.S. auto pick, saying the company's artificial intelligence and robotics efforts could power growth even as the mainstay car business stumbles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-rises-2-morgan-stanley-backs-ai-robotics-efforts-with-top-pick-status-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXEM5SQKIBPHBBGTK7AC3PAAGU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:16:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔各部门成为焦点，台积电、博通周旋其中]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，英特尔的竞争对手台湾中芯国际集成电路制造股份有限公司和博通公司（Broadcom）正在探讨可能拆分这家美国芯片巨头的潜在交易。【原文：Intel rivals Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co and Broadcom are reportedly exploring potential deals that could split the storied American chip giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intels-divisions-spotlight-tsmc-broadcom-circle-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N552MIZ75BIKVLQYSL5SPH7Q7I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:12:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国航空公司希望禁止直升机飞越华盛顿特区机场附近的部分航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年 1 月，一架陆军直升机与美国航空公司的支线喷气式飞机在华盛顿里根国家机场附近相撞，造成 67 人死亡。【原文：A group representing U.S. airlines wants a series of safety changes after a fatal collision between an Army helicopter and American Airlines regional jet killed 67 people in January near Washington's Reagan National Airport.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airlines-want-helicopters-barred-some-routes-near-dc-airport-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SEOA5RZVQVNQZBX366NDMDZJZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:05:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Kraken 称美国证券交易委员会将驳回诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币交易所 Kraken 周一表示，美国证券交易委员会原则上同意驳回指控其非法经营未注册证券交易所的民事诉讼。【原文：Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken said on Monday that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission had agreed in principle to dismiss a civil lawsuit accusing it of illegally operating as an unregistered securities exchange.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/kraken-says-sec-dismiss-lawsuit-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J676O2YNTNMHRNZR7LIOZEFXAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:38:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份建筑支出意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[受多户住宅建设支出下降的影响，1 月份美国建筑支出意外下降。【原文：U.S. construction spending unexpectedly fell in January, pulled down by a decline in outlays on multi-family homebuilding.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-unexpectedly-declines-january-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">53EZGD4TQFLTFCA5MN4RBOQOVM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会的卡尔表示，欧盟内容法与美国言论自由传统不符]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦通信委员会（FCC）主席周一表示，欧盟的内容节制法不符合美国的言论自由传统，有可能过度限制言论自由。【原文：The European Union's content moderation law is incompatible with America's free speech tradition and there is a risk that it will excessively restrict freedom of expression, the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) chairman said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-content-law-incompatible-with-us-free-speech-tradition-says-fccs-carr-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CLTRNYUEQROVBMQET4HHWYJ3R4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:17:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电首席执行官将与特朗普会面，推销投资计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[台积电首席执行官魏幸全表示，该公司计划于周一与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普会面，讨论这家台湾半导体公司在美国的投资计划。【原文：TSMC CEO C. C. Wei plans to meet with President Donald Trump on Monday to discuss the Taiwanese semiconductor company's investment plans in the United States, the company said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tsmc-ceo-meet-with-trump-tout-investment-plans-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VXOFNVXJRPNVICSBF6DCT5Y64</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着周二最后期限的临近，特朗普将决定美国对墨西哥和加拿大的关税水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）预计将于周一决定他将在周二早些时候对加拿大和墨西哥征收何种程度的关税，而此时正值就边境安全和努力阻止芬太尼类阿片流入进行最后一分钟谈判之际。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump is expected to decide on Monday what levels of tariffs he will impose early on Tuesday on Canada and Mexico amid last-minute negotiations over border security and efforts to halt the inflow of fentanyl opioids.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-decide-us-tariff-levels-mexico-canada-tuesday-deadline-approaches-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OP77D6TBBKN5B2WEGK4ZASOUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2 月份美国制造业保持稳定，但关税风暴正在酝酿之中]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 月份，美国制造业保持稳定，但衡量工厂门口价格的一项指标跃升至近三年来的新高，而且材料交付所需的时间也在延长，这表明进口关税可能很快会阻碍生产。【原文：U.S. manufacturing was steady in February, but a measure of prices at the factory gate jumped to near a three-year high and it was taking longer for materials to be delivered, suggesting that tariffs on imports could soon hamper production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-stable-february-storm-brewing-tariffs-2025-03-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HSISBK65BNKHJBRRIJKQXRYUZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>