<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:35:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:35:54 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍威尔尚未准备好就特朗普政策对经济的影响发表看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周三表示，现在断言当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出的经济政策将对经济产生什么影响，以及这可能对央行的政策选择产生什么影响还为时过早。【原文：Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Wednesday it's too soon to say what President-elect Donald Trump's proposed economic policies will do to the economy and how that might bear on the central bank's policy choices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-powell-not-ready-say-what-trump-policies-will-do-economy-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERRP63UE5JPHDPFULQFGI6OLIE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克新任首席执行官希尔有机会阐述扭亏为盈计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃利奥特-希尔（Elliott Hill）在担任耐克公司首席执行官两个月后，本周四将迎来他的第一次机会，以说服投资者他能在裁员和销售下滑的一年后拯救这家陷入困境的运动服装公司。【原文：Two months into his tenure as Nike CEO, Elliott Hill gets his first shot on Thursday to convince investors he can rescue the flailing sportswear company after a year stained by layoffs and cratering sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/new-nike-ceo-hill-gets-his-chance-lay-out-turnaround-plan-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GWRYC5VWYFJ5JIKQCPCKXSC5AA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 美联储降息 25 个基点，缩减 2025 年宽松政策预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）周三下调了利率，并表示鉴于失业率相对稳定，且近期通胀几乎没有改善，将放慢借贷成本进一步下降的步伐。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve cut interest rates on Wednesday and signaled it will slow the pace at which borrowing costs fall any further given a relatively stable unemployment rate and little recent improvement in inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/view-fed-cuts-25-bp-scales-back-2025-easing-projections-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCZRAEMPA5ICVPH4RJVB34AJBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国利率期货价格预计美联储 1 月按兵不动，2025 年两次降息--LSEG 预计]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦基金利率是衡量银行间无担保隔夜贷款成本的指标，在美联储于周三结束为期两天的会议并将利率下调 25 个基点后，联邦基金利率期货已计价为隔夜基准利率将在美联储 1 月份的政策会议上保持不变。【原文：Futures on the federal funds rate, which measure the cost of unsecured overnight loans between banks, have priced in that the overnight benchmark rates will remain unchanged at the Federal Reserve's January policy meeting after the Fed lowered rates by 25 basis points at the end of its two-day meeting on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-rate-futures-price-fed-hold-january-two-cuts-2025-lseg-estimates-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5M4DVMLVVNJLMYPGIDKVI67MA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监察机构建议能源部停止向绿色项目提供贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部监察长敦促该机构的贷款办公室立即停止向绿色项目发放数十亿美元的贷款，称审查这些项目的承包商可能既为能源部服务，也为潜在借款人服务。【原文：The inspector general of the U.S. Department of Energy urged the agency's loan office to immediately halt issuing billions of dollars in loans to green projects, saying contractors who vet them may be serving both the agency and potential borrowers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-watchdog-recommends-energy-department-halt-loans-green-projects-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQNIEQ52RFJ5JDNBGLJ752BUFU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道信中称，尽管修改了提案，新日铁交易仍将受阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一封信显示，尽管新日铁不断与美国官员会面和通话，并提出了三项改良方案以缓解国家安全方面的担忧，但仍未能获得负责审查其 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的强大小组的批准。【原文：Despite a steady stream of meetings and calls with U.S. officials, and three revamped proposals to assuage national security concerns, Nippon Steel has failed to garner approval from a powerful panel reviewing its $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel , a letter seen by Reuters shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/despite-revamped-proposals-nippon-steel-deal-track-be-blocked-letter-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCPI6UMR4FMCJOZV4HARM4B3MQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构命令 USAA 联邦储蓄银行纠正不安全行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国货币监理署（OCC）周三表示，USAA 联邦储蓄银行已被责令纠正一系列长期存在的监管缺陷，这些缺陷相当于不安全和不健全的做法。【原文：USAA Federal Savings Bank has been ordered to correct a range of longstanding regulatory deficiencies amounting to unsafe and unsound practices, the U.S. Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulator-orders-usaa-federal-savings-bank-correct-unsafe-practices-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVPR5ARWG5IQNGXUPTYX6ER34A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储下调逆回购利率的幅度大于基金利率目标值]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周三调整了其利率控制工具箱中的一个关键部分，下调了逆回购工具的利率，降幅超过了联邦基金利率的下调幅度。【原文：The Federal Reserve adjusted a key part of its rate control toolkit on Wednesday, lowering the rate it offers on its reverse repo facility by more than it cut the federal funds rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-cuts-reverse-repo-rate-by-wider-margin-than-funds-rate-target-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3PKUJBBN5IRHLUEFSML5DTEZ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储决策者预计明年降息两个季度点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国央行行长们周三发布了新的预测，呼吁在通胀率上升的情况下明年降息两个季度点，这一预测与唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）1月份开始其在白宫的第二个四年任期时采取观望态度是一致的。【原文：U.S. central bankers on Wednesday issued fresh projections calling for two quarter-point interest-rate cuts next year amid rising inflation, a forecast consistent with a wait-and-see approach come January as Donald Trump starts his second four-year stint in the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-policymakers-project-two-quarter-point-rate-cuts-next-year-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7IDWPAYWRMDPN4YNS5SF35DBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特将更换质量领导者，以降低保修成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周三证实，该公司将任命一位新的质量主管，以扭转其行业最高的召回记录并降低保修成本。【原文：Ford Motor is appointing a new head of quality, the company confirmed on Wednesday, as the automaker works to reverse its industry-topping record of recalls and reduce warranty costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-change-its-quality-leader-it-chases-lower-warranty-costs-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFR7VWNSZJPFPAGTJZIUZDGVHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BNPL 贷款公司 Sezzle 因做空机构 Hindenburg Research 的攻击而暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在兴登堡研究公司（Hindenburg Research）披露空头头寸后，Sezzle 的股价在周三暴跌，原因是该公司的借贷行为存在风险，同时客户和商户数量也在减少。【原文：Buy now, pay later firm Sezzle's shares plunged on Wednesday after Hindenburg Research disclosed a short position, citing risky lending practices alongside a decline in customers and merchants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bnpl-lender-sezzle-plunges-short-seller-hindenburg-research-takes-aim-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U6VTH7LLLVJW3CK4PDSERAJLHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议院共和党高层敦促最高法院驳回 TikTok 的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院共和党头号人物米奇-麦康奈尔（Mitch McConnell）周三敦促美国最高法院驳回 TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动的诉讼请求，以阻止一项旨在强制在 1 月 19 日前出售短视频应用程序的法律，否则将以国家安全为由面临禁令。【原文：Top Senate Republican Mitch McConnell on Wednesday urged the U.S. Supreme Court to reject a bid by TikTok and its China-based parent company ByteDance to block a law intended to force the sale of the short-video app by Jan. 19 or face a ban on national security grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-senate-republican-urges-supreme-court-reject-tiktok-appeal-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">462DFVRYZFOTDEYS2WDFIA42GE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车需求降温，Stellantis 提前推出混合动力车 Ramcharger]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 公司周三表示，由于电动汽车需求放缓，该公司将提前推出其最畅销的公羊皮卡车的新型混合动力版，而不是电动版。【原文：Stellantis said on Wednesday it would move up the launch of a new hybrid version of its best-selling Ram pickup truck ahead of an electric version, citing slowing EV demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-moves-up-launch-hybrid-ramcharger-ev-demand-cools-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5R6RLB6GOZO45ND4CEG4PPVHRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将审理 TikTok 要求停止禁令的申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周三决定听取 TikTok 及其中国母公司字节跳动的诉讼请求，以阻止一项旨在强制在 1 月 19 日前出售短视频应用程序的法律，否则将以国家安全为由面临禁令。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court decided on Wednesday to hear a bid by TikTok and its China-based parent company ByteDance to block a law intended to force the sale of the short-video app by Jan. 19 or face a ban on national security grounds.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-consider-tiktok-bid-halt-ban-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FYYLJIXCBRKITNVVZWNFTDVJRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德事隆权衡越野车业务选择，暂停生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[赛斯纳喷气机制造商德事隆（Textron）周三表示，由于需求持续疲软，该公司正在探索动力产品线的战略替代方案。【原文：Textron is exploring strategic alternatives for its Powersports product line due to persistent weak demand, the Cessna jet maker said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/textron-weighs-options-off-road-vehicles-business-pauses-production-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADJPHU7IKJNSDEHCZWBK7655FY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brooge Energy 投资者投诉安永会计师事务所欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[布罗吉能源公司的一些股东在美国对安永会计师事务所提起欺诈诉讼，指控该审计师未能发现这家石油储存公司两年年度报告中的虚假收入。【原文：Some shareholders in Brooge Energy have filed a fraud complaint in the United States against Ernst &amp; Young, alleging the auditor failed to identify fabricated revenues in two years of the oil storage firm's annual reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/brooge-energy-investors-file-fraud-complaint-against-ernst-young-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BOECGUMOVNWLA2COQ2O27SEKE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:09:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局批准加州计划，从 2035 年起禁止使用纯汽油汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环境保护局（U.S. Environmental Protection Agency）周三表示，它已经批准了加利福尼亚州具有里程碑意义的计划，即到 2035 年停止销售纯汽油车。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency said on Wednesday it has approved California's landmark plan to end the sale of gasoline-only vehicles by 2035.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-epa-approves-california-plan-ban-gas-only-cars-starting-2035-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72FQIYIWGFNE5M7QHJ2DTTEX2M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:04:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度经常账户赤字创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于进口激增和基本收入减少，美国第三季度经常账户赤字扩大至历史最高水平。【原文：The U.S. current account deficit widened to a record high in the third quarter amid a surge in imports and lower primary income receipts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-current-account-deficit-hits-record-high-third-quarter-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUIXYKPYEJK4XJFFIKB7RGVOAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德控股公司以 165 亿美元完成对康泰伦特的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德控股公司（Novo Holdings）已完成对康泰伦特公司（Catalent）的 165 亿美元收购，这家合同药品生产商周三表示，几天前两家公司披露，完成交易的所有监管条件均已满足。【原文：Novo Holdings has completed its $16.5 billion acquisition of Catalent , the contract drug manufacturer said on Wednesday, days after the companies disclosed that all regulatory conditions to close the deal were fulfilled.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/novo-holdings-completes-165-bln-takeover-catalent-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMDPPSWTGRNS7MESLEAFJHZNRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 11 月独户住宅开工率反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着飓风的影响逐渐减弱，美国单户住宅建设在 11 月份出现反弹，但对进口商品征收关税的威胁以及大规模驱逐可能造成的劳动力短缺可能会阻碍明年的新建筑工程。【原文：U.S. single-family homebuilding rebounded in November as the drag from hurricanes faded, but the threat of tariffs on imported goods and potential labor shortages from mass deportations could hamper new construction next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-single-family-housing-starts-rebound-november-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LN6TCFADHBMG5IAXAFDKRHES2I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 13:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔称日产本田合并不会带来快速解决方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[S&amp;P分析师周三表示，本田和日产的合并不会带来快速收益，因为这两家汽车制造商首先需要调整战略，而重叠的区域市场将限制销售收益。【原文：A merger between Honda and Nissan would not come with quick gains, as the automakers would first need to align their strategies while overlapping regional markets would limit the sales benefits, S&amp;P analysts said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/nissan-honda-merger-would-not-bring-quick-fixes-sp-says-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7YG67OQEFVOTXKQJA5BMQSBLIA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 13:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚果律师称苹果供应链声明必须经过验证]]></title><description><![CDATA[刚果民主共和国的国际律师对苹果公司因冲突恶化而决定停止从该国采购矿产表示欢迎，但表示他们将继续在欧洲起诉该公司。【原文：International lawyers for the Democratic Republic of Congo welcomed Apple's decision to stop sourcing minerals from there due to worsening conflict, but said they would press ahead with their cases against the company in Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/congo-lawyers-say-apples-supply-chain-statement-must-be-verified-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IAOQLLUNURO6VFLIJRHSOB7PHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 13:17:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sam Altman 支持的 Oklo 公司与数据中心运营商签署电力协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）支持的核电初创公司 Oklo Inc 周三表示，该公司已经签署了一份不具约束力的协议，将为拉斯维加斯的数据中心运营商 Switch 提供电力。【原文：Sam Altman-backed nuclear startup Oklo Inc said on Wednesday it has signed a non-binding agreement to provide power to Las Vegas-based data center operator Switch.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/sam-altman-backed-oklo-signs-power-agreement-with-data-center-operator-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T3ALKCQI5BLL7GFSFUU3C7VX5M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 13:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Swiss report on Credit Suisse collapse to be published Friday]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Swiss parliamentary report into how authorities managed the 2023 collapse of Credit Suisse will be published on Friday, the Swiss parliament said on Wednesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-report-credit-suisse-collapse-be-published-friday-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PH43C37UMBKD7NIIIECZGEMNX4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instagram to make up more than half of Meta's US ad revenue in 2025, report shows]]></title><description><![CDATA[Instagram is set to account for more than half of Meta Platforms' advertising revenue in the United States next year, as the social media platform improves monetization of its products, according to research firm Emarketer.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/instagram-make-up-more-than-half-metas-us-ad-revenue-2025-report-shows-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3GB7V2NSNKQXPMECHRF76ZAC4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[General Mills beats second-quarter sales estimates, lowers profit forecast]]></title><description><![CDATA[General Mills beat quarterly sales and profit estimates on Wednesday, boosted by its efforts to reduce prices on some products and improve demand.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/general-mills-beats-second-quarter-sales-estimates-lowers-profit-forecast-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUSGJ3KH2NMFVKSIFZH2G7OJRE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：市场焦虑不安，等待美联储]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-pix-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VCW6J6BBKVLF5OERES47PW4KAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场等待美联储决议，期货价格稳步走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股指期货走高，交易商在等待美联储今年最后一次利率决定，以及有关决策者是否会在 2025 年采取更加谨慎立场的信号。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were higher on Wednesday, as traders waited for the Federal Reserve's final rate decision of the year and signals on whether policymakers will take a more cautious stance in 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-inch-higher-markets-await-fed-decision-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WXWGONPFJOOJACSDY6G5SHCI4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔在担任美联储主席的最后一整年里有很多工作要做]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储将于本周三结束2024年的最后一次会议，明年很可能是美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔执掌美国央行的最后一个完整任期，他的四年任期将于2026年5月届满。【原文：The Federal Reserve will conclude its final meeting of 2024 on Wednesday, and next year will likely be Fed Chair Jerome Powell's last full one at the helm of the U.S. central bank, with his four-year term due to expire in May of 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/powell-has-long-to-do-list-his-last-full-year-fed-chief-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26SXR666JNLHJIRLXHSVIUP554</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:11:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储似将调整逆回购利率以加速现金退出]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美联储进入一个更加不确定的时期，在许多人看来，这是美联储缩减资产负债表努力的最后几个月，美联储似乎有可能在周三采取一项措施，将现金从其资产负债表中移除。【原文：The Federal Reserve appears likely to take a step on Wednesday to nudge cash off its balance sheet as it enters a more uncertain period in what many see as the final months in its effort to draw down its balance sheet.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-looks-set-tweak-reverse-repo-rate-speed-exit-cash-2024-12-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W26Q4LKINRL65LQT5CL34TRQFA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>