<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:39:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:39:26 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[白宫公布人工智能政策计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三发布了一项人工智能（AI）政策计划，阐明了美国在该领域取得 "全球主导地位 "的优先事项。【原文：The White House released an artificial intelligence (AI) policy plan on Wednesday spelling out priorities for the U.S. to achieve "global dominance" in the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/white-house-unveils-artificial-intelligence-policy-plan-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PR53VPTRJNJFFDTNO4644AZQUE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:57:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司称美国火星油产出中的锌含量未超出限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪佛龙公司（Chevron）周二表示，最近的测试表明，美国旗舰海上原油火星生产流程中的锌含量目前处于预期水平之内。【原文：Chevron on Tuesday said recent testing indicates that zinc levels in flagship U.S. offshore crude Mars' production stream were now within expected levels.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chevron-says-zinc-levels-us-mars-oil-output-within-limits-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT5UAKCSTRP2JH6CYJOWMQ6PEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电子设备需求强劲，安费诺预计季度业绩乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[在电缆、传感器和天线等产品需求强劲之后，安费诺公司周三预计第三季度业绩将高于华尔街预期，股价因此上涨 4%。【原文：Amphenol forecast third-quarter results above Wall Street estimates on Wednesday, after seeing strong demand for its products such as cables, sensors and antennas, sending its shares up 4%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/amphenol-forecasts-upbeat-quarterly-results-strong-demand-electronic-equipment-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVQG7V6HW5M6LAAC2NIZMZTDYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:41:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国大陆资源公司撤销对竞争对手赫斯的欺诈诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国页岩油气生产商大陆资源公司（Continental Resources）撤销了今年 5 月对竞争对手赫斯公司（Hess Corp）提起的诉讼。【原文：U.S. shale producer Continental Resources has dropped a lawsuit it filed against rival Hess Corp in May, which alleged it was defrauded out of up to $69 million through a series of deals the well operator conducted with its subsidiaries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-oil-producer-continental-resources-drops-fraud-lawsuit-against-rival-hess-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTM6YY5Q5VLEXMSAYRH76ZQSDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国发布自动驾驶技术伦理指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国科技部周三发布了自动驾驶技术道德准则，要求开发人员在发布研究成果时优先考虑用户安全，不得散布虚假信息。【原文：China's science and technology ministry on Wednesday issued ethical guidelines for autonomous driving technology, requiring developers to prioritise user safety and refrain from spreading false information when publishing research results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/china-issues-ethical-guidelines-autonomous-driving-technology-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54YCTRRGCNIYROL4EXANRCYYZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白银连涨步伐加快，市场创 2011 年以来新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，白银价格飙升至近14年来的最高点，这主要得益于对美国关税政策的担忧、现货市场供应紧张的迹象以及投资者对黄金替代品日益浓厚的兴趣。【原文：Silver prices surged to their highest in almost 14 years on Wednesday, aided by worries about U.S. tariff policy, signs of tightness in the spot market and growing investor interest in alternatives to gold.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/silvers-hot-streak-gathers-pace-market-highest-since-2011-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGM25CXQOFNVDPP37UO47AIAZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 6 月成屋销售降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 6 月份成屋销售降幅超过预期，表明随着抵押贷款利率上升和经济不确定性使潜在购房者保持观望，房地产市场的低迷可能正在加深。【原文：U.S. existing home sales fell more than expected in June, suggesting the housing market slump could be deepening as higher mortgage rates and economic uncertainty keep potential buyers on the sidelines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-existing-home-sales-fall-more-than-expected-june-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LM5RKJSWPNOQVP7GHCKI5RMEAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[从亚马逊到沃尔玛，全球电子商务公司在印度面临监管审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在印度蓬勃发展的电子商务领域开展业务的外国公司面临着许多监管和法律挑战，这些挑战来自因涉嫌不遵守印度法律而对其进行调查的当局，这些举措主要是为了保护当地企业。【原文：Foreign companies operating in India's booming e-commerce sector face many regulatory and legal challenges from authorities investigating them for alleged non-compliance with Indian laws, moves largely aimed at protecting local businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/amazon-walmart-global-e-commerce-firms-face-regulatory-scrutiny-india-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQO5HPRHBFL5TFFLHF3IZHYEJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[COVID 事件五年后，医药股在美国政策困境中徘徊不前]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球医疗保健股几十年来从未如此便宜过，流入该行业的资金正在回升，但股价仍然低迷，凸显了唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后药品定价政策的不确定性。【原文：Global healthcare stocks have not been this cheap in decades and fund inflows into the sector are picking up, yet the shares remain in the doldrums, highlighting uncertainty over drug pricing policies since Donald Trump returned to the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/five-years-after-covid-pharma-shares-languish-us-policy-limbo-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBO36OLVHBK6JLVWTUKAWKNOM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上游石油和天然气交易下滑，波动性令投资者动摇]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析公司 Enverus 周三表示，第二季度能源和股票市场的波动令投资者感到恐慌，从而减缓了美国上游石油和天然气行业的并购步伐。【原文：Volatility across energy and equity markets spooked investors in the second quarter, slowing the pace of mergers and acquisitions in the U.S. upstream oil and gas sector, analytics firm Enverus said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/dealmaking-us-upstream-oil-gas-tumbles-volatility-rattles-investors-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DMWMZ2KC6FOPXJANRSZO3HNH5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普再次呼吁美联储董事会采取行动，称鲍威尔 "不明白"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔不断呼吁降低利率之际，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三重申了他对美联储主席鲍威尔的批评，并呼吁央行董事会采取行动。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday reiterated his criticism of Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell amid his ongoing call for lower rates, and called on the central bank's board to act.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-again-calls-fed-board-act-says-powell-doesnt-get-it-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ALNIELOBRZJBDDXAZ7CYHUUZGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛与纽约银行联手推出与货币市场基金挂钩的代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）和纽约银行（BNY）联手推出了反映货币市场基金份额的数字代币，深化了华尔街将区块链技术引入传统金融领域的努力。【原文：Goldman Sachs and BNY have joined hands to launch digital tokens that mirror shares of money market funds, deepening Wall Street's push to bring blockchain technology into traditional finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/goldman-bny-team-up-launch-tokens-tied-money-market-funds-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUK562MEQRMYTD2IKB4ASKHXZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济动荡不安，巴西 WEG 公布第二季度盈利不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西汽车制造商 WEG 周三公布，其第二季度净利润同比增长 10.4%，但未能达到市场预期，原因是全球经济波动加剧。【原文：Brazilian motor maker WEG on Wednesday reported a 10.4% year-on-year rise in its second-quarter net profit, but missed market forecasts amid what it called elevated volatility in global economics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-weg-reports-q2-earnings-miss-amid-global-volatility-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIB5MLIK7ZOPRPS2DQRMPF2UVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究人员称微软服务器黑客已入侵 400 家机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[据荷兰 Eye Security 公司的研究人员称，在发现以微软服务器软件为中心的大规模网络间谍活动后，约有 400 家组织显示出被入侵的迹象。【原文：About 400 organizations show signs of having been compromised following the discovery of a sweeping cyberespionage operation centered on Microsoft's server software, according to researchers at Netherlands-based Eye Security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/microsoft-server-hack-has-compromised-400-organizations-researchers-say-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDGYUVA6TBN63IC56HRRQO52GM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三叶草增长放缓，Fiserv 下调年度收入预期，股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fiserv 周三下调了年度收入增长预期，原因是该支付公司正努力应对其销售点和业务管理平台 Clover 业务增长放缓的问题。【原文：Fiserv tempered down annual revenue growth forecast on Wednesday, as the payments firm grapples with slowdown in the Clover business, its point-of-sale and business management platform.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fiserv-trims-annual-revenue-forecast-clover-growth-slows-down-shares-slide-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GTDPQ6ZFZIJVG5RTQHLMX5Q4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于铜价和金价上涨，自由港麦克莫兰公司（Freeport-McMoRan）季度利润超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[矿业公司 Freeport-McMoRan 周三公布的第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，原因是铜和黄金价格上涨帮助抵消了产量下降的影响。【原文：Miner Freeport-McMoRan beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Wednesday, as higher copper and gold prices helped offset lower production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/freeport-mcmoran-beats-quarterly-profit-higher-copper-gold-prices-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DC7YQGUTPVOSHMHRYYMTP4EUJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场欢庆日本贸易协定，企业业绩却黯淡无光]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战造成了损害，即使日本达成的协议提振了股市，欧洲也有望达成类似的协议。【原文：Businesses making everything from chips to steel reported downbeat results on Wednesday, with U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war inflicting damage even as Japan's deal lifted stocks and hopes that Europe can clinch a similar agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/businesses-deliver-gloomy-results-even-markets-celebrate-japan-trade-deal-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C3R3I2OMPNPKPBHKUATSMSGXHQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:11:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国防需求强劲，Teledyne Technologies 上调 2025 年利润展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[受军用无人机和目标探测传感器需求强劲的推动，Teledyne Technologies 周三公布的第二季度业绩超出华尔街预期，并上调了全年利润预期的下限。【原文：Teledyne Technologies raised the lower end of its annual profit forecast after topping Wall Street expectations for second-quarter results on Wednesday, driven by strong demand for its military drones and target detection sensors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/teledyne-technologies-raises-2025-profit-outlook-strong-defense-demand-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBBOCTTBKZLRTAX4KQGHEQDO4Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:07:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，中国汽车制造商在萎缩的欧洲市场站稳脚跟]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jato Dynamics 公司周三提供的数据显示，6 月份欧洲汽车注册量有所下降，同比减少 4.4%，为 125 万辆。【原文：Car registrations across Europe declined in June, with a 4.4% year-on-year drop to 1.25 million vehicles, data from Jato Dynamics showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinese-automakers-gain-ground-contracting-european-market-data-shows-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QX4MR4NFJ5K3BALNBK57PVZCPU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠灵顿主导的融资使 Vanta 的估值在一年内提高了 69]]></title><description><![CDATA[在线安全与合规管理平台 Vanta 在其最新一轮融资中的估值为 41.5 亿美元，高于一年前的 24.5 亿美元，这是因为投资者对风险缓解软件的吸引力随着网络攻击而上升。【原文：Online security and compliance management platform Vanta was valued at $4.15 billion in its latest fundraising round, up from $2.45 billion just a year ago, as investor appeal of risk-mitigating software rises in tandem with cyber attacks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wellington-led-funding-boosts-vantas-valuation-by-69-year-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRX5AYDVORIJ3L4R2CBAMOT77Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司因心脏设备需求稳定而上调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司（Boston Scientific）周三上调了年度利润预期，此前对其心脏设备的强劲需求帮助这家美国医疗设备制造商第二季度利润超出预期。【原文：Boston Scientific raised its annual profit forecast on Wednesday, after strong demand for its heart devices helped the U.S. medical device maker beat second-quarter profit estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/boston-scientific-lifts-annual-profit-view-steady-heart-devices-demand-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNJCWOVWK5N35C7ECMHQT5ER4I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪公布第二季度利润增长，分析部门表现强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[评级机构穆迪（Moody's）周三报告称，受数据和分析部门的强劲收益以及政府借贷增加的推动，第二季度利润有所增长。【原文：Ratings agency Moody's reported a rise in second quarter profit on Wednesday, driven by robust gains in its data and analytics unit and an increase in government borrowing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/moodys-reports-higher-second-quarter-profit-analytics-unit-strength-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H4PWREPSDJKA7CJEPAOH6LN36M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[北方信托首席执行官否认本季度业绩强劲后有出售计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[北方信托公司首席执行官周三表示，在这家财富与资产管理公司公布第二季度利润超过预期之后，他没有也不打算讨论出售问题。【原文：Northern Trust's CEO said on Wednesday that he has not entertained sale discussions and does not intend to, after the wealth and asset manager reported a second-quarter profit that beat estimates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/en/northern-trust-ceo-denies-talks-sale-after-strong-quarter-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIQPK7QXWJLONG2JCSJZS5MUUI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NextEra Energy 因可再生能源增长和人工智能驱动的电力需求，季度利润超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[NextEra Energy 周三公布的第二季度调整后利润超出华尔街预期，主要得益于其可再生能源部门的强劲表现，以及人工智能数据中心和超大规模服务器不断增长的电力需求。【原文：NextEra Energy beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter adjusted profit on Wednesday, driven by strong performance in its renewables unit amid rising power demand from AI data centers and hyperscalers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/nextera-energy-beats-quarterly-profit-estimates-renewables-growth-ai-driven-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKPUUZA3P5NF7KORCVSNITS7RM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长贝森特：特朗普政府不急于撤换鲍威尔]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三表示，特朗普政府并不急于提名新的美联储主席来接替杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Wednesday that the Trump administration was not in a rush to nominate a new Federal Reserve Chair to replace Jerome Powell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-not-rush-replace-powell-treasury-chief-bessent-says-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUNATW6BPNN3TDFXPBCQ3QIWNU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特：特朗普在关税税率问题上具有影响力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三在接受彭博电视采访时表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普就关税税率发表的信函为贸易问题创造了很多筹码。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump has created a lot of leverage on trade with his letters on tariff rates, U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent told Bloomberg Television in an interview on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-treasurys-bessent-says-trump-has-leverage-with-tariff-rates-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIHZYRRH5JYTMU5HSZ56MOB6U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:39:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第二季度利润超预期，通用电气弗诺瓦公司上调年度预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[电力设备制造商通用电气弗诺瓦公司周三上调了本年度收入和自由现金流预期，此前该公司第二季度利润超出华尔街预期，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨超过 4%。【原文：Power equipment maker GE Vernova raised its current-year revenue and free cash flow forecast after beating Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit on Wednesday, sending its shares rising more than 4% in premarket trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ge-vernova-raises-annual-forecasts-after-second-quarter-profit-beat-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDD2BQDBIFKOBMI3BQZCE7RIN4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将提交针对美国商品的反制措施，以避免即将到来的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会计划向欧盟成员国提交对930亿欧元（约合1090亿美元）美国商品征收反关税的申请，同时其贸易负责人将与美国商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）举行会谈。【原文：The European Commission plans to submit counter-tariffs on 93 billion euros ($109 billion) of U.S. goods for approval to EU members, while its trade chief will hold talks with U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-submit-countermeasures-us-goods-avert-looming-tariffs-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCI4SKLV3ZNVPD6EAXT37R3KCQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟技术主管表示：没有计划让大科技公司支付数字法律合规成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟科技主管周三表示，欧盟委员会不会要求 Alphabet、亚马逊、苹果、ByteDance、Meta Platforms 和微软支付监督它们遵守新数字法律的费用。【原文：The European Commission will not ask Alphabet , Amazon , Apple , ByteDance, Meta Platforms and Microsoft to pay the cost of monitoring their compliance with a new digital law, the EU tech chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/no-plans-get-big-tech-pay-digital-law-compliance-costs-eu-tech-chief-says-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BXHMKHESYJMDXDZIB4WEHK3IUY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司因喷气机交付量增加而实现季度利润增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司（General Dynamics）周三公布的第二季度利润增长了近 15%，主要得益于公务机交付量的增长，该公司股价在收盘前上涨了 1.7%。【原文：General Dynamics on Wednesday second-quarter profit rose nearly 15% on the back of stronger business jet deliveries, sending the company's shares up 1.7% before the bell.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-quarterly-profit-rises-higher-jet-deliveries-2025-07-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2LLVSBJ7RNRVO2YLE47RAMLMY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>