<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:04:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:04:46 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据英国《金融时报》报道，马斯克的 SpaceX 公司准备在 12 月以每股 135 美元的价格发起要约收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国《金融时报》周五援引知情人士的话报道称，埃隆-马斯克的 SpaceX 公司准备在 12 月发起要约收购，以每股 135 美元的价格出售现有股份。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX is preparing to launch a tender offer in December to sell existing shares at a price of $135 per share, the Financial Times reported on Friday, citing people with knowledge of the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/space/musks-spacex-preparing-launch-tender-offer-dec-135share-ft-reports-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDQJXRKX7BL35DTGTVT2C2W6YY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份零售销售略高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 10 月份的零售额增幅略高于预期，但消费者支出的基本势头在第四季度初似乎有所放缓。【原文：U.S. retail sales increased slightly more than expected in October, but underlying momentum in consumer spending appeared to slow at the start of the fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-retail-sales-slightly-above-expectations-october-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YQIRTC5YJ5KAXMA3JOTZVWJAZE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:40:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称通用汽车裁员近千人，其中大部分在美国]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位消息人士周五告诉路透社，通用汽车公司正在全球范围内裁员近1000人，其中大部分在美国，因为该公司希望精简业务。【原文：General Motors is laying off nearly 1,000 workers worldwide, most in the U.S., as it looks to streamline operations, a source told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-laying-off-nearly-1000-workers-most-us-source-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NGC2LZ3PBNEZJZ3IJEQHGUDHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 13:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业盈利乐观，美国股票基金资金流入强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月13日的一周内，投资者对美国股票基金的需求大幅增加，原因是人们对唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）重新上台将改善美国企业盈利前景持乐观态度。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed a significant boost in investor demand in the week through Nov. 13, fueled by optimism that Donald Trump’s return to office would enhance the outlook for U.S. corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-robust-inflows-corporate-earnings-optimism-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S6EI6BCLVBN3ROQ5GQWFFFLAH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪斯尼接近临界点，流媒体利润开始抵消有线电视的下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[2022 年，鲍勃-艾格重返华特迪士尼担任首席执行官，并大胆承诺要让流媒体盈利。【原文：Bob Iger returned to Walt Disney as CEO in 2022 with a bold promise of making streaming profitable.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-nears-tipping-point-streaming-profits-start-offset-cable-decline-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5CUNW7YSCVMJ5NNZOISMQ47GJU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[格兰霍姆称，取消美国电动汽车税收抵免将让位于中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源部长詹妮弗-格兰霍尔姆（Jennifer Granholm）周五在巴库举行的COP29气候大会上对记者说，取消美国电动汽车税收抵免将适得其反，并将把市场拱手让给中国的汽车制造商。【原文：Cancelling the U.S. electric vehicle tax credit would be counterproductive and cede ground to car-makers in China, U.S. Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm told reporters on Friday at the COP29 climate conference in Baku.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rescinding-us-ev-tax-credit-would-cede-ground-china-granholm-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6K5OZXSVBNHHLAOYJAZR5ZPKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大手笔预算和特朗普获胜后，英国通胀忧虑升温]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在英国似乎要摆脱通胀问题时，新政府的大肆挥霍以及美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税计划引发的全球贸易战风险却威胁着通胀问题的延续。【原文：Just when Britain seemed to be moving beyond its inflation problem, the new government's spending splurge and the risk of a global trade war triggered by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's tariff plan are threatening to extend it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-inflation-worries-tick-up-after-big-spending-budget-trump-win-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4UJMDRCRRLABBIAHREYOPUTR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道联合利华将欧洲裁员预期减半，部分员工转至冰淇淋部门--工厂委员会]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华欧洲工作委员会负责人告诉路透社，联合利华在欧洲的裁员数量将比最初预计的少约 1500 人，并将为其即将分拆的冰淇淋业务招聘约 1000 人，主要是那些受其成本削减行动影响的员工。【原文：Unilever is cutting about 1,500 fewer jobs in Europe than initially anticipated and hiring about 1,000 people, primarily those affected by its cost-cutting drive, for its soon-to-be spun off ice cream business, the head of the company's European Works Council told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-nearly-halves-expected-european-job-cuts-switching-some-staff-ice-cream-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AD5KEXTSXFNTXCR2BBIHPMWZB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国阿里巴巴季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿里巴巴集团周五公布的季度销售额不及分析师预期，原因是经济不确定性持续存在，削弱了中国消费者的支出，并拖累了这家电子商务巨头的国内业务。【原文：Alibaba Group Holding missed analysts' estimates for quarterly sales on Friday, as lingering economic uncertainty sapped consumer spending in China and weighed on the e-commerce giant's domestic business.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/chinas-alibaba-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ASQLJKRGJLYNGS2DIRYZQTM4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标美联储为大选后的宽松政策披上面纱]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBI4TJCWMFIF5EZVETVYCPEZI4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小肯尼迪誓言肃清食品及药物管理局，与大药厂碰撞出火花]]></title><description><![CDATA[小罗伯特-肯尼迪希望做出的任何改变都将面临制药业的反对，而制药业为美国食品和药物管理局支付了大量费用。【原文：Any changes Robert F. Kennedy Jr. wants to make will come up against a pharmaceutical industry that pays much of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's bills.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/rfk-jr-vow-purge-fda-sets-up-collision-with-big-pharma-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PVFAWBRTMBNRBMJO6XGH7VMXLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍威尔发出不急于降息的信号，期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）表示没有必要急于降息之后，美国股指期货周五下跌，从而推高了债券收益率，并对利率敏感的股市构成压力。【原文：U.S. stock index futures fell on Friday after Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said there was no need to reduce interest rates in a hurry, pushing up bond yields and pressuring rate-sensitive equities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-drop-powell-signals-no-hurry-rate-cuts-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">USNBP753CJKXJKGOM7MRZELYYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：波士顿联储主席称 12 月降息并非 "板上钉钉]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）在接受《华尔街日报》采访时表示，12 月再次降息已经摆在桌面上，但并非 "板上钉钉"。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said in an interview with the Wall Street Journal that another rate cut in December is on the table, but it is not a "done deal".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/boston-fed-president-says-december-rate-cut-not-done-deal-wsj-reports-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F4ECU7JAYBOYVJV5RC5Q5OSSTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员会称美国保护主义对美欧极为有害]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲经济专员保罗-真蒂洛尼（Paolo Gentiloni）周五表示，美国贸易政策保护主义的加剧将对美国和欧洲都极为不利。【原文：Increased protectionism of U.S. trade policy would be extremely harmful to both the United States and to Europe, European Economic Commissioner Paolo Gentiloni said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/us-protectionism-would-be-extremely-harmful-us-europe-says-eu-commission-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2S6YGP6GJKTLKCSKK47YQ354U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[疫苗生产商巴伐利亚北欧公司表示，特朗普执政后美国有望增加生物防御开支]]></title><description><![CDATA[疫苗生产商巴伐利亚北欧公司首席执行官周五表示，尽管对疫苗持怀疑态度的小罗伯特-肯尼迪（Robert F. Kennedy Jr.【原文：Vaccine maker Bavarian Nordic expects the incoming Trump administration to boost biodefence funding despite the nomination of Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a vaccine sceptic, as health secretary, the company's CEO said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bavarian-nordic-ceo-says-kennedy-nomination-could-fuel-vaccine-scepticism-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIHHEUZKF5LQNLCTN2OLOSMAWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 提高收购富士软的要约收购价]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司 KKR 周五表示，已将收购日本软件开发商 Fuji Soft 的要约收购价从之前的每股 8,800 日元提高到 9,451 日元（60.86 美元）。【原文：Private equity firm KKR has raised its tender offer price for the acquisition of Japanese software developer Fuji Soft to 9,451 yen ($60.86) a share from 8,800 yen previously, the Japanese company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kkr-raises-tender-offer-price-fuji-soft-acquisition-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HTSTUGN33RPMNCRGDES3EJN5O4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:40:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金创十多年来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至11月13日的一周内，全球股票基金创下了十多年来最大的单周净购买量，原因是投资者乐观地认为，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）决定性的连任将促进企业盈利并推动美国经济增长。【原文：Global equity funds saw the largest weekly net purchases in over a decade in the week to Nov. 13, driven by investor optimism that a decisive second-term mandate for Donald Trump would bolster corporate earnings and fuel U.S. economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6JH6CSPKARO7VCPNNNV4N3WPQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在特朗普回国前敲定授予台积电 66 亿美元芯片合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，已敲定向台湾积体电路制造股份有限公司（Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co.【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department said Friday it has finalized a $6.6 billion government subsidy for Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co's U.S. unit for semiconductor production in Phoenix, Arizona.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-finalizes-66-billion-chips-award-tsmc-ahead-trump-return-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEOT3RK6ANOQPKQLGHOYKZIFGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 10:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团警告特朗普的政策可能会减缓新兴市场的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团分析师预计，在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最近赢得美国总统大选后，新兴市场股票的表现将逊于全球同行，尽管中国最近采取了一些政策措施，全球经济也在增长。【原文：Citigroup analysts anticipate that emerging market stocks will underperform compared to global peers following Donald Trump's recent victory in the U.S. presidential election, despite China's recent policy initiatives and global economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/citigroup-warns-trumps-policies-may-slow-growth-emerging-markets-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QIX6RPY6OJJTRND7TEUQ75WF3Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:59:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者围观特朗普贸易的全球市场受害者]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球大型投资者正在退出那些押注美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的税收和关税政策将提振华尔街并给海外市场造成破坏的热门交易，转而投向 11 月 5 日大选中一些最大的市场受害者。【原文：Big global investors are exiting popular trades that bet on U.S. President-elect Donald Trump’s tax and tariff policies boosting Wall Street and wreaking damage abroad and swooping in on some of the Nov. 5 election's biggest market victims.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-circle-trump-trades-global-market-victims-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UXLG5IFQJP7RMBF2LGQIP5UAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星电子计划回购 72 亿美元以提升股东价值]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子在周五收盘后提交的一份监管文件中表示，该公司计划在一年内回购价值 10 万亿韩元（71.7 亿美元）的股票，以提升股东价值。【原文：Samsung Electronics plans to buy back shares worth 10 trillion won ($7.17 billion) over a one-year period to boost shareholder value, it said in a regulatory filing submitted after the market closed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-electronics-plans-72-bln-buyback-boost-shareholder-value-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOA2ZTIVVFNCDLVUWFGXC75XGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：信中称，脆弱国家将在 COP29 上推动 200 亿美元的气候融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一封信显示，一些受冲突影响的国家正在COP29会议上推动将财政援助增加一倍，达到每年200多亿美元，以应对这些国家的人民所面临的自然灾害和安全危机。【原文：A group of conflict-affected countries is pushing at COP29 to double financial aid to more than $20 billion a year to combat the natural disaster and security crises facing their populations, a letter seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/fragile-countries-make-20-bln-climate-finance-push-cop29-letter-says-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ZOICYZUGZI5TNGE2SQBIO46RE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员在美国期权市场追逐大选后的股票涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股市的期权交易者们正纷纷加大风险押注，支持美国股市在大选忧虑消退、共和党有望在明年锁定华盛顿权力的背景下反弹。【原文：Options players are piling in to riskier bets across the U.S. stock market, supporting a rally that has come on the back of fading election worries and expectations of a Republican lock on power in Washington next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/traders-chase-post-election-stock-gains-us-options-market-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMCYCX2ZPFOLXERUS5XXGNHPSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 06:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[健康倡导者要求 Cepheid 提供更便宜的 mpox 检测试剂盒]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球健康倡导者已致函一种重要的水痘诊断检测试剂的制造商，呼吁将其价格从每次约 20 美元降至 5 美元，以帮助受病毒严重影响的贫困国家解决检测率低的问题。【原文：Global health advocates have written to the makers of a key mpox diagnostic test to call for its price to be cut from around $20 per test to $5, to help tackle low testing rates in poorer countries badly hit by the virus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/health-advocates-press-cepheid-cheaper-mpox-tests-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QHYNIIKBBL6XCB6CRR6BUURWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 06:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标中国消费者支出增加，但不是在房地产上]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CA2E37TYYVNCNEGX44KFV7HMUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[礼来起诉美国机构阻止药品回扣计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[礼来公司周四表示，它起诉了联邦卫生资源与服务管理局（HRSA），指控其阻止该公司改变向医院提供药品折扣方式的计划。【原文：Eli Lilly said on Thursday it sued the federal Health Resources and Services Administration (HRSA) over allegedly blocking the company's plan to change the way it offers drug discounts to hospitals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/lilly-sues-us-agency-over-blocking-drug-rebate-program-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXQRADYBIRMKBDGSU6ONCSCW4M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本 10 月通胀可能放缓，出口回升：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五的一项民意调查显示，由于能源价格增长放缓，日本10月份的核心消费通胀率可能连续第二个月下降。【原文：Japan's core consumer inflation likely cooled for the second straight month in October on slower growth in energy prices, a Reuters poll showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-october-inflation-likely-eased-exports-picked-up-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7J4Q6Y5435MV5CLKKIJXLTDETU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 04:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025 年新增氧化铝供应有望打破价格涨势纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[将铝土矿转化为氧化铝的新产能将于明年投产，这将缓解供应紧张的局面，并有可能阻止用于制造铝的材料价格破纪录地上涨。【原文：New capacity for converting bauxite into alumina due online next year is set to ease tight supplies and potentially halt a record-breaking price rally of the material used to make aluminium.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/new-alumina-supplies-2025-poised-rupture-record-price-rally-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTKXQZA52NOW3FOO7DCFSPUTFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 04:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 希望通过保罗与泰森的比赛实现体育直播的突破]]></title><description><![CDATA[前重量级拳王迈克-泰森（Mike Tyson）与社交媒体影响者杰克-保罗（Jake Paul）将于本周五进行对决，这是 Netflix 最新的一记重拳，这家媒体巨头希望在体育节目流媒体化的冲刺阶段从中获利。【原文：A showdown between former heavyweight champion Mike Tyson and social media influencer-turned-fighter Jake Paul on Friday is the latest one-two punch from Netflix, as the media giant hopes to cash in on sports' sprint to streaming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-hopes-live-sports-knockout-with-paul-tyson-fight-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AETMKO7MCBJ6FB2YGA7XC3Y3TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:58:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大劳工委员会命令蒙特利尔港口恢复运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大劳资关系委员会（CIRB）命令蒙特利尔港从周六上午起恢复运营，该港口的雇主协会称，在联邦政府介入并指示劳资委员会结束港口纠纷后，蒙特利尔港恢复了运营。【原文：Canada's Industrial Relations Board (CIRB) ordered a resumption of operations at the Port of Montreal from Saturday morning, the port's employers association said, after the federal government stepped in and directed the labour board to end port disputes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-labour-board-orders-operations-resume-montreal-port-2024-11-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCBVKAM6FRLVVLHGKLBXEBBJ74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:53:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>