<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:37:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:37:08 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国零售商试图在更短的假日购物季中激发消费热情]]></title><description><![CDATA[为了在 "黑色星期五 "吸引购物者，大型连锁零售商打算展示互动产品和体验，包括雷朋（Ray Ban）的增强现实眼镜、电子产品零售商百思买（Best Buy）的超大电视以及美国连锁百货公司诺德斯特龙（Nordstrom Inc.【原文：To entice shoppers on Black Friday, major retail chains intend to showcase interactive products and experiences, including Ray Ban augmented-reality glasses, extra-extra-large TVs at electronics retailer Best Buy and new spa services at U.S. department store chain Nordstrom Inc .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-retailers-attempt-stir-excitement-during-shorter-holiday-shopping-season-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXH57COC5NL5HA7AOZS2CBI6TE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:24:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥警告特朗普关税将扼杀 40 万个美国就业机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥是美国最大的贸易伙伴。【原文：Mexico is the United States' top trade partner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/mexico-warns-trumps-tariff-would-kill-400000-us-jobs-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q65TG5JMBBJ7NMNISKY7NTZLU4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:21:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第三季度经济增长率未作修正，为 2.8]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周三证实，在消费者支出强劲的推动下，美国经济在第三季度实现了稳健增长。【原文：The U.S. economy grew at a solid clip in the third quarter, the government confirmed on Wednesday, amid robust consumer spending.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-third-quarter-economic-growth-unrevised-28-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVQ7Z5ASTJM5BHM7OCSDZLIZAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:14:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，11月美国汽车销量将在更大幅度的折扣中增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[据行业咨询公司J.D. Power和GlobalData周三联合发布的报告称，受为清理库存而提高折扣的影响，预计11月份美国新车销量将同比增长6.7%。【原文：New vehicle sales in the U.S. are projected to have risen 6.7% in November from a year earlier, driven by higher discounts to clear elevated inventory, according to a joint report by industry consultants J.D. Power and GlobalData on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-auto-sales-set-rise-november-amid-steeper-discounts-report-shows-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JGOVWKO2AZJYPM2GOTNHALK2VM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 10 月份核心资本货物订单意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，美国主要制造业资本货物的新订单出人意料地减少，表明本季度企业在设备方面的支出有所放缓。【原文：New orders for key U.S.-manufactured capital goods unexpectedly fell in October, suggesting a moderation in business spending on equipment this quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-core-capital-goods-orders-unexpectedly-fall-october-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R5CAICT3RBPMXGBKXC4EIMASQQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数进一步下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济金的美国人数量再次下降，但许多下岗工人正经历着长期失业，这为美联储在 12 月再次降息敞开了大门。【原文：The number of Americans filing new applications for unemployment benefits fell again last week, but many laid-off workers are experiencing long bouts of joblessness, keeping the door open to another interest rate cut from the Federal Reserve in December.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-decline-further-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ITNIGTJBNKRZP5ZRKCY5WLGBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称福特裁员意味着德国工厂的 "逐步死亡]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国 IG Metall 工会周三抨击了福特公司削减数千个工作岗位的计划，称重组将意味着这家美国汽车制造商在科隆的生产基地将慢慢死亡。【原文：Germany's IG Metall union lashed out on Wednesday at plans to cut thousands of jobs at Ford, saying that the restructuring would spell a slow death for the U.S. automaker's production site in Cologne.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/union-says-layoffs-ford-spell-incremental-death-german-site-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26CLOGW3LZJNJEPE67NBFPBVMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宜家高管：贸易关税加大了保持低价的难度]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大家具零售商宜家的首席财务官周三告诉路透社，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普计划征收的关税将使宜家更难保持低价。【原文：Tariffs planned by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump will make it harder for IKEA to keep prices low, the chief financial officer of the world's biggest furniture retailer told Reuters on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trade-tariffs-make-it-harder-keep-prices-low-ikea-executive-says-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MILRNQIJPFN5PAQ3VGUPBARESM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[最大的宜家零售商因降价影响销售而遭受利润打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的宜家家具零售商宜家家居（IKEA）周三公布年度净利润大幅下降，原因是该公司试图通过降价吸引更多注重成本的顾客光顾其蓝色大卖场。【原文：The world's biggest retailer of IKEA furniture on Wednesday reported a big drop in annual net profit after cutting prices in an attempt to coax more cost-conscious shoppers into its big blue stores.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/biggest-ikea-retailer-takes-profit-hit-price-cuts-dent-sales-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TLJW2PXQBZJFXFZKO3M2OYTQY4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即使房价上涨放缓，美国住房负担能力仍将恶化]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社对房地产专家进行的一项民意调查显示，由于供应紧张和美联储仅再下调几次利率，未来一年美国首次购房者的购房负担能力将进一步恶化，即使平均房价涨幅放缓。【原文：Purchasing affordability for first-time U.S. homebuyers will worsen over the coming year on tight supply and just a few more Federal Reserve interest rate cuts, even as average home price rises slow, according to a Reuters poll of property experts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-housing-affordability-worsen-even-price-rises-slow-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AUTHZUOBGFPUBC4WLIFOXXJOKM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Avolta 赢得肯尼迪机场合同，是其 2024 年在北美最大的合同之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士免税零售商 Avolta 周三表示，该公司赢得了一项从 2026 年起在纽约肯尼迪国际机场经营多家免税店、旅游便利店和特色零售店的合约，这是该公司今年在北美签订的最大合约之一。【原文：Avolta has won a deal to operate several duty-free, travel convenience and specialty retail stores at New York's John F. Kennedy International Airport from 2026, one of its largest contracts in North America this year, the Swiss duty-free retailer said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/avolta-wins-contract-jfk-airport-among-its-largest-namerica-2024-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LW4DXWKAZ5JVRCIZMC5WF6ODH4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国内阁批准改善资本市场准入的措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国政府消息人士告诉路透社，德国内阁周三批准了一揽子促进初创企业发展和改善资本市场准入的措施，但目前还不清楚议会是否会在二月大选前批准这些措施。【原文：The German cabinet on Wednesday approved a package of measures to promote startups and improve access to capital markets, government sources told Reuters, though it is unclear whether it will also be green-lit by parliament before February elections.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-cabinet-approves-measures-better-access-capital-markets-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5VIUJFY7NPJLE3WDQLZQVZWJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于阿达尼美国贿赂案起诉书您需要了解的信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌参与一项价值 2.65 亿美元的贿赂计划而被美国当局起诉，这在他的同名港口大豆企业集团中引起了轩然大波。阿达尼集团否认了这些指控。【原文：Indian billionaire Gautam Adani's indictment by U.S. authorities for his alleged role in a $265 million bribery scheme has sent shockwaves through his eponymous ports-to-soybeans conglomerate. The Adani Group denies the allegations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/what-you-need-know-about-adani-us-bribery-indictment-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFBXGD22TJI2DMPIERAJ3ROUNM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:26:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[烈酒行业寻求豁免特朗普的普遍关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个代表顶级烈酒制造商的贸易机构告诉路透社，烈酒行业正计划推动豁免即将上任的特朗普政府对美国进口产品征收的任何普遍关税。【原文：The spirits industry is planning to push for an exemption to any universal tariffs on U.S. imports imposed by the incoming Trump administration, a trade body representing top spirits makers told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spirits-industry-ask-exemption-trumps-universal-tariffs-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFMYBEFLTFMRRP7MFO2DU65W64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:21:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠普、戴尔预测疲软引发股价大跌，PC 市场复苏存疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[戴尔和惠普的股价周三下跌，因为这两家个人电脑制造商发布的预测对人工智能个人电脑推动的市场复苏表示怀疑。【原文：Shares of Dell and HP fell on Wednesday after the personal computer makers issued forecasts that cast doubt on a market recovery driven by artificial intelligence-enabled PCs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/hp-dells-weak-forecasts-spark-share-selloff-doubts-over-pc-market-recovery-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLTNZNAKVJPY5K2IACO72FPGLA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者等待美国关键数据，多伦多证券交易所期货上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[与加拿大主要股指挂钩的期货周三小幅上涨，因为投资者在等待当天晚些时候美国的关键通胀数据，以判断美联储的货币政策前景。【原文：Futures tied to Canada's main stock index rose slightly on Wednesday, as investors awaited key U.S. inflation data later in the day to gauge the Federal Reserve's monetary policy outlook.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tsx-futures-edge-up-investors-await-key-us-data-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q5D6D4XGCFNGDBJS7S6MFXGRJA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通胀数据公布前市场谨慎，期货下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周三下滑，因为投资者在等待关键的经济数据，包括一份至关重要的通胀报告，预计该报告将影响美联储未来的货币政策路径。【原文：U.S. stock index futures slipped on Wednesday as investors awaited key economic data, including a crucial inflation report, which is expected to influence the Federal Reserve's future monetary policy path.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-dip-caution-prevails-ahead-inflation-data-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPONA3HVP5IW5NCB6HLY72XUQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士信贷银行在 2022 年可卡因洗钱案中被判无罪释放]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士一高级法院周三宣判瑞士信贷银行（Credit Suisse）在 2022 年的一项刑事判决中无罪释放，该银行现在是瑞银集团（UBS）的一部分，被认定未能阻止一个保加利亚可卡因贩运团伙的洗钱活动。【原文：A top Swiss court on Wednesday acquitted Credit Suisse of a 2022 criminal conviction when the bank that is now part of UBS was found guilty of failing to prevent money laundering by a Bulgarian cocaine trafficking gang.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/credit-suisse-acquitted-2022-conviction-over-cocaine-cash-laundering-case-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PXHUCXT555KNJAKPW62UOLX2PI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国假期美国关注通胀，法国局势紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RF4U42U7XJMZ7J6MIM7HN3XMWQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:18:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citgo 股票拍卖陷入困境，美国法院准备重启计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位法院顾问周二建议，为支付对委内瑞拉的索赔而进行的 Citgo Petroleum (PDVSAC.UL) 母公司股份拍卖需要彻底改变，并承认长达一年之久的拍卖过程一团糟，需要重新开始。【原文：An auction of shares in a Citgo Petroleum (PDVSAC.UL) parent to pay claims against Venezuela needs to be overhauled, a court adviser recommended on Tuesday, conceding a year-long sale process was in shambles and needed to start fresh.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/with-citgo-share-auction-shambles-us-court-readies-plan-start-over-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PY3NXBRO2VKUJBOYPEAALCGNK4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，CFM 重新分配部分发动机，以促进空中客车公司的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士透露，喷气发动机制造商CFM公司已同意向空中客车公司提供部分发动机，以缩小供应缺口，因为空中客车公司正在努力实现年底目标。【原文：Jet engine maker CFM has agreed to divert some engines to Airbus to narrow a supply gap as the planemaker battles to hit end-year targets, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/cfm-re-allocates-some-engines-boost-airbus-sources-say-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7V4KUCZGMBPJBLUNV6WJLZEGPI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车因后视摄像头显示问题在美国召回超过 22.6 万辆汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周三表示，由于后视摄像头图像可能无法显示，现代汽车公司将在美国召回226,118辆汽车。【原文：Hyundai Motor is recalling 226,118 vehicles in the U.S. over concerns the rear view camera image may fail to display, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-recall-over-226000-vehicles-us-over-rear-view-camera-display-concerns-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M63XVINNRRNOFFQXE6U7BO2LZU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国机器人出租车初创企业 Pony AI 在美国上市融资 2.6 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国机器人出租车公司 Pony AI 周三表示，该公司在美国的首次公开募股已募集到 2.6 亿美元，其美国存托股票的定价为每股 13 美元。【原文：China-based robotaxi company Pony AI said on Wednesday it had raised $260 million in its U.S. initial public offering, pricing its American depositary shares at $13 each.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-robotaxi-startup-pony-ai-raises-260-mln-us-ipo-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RMZM6QKLHZLOJMQCJUCVMJ5RE4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:34:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通因美国经济增长上调墨西哥股票评级，下调巴西股票评级]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国经济增长强劲，摩根大通将墨西哥股票评级从 "中性 "上调至 "增持"，但下调了巴西股票评级，理由是中国经济增长放缓，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税政策带来新的压力。【原文：JPMorgan upgraded Mexican equities to "overweight" from "neutral" on the back of strong U.S. growth, but cut Brazilian equities citing slower growth in China amid emerging pressures from President-elect Donald Trump's tariff policy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/jpmorgan-upgrades-mexican-equities-us-growth-downgrades-brazil-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WZPSZUPA5NZ3J3EIEG6VMQB6A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋航空称波音延误 "折断了翅膀]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿联酋航空公司总裁周三表示，由于缺乏飞机，该公司是一个 "沮丧的实体"，并补充说，如果飞机制造商能够按时交付波音 777-9X 飞机，该公司现在将拥有一支由 85 架飞机组成的机队。【原文：Emirates Airline is a "frustrated entity" because of a lack of planes, the carrier's president said on Wednesday, adding that it would now have an 85-strong fleet of Boeing 777-9X jets if the planemaker had been able to deliver them on time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/emirates-airline-says-wings-clipped-by-boeing-delays-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OL5TUKDLJBJ4FGTHVKYTNGRF4A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[GfK 报告显示，因担心裁员，12 月德国消费者情绪下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三的一项调查显示，德国消费者信心指数预计将在今年最后一个月下滑，打破连续增长的势头，因为面对裁员的报道，家庭对收入前景更加悲观。【原文：German consumer sentiment is expected to tumble in the last month of the year, breaking a streak of increases as households, confronted by reports of job cuts, grow more pessimistic about their income prospects, a survey showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/german-consumer-sentiment-tumbles-december-job-cut-fears-gfk-report-shows-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y7XP6FSVENJKNFL42EH7U52URA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果特朗普征收关税，亚洲可能受益于更便宜的加拿大和墨西哥石油]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易商和分析师表示，如果美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普对从加拿大和墨西哥进口的原油征收25%的进口关税，那么这两个国家的石油生产商将可能被迫降低价格，并将供应转向亚洲。【原文：Oil producers in Canada and Mexico will likely be forced to reduce prices and divert supply to Asia if U.S. President-elect Donald Trump imposes 25% import tariffs on crude imports from the two countries, traders and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/asia-likely-benefit-cheaper-canadian-mexican-oil-if-trump-imposes-tariffs-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEXSCFJVOZJCNEUM4OY2VJBP3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:20:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，10月份外国智能手机在华销量下降44.25]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家政府下属研究公司周三公布的数据，包括苹果公司 iPhone 在内的外国品牌智能手机 10 月份在中国的销量同比下降了 44.25%。【原文：Sales of foreign-branded smartphones, including Apple Inc's iPhone, in China fell 44.25% in October year-on-year, according to data released on Wednesday from a government-affiliated research firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/foreign-smartphone-sales-china-drop-4425-oct-data-shows-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NAMRHZMPFNIT3IG5W24ELA45WE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯顿-马丁筹集新资金，对利润发出警告；股价创两年新低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，英国豪华汽车制造商阿斯顿-马丁（Aston Martin）警告称，由于交货延迟，该公司的年度利润可能下降多达 11%，并表示将筹集新的资金，阿斯顿-马丁的股价下跌多达 9%，创下两年多来的新低。【原文：Shares in Aston Martin fell as much as 9% to a more than two-year low on Wednesday after the British luxury carmaker warned that annual profit could fall as much as 11% on delivery delays and said it would raise new capital.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/aston-martin-raises-265-mln-electrification-drive-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADNNLPGV6NMVZLQIUJJKRHYS3E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚出台法案，对超市不当行为处以巨额罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚政府周三向议会提交了一项法案，该法案将对未能遵守确保不虐待供应商的行业行为准则的大型连锁超市处以可能高达数十亿美元的罚款。【原文：The Australian government on Wednesday introduced a bill into parliament that would impose potentially billion-dollar fines on big supermarket chains that fail to comply with an industry code of conduct ensuring they do not mistreat suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-introduces-bill-imposing-big-fines-supermarket-misconduct-2024-11-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ERLHE3ONNNMRHNVS4FXRC7FUU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:19:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>