<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:42:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:42:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟负责人表示，欧盟将针对美国的对等关税准备反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会主席乌苏拉-冯德莱恩（Ursula von der Leyen）将美国唐纳德-特朗普的普遍关税描述为对世界经济的重大打击，并表示如果谈判失败，欧盟准备采取反制措施。【原文：European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen described U.S. Donald Trump's universal tariffs as a major blow to the world economy and said that the European Union was prepared to respond with countermeasures if negotiations failed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/eu-prepare-countermeasures-us-reciprocal-tariffs-says-eu-chief-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QADMRSBRQJP3ZIC2NNSYZFWB44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:35:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织认为日本可持续实现央行的通胀目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）周三表示，日本正呈现出可持续实现央行 2% 通胀目标的迹象，强劲的消费和资本支出可能会支撑日本经济。【原文：Japan is showing signs of sustainably achieving the central bank's 2% inflation target with robust consumption and capital expenditure likely to underpin the economy, the International Monetary Fund said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/imf-sees-japan-sustainably-hitting-central-banks-inflation-target-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EA36IVJRXJMP7PN3Q54G3NEWRI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:24:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布全面征收关税，避险黄金创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对主要贸易伙伴征收比预期更为激进的关税，扩大了全球贸易战，紧张的投资者纷纷转向避险资产，黄金在周四创下历史新高。【原文：Gold hit a record high on Thursday, as nervous investors rushed towards safe-haven assets after U.S. President Donald Trump announced more aggressive-than-anticipated tariffs against major trading partners, widening the global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/safe-haven-gold-hits-record-peak-trump-announces-sweeping-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSULCURIFZJXTNCUYP2DN5AEWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称，因特朗普加征关税，Stellantis 将关闭加拿大温莎工厂两周]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大工会 Unifor 周三表示，汽车制造商 Stellantis 将关闭其位于安大略省温莎的装配厂两周。【原文：Carmaker Stellantis will close its assembly plant in Windsor, Ontario for two weeks, Canadian labour union Unifor said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-close-canadas-windsor-plant-two-weeks-over-trump-tariffs-union-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AG35VCLX5ZNJFMDCMGTPVD65WE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的对等关税将如何影响印度的出口？]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对所有进入美国的商品提高贸易壁垒，印度在周三遭到了美国的对等征税。【原文：India was slapped with a reciprocal tax by the United States on Wednesday, as President Donald Trump raised trade barriers on all goods entering America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/how-will-trumps-reciprocal-tariffs-impact-indian-exports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJBLZ6GZGRKANG2P4BN5764PNQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发全球反制承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周三宣布对来自所有国家的商品征收 10%的新基准关税，并对其政府称对美国进口设置高壁垒的国家征收对等关税后，世界各国政府承诺对美国采取反制措施。【原文：Governments around the world pledged counter measures on the U.S. after President Donald Trump unveiled on Wednesday a new baseline 10% tariff on goods from all countries plus reciprocal tariffs on those that his administration says have high barriers to U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariffs-draw-global-promises-counter-measures-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QOWEL7SVZRIXVHUNO6O4RLE5HI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称将采取一切措施应对特朗普的关税政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本贸易大臣武藤洋治周四表示，日本将保留所有选择来应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普新宣布的关税。【原文：Japanese Trade Minister Yoji Muto said on Thursday that Japan is leaving all options open to respond to U.S. President Donald Trump's newly announced tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japan-says-it-is-leaving-all-options-open-against-trumps-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KFBIKM47QZLZZBPE4G57EZJV4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商业团体在关税后表示台美是共同繁荣的推动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国宣布加征关税后，台湾美国商会周四表示，台美伙伴关系是共同经济繁荣的推动力，也是该地区供应链安全与稳定的核心。【原文：The Taiwan-U.S. partnership is a driver of shared economic prosperity and central to supply chain security and stability in the region, the American Chamber of Commerce in Taiwan said on Thursday after U.S. tariffs were announced.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/taiwan-us-driver-shared-prosperity-us-business-group-says-after-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">44BYARRTBVOBHLB2MI2BV24KGY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国敦促美国取消对等关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国商务部周四表示，中国已敦促美国立即取消单边关税措施，并通过平等对话妥善解决与贸易伙伴的分歧。【原文：China has urged the United States to immediately cancel unilateral tariff measures and properly resolve differences with trading partners through equal dialogue, the commerce ministry said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/china-urges-us-cancel-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXX5QYNTYJMGZLMJVSB4DKDKDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：大众汽车将对受关税影响的汽车征收 "进口费]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三报道，大众汽车将对受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收 25% 关税影响的车辆征收 "进口费"。【原文：Volkswagen will introduce an "import fee" on vehicles affected by the 25% tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-introduce-import-fee-tariff-hit-cars-wsj-reports-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YV45SEUXAJKLRGMBNFEDZUOLJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新PMI显示中国服务业活动升至三个月高点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一项私营部门调查显示，中国 3 月份的服务业活动升至三个月来的新高，商业活动和新订单均比 2 月份有所回升。【原文：China's services activity rose to three-month high in March, with both business activity and new orders picking up from February, a private sector survey showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-services-activity-rises-three-month-high-caixin-pmi-shows-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4X4XTT23WNNSLLHVK2SWU6RWWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 Galan Lithium 公司拒绝接受 1.5 亿美元的阿根廷资产收购要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚伽蓝锂业公司（Galan Lithium）周四表示，该公司拒绝了浙江华友钴业股份有限公司和雷诺集团提出的以1.5亿美元现金收购这家锂勘探公司在阿根廷资产中的股份的提议。【原文：Australia's Galan Lithium said on Thursday that it rejected an offer from Zhejiang Huayou Cobalt Co and Renault Group to acquire the lithium explorer's stake in its Argentine assets for $150 million in cash.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/australias-galan-lithium-declines-150-million-buyout-bid-argentine-assets-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H22I22OMORL7NE235PLKNP72ZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普经济顾问告诉《福克斯商业》：关税将造成 "短期颠簸]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的经济顾问委员会主席斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周三告诉《福克斯商业》（Fox Business），华盛顿宣布的关税措施将造成短期冲击。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's Council of Economic Advisers Chair Stephen Miran told Fox Business on Wednesday there will be short-term bumps caused by tariffs announced by Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tariffs-cause-short-term-bumps-trump-economic-adviser-tells-fox-business-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">724FNX3Z3NPZNENSD3RT4HYOYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布全面征收新关税后，石油下跌近 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对贸易伙伴征收对等关税后，油价周四下跌了 2 美元，这加剧了人们对全球贸易战可能抑制原油需求的担忧。【原文：Oil prices dropped $2 on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced reciprocal tariffs on trading partners, stoking concerns that a global trade war may dampen demand for crude.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-sinks-nearly-3-after-trump-announces-sweeping-new-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFB7DJHL4BIKVA7PLYY33GDARI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:13:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车表示暂无在美国涨价计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车公司联席首席执行官何塞-穆诺兹（Jose Munoz）周四表示，目前没有针对美国关税在美国提价的计划。【原文：Jose Munoz, co-CEO of Hyundai Motor , said on Thursday there were no plans to raise prices in the United States at this time in response to U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-motor-says-no-plan-price-hikes-us-now-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MTMCRYPUZ5LJLKLXWYY5QAQELQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FACTBOX 特朗普大刀阔斧的新互惠关税制度有哪些内容？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对来自所有国家的商品征收 10%的新基准关税，并对其政府称对美国进口设置高壁垒的国家征收更高的互惠税率，从而粉碎了拥有超过 75 年历史的全球贸易体系。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump smashed a more than 75-year-old global trading system with a new baseline 10% U.S. tariff on goods from all countries and higher reciprocal tariff rates for countries that his administration says have high barriers to U.S. imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/whats-trumps-sweeping-new-reciprocal-tariff-regime-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X2G5FVETP5PHXOZ674WF635CLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:49:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行警告美国关税政策可能威胁全球经济增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社悉尼4月3日电）澳大利亚央行周四警告称，美国的贸易政策可能对全球经济构成重大不利因素，导致市场避险情绪急剧升温，并抬高企业的融资成本。【原文：SYDNEY, April 3 (Reuters) - Australia's central bank warned on Thursday that U.S. trade policies could pose significant headwinds for the global economy, causing a sharp rise in risk aversion in markets and lifting financing costs for firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-central-bank-warns-us-tariff-policies-could-threaten-global-growth-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HQTAGUTWZIXZKPBZ53QTJCXXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税后交易员涌入避险天堂，美元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对主要贸易伙伴征收比预期更为激进的关税后，美元周四大幅下滑，欧元则持稳，投资者纷纷寻求避险的日元和瑞士法郎，令市场震荡。【原文：The dollar slid broadly on Thursday, while the euro was steady after U.S. President Donald Trump announced more aggressive-than-anticipated tariffs against major trading partners, jolting the markets as investors sought safe haven yen and Swiss franc.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-slides-traders-rush-into-safe-havens-after-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BDN25IZDGFNQ3GWOZN5IA77M7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:08:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在双边贸易谈判进行之际，美国对印度征收 26% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国对印度征收 26% 的互惠关税，使这个南亚国家期望从唐纳德-特朗普总统的全球贸易政策中获得救济的愿望受挫。【原文：The U.S. slapped a 26% reciprocal tariff on India in a setback to the South Asian country's expectation of getting relief from President Donald Trump's global trade policy that has unnerved world markets for weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-slaps-26-tariff-india-amid-ongoing-bilateral-trade-talks-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEMUF6VZGJPBZE46LN6L4FZ34I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[企业面临特朗普关税乱局的新现实]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在，美国已在全球范围内征收广泛的关税，企业将被迫做出调整--但应对超出预期的征税的选择是有限的，而且对企业及其客户来说也是难以接受的。【原文：Now that the U.S. has instituted broad tariffs worldwide, businesses will be forced to adjust - but the options to cope with the greater-than-expected levies are limited and unpalatable for companies and their customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/companies-face-new-reality-trump-tariff-chaos-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVTV6EBI75N5JIHCJQGZATNKHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 23:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道福特将提供全面折扣，抓住近期关税引发的销售高峰]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位消息人士称，福特汽车公司计划从周四开始宣布多款车型的折扣，利用其健康的库存为客户提供数千美元的优惠，因为一些竞争对手已经提价以消化关税带来的额外成本。【原文：Ford Motor plans to announce discounts across multiple models starting on Thursday, three sources said, leaning on its healthy inventory to offer customers thousands off their vehicles as some competitors have hiked prices to absorb added costs from tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-offer-across-the-board-discounts-jumping-recent-tariff-induced-sales-bump-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7OD3Y4Z6V5MPXDKXCOTAO2ZF7E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 23:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉经济学家称美国关税率飙升至 22%，为 1910 年以来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）的美国经济研究主管周三表示，根据美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）实施的新的全球征税措施，美国对所有进口商品征收的关税税率已从2024年的2.5%飙升至22%。【原文：The U.S. tariff rate on all imports has rocketed to 22% from just 2.5% in 2024 under the new global levies imposed by President Donald Trump, Fitch Ratings' U.S. economic research chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-tariff-rate-rockets-22-highest-since-1910-fitch-economist-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SM3RVL2VYZJBHJXXBJBFGFQDTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:55:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚称美国加征关税 "非朋友所为"，但排除采取对等行动的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税的决定 "不是朋友的行为"，但排除了对美国征收对等关税的可能性。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said on Thursday the decision by U.S. President Donald Trump to impose tariffs was "not the act of a friend," but ruled out placing reciprocal tariffs against the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/australia-says-us-tariffs-not-act-friend-rules-out-reciprocal-move-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LK2OSDXFFFKBNDHGJJY2RTYL4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡尼表示加拿大将对美国采取反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周三表示，加拿大将以反制措施对抗美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税。【原文：Canada will fight U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs with countermeasures, Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-will-impose-counter-measures-united-states-says-carney-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNREBVW6I5ML5PI4IXBR7U6NPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油进口免受特朗普全面关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面新关税豁免了石油、天然气和精炼产品的进口。【原文：Imports of oil, gas and refined products were exempted from U.S. President Donald Trump’s sweeping new tariffs, the White House said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-imports-exempted-trumps-sweeping-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YRUE4ICZVKP5CHHAICKXJOWZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税给疲软的世界经济带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周三公布的最新一轮贸易关税将进一步削弱世界经济的活力，因为世界经济刚刚从大流行后的通胀飙升中恢复过来，又被创纪录的债务所拖累，并受到地缘政治纷争的困扰。【原文：The latest round of U.S. trade tariffs unveiled on Wednesday will sap yet more vigour from a world economy barely recovered from the post-pandemic inflation surge, weighed down by record debt and unnerved by geopolitical strife.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariffs-pile-stress-ailing-world-economy-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZJZX77YKRLPBJJXXUUJDRWTYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大和墨西哥在芬太尼和边境令生效期间不受新的全球税率限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据白宫周三发布的一份情况说明，唐纳德-特朗普总统不会对来自加拿大和墨西哥的商品征收 10%的新全球关税，而他之前因边境控制和芬太尼贩运问题而对来自这两个国家的许多商品征收高达 25% 关税的命令仍然有效。【原文：President Donald Trump is not imposing his new 10% global tariff rate on goods from Canada and Mexico while his previous order remains in place for up to 25% tariffs on many goods from the two in connection to border control and fentanyl trafficking issues, according to a White House fact sheet released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-mexico-not-subject-new-global-rates-while-fentanyl-border-order-place-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTTAL4FU5ZO6FPJT5DIZF5KRIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税令附带的白宫概况介绍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三宣布对从大多数美国贸易伙伴进口的商品全面征收至少 10%的全球关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Wednesday unveiled sweeping global tariffs of at least 10% on goods imported from most U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-fact-sheet-accompanying-trumps-new-tariff-orders-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGMMSUUY4VOFLPCXN56QWZSX6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，甲骨文公司告知客户最近第二次遭到黑客攻击，登录数据被盗]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引两位熟悉此事的人士的话报道，甲骨文公司已告知客户，一名黑客入侵了计算机系统，并盗取了旧的客户登录凭证。【原文：Oracle has told customers that a hacker broke into a computer system and stole old client log-in credential, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/oracle-tells-clients-second-recent-hack-log-in-data-stolen-bloomberg-news-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JOROTHM5VIJBOL3VMITEPOM34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界各国领导人对特朗普的全球关税作出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四公布全球互惠关税后，世界各国领导人开始作出回应。【原文：World leaders began responding after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled global reciprocal tariffs on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/world-leaders-react-trumps-global-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRZZJYMTRJLFBFDKQK5ILR6HEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>