<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:06:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:06:42 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁后，墨西哥 Terrafina 将取消 CIBanco 的托管人身份]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥房地产信托公司 Terrafina 周五表示，由于受到美国洗钱指控，该公司计划解除 CIBanco 银行的受托人职务，这导致墨西哥银行监管机构介入管理。【原文：Mexican real estate trust Terrafina said on Friday it planned to remove bank CIBanco as its trustee due to U.S. money laundering accusations, which resulted in Mexico's banking regulator stepping in to manage it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-terrafina-remove-cibanco-trustee-after-us-sanctions-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FW4SAJ6Z2JJFXBNYXMCKJOBCOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在货币困境中，玻利维亚加密货币交易量增长超过 530]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一篇报道显示，越来越多的玻利维亚人开始转向Binance等加密货币交易所和Tether等稳定币，以对冲当地玻利瓦尔货币的贬值。【原文：Bolivia's central bank on Friday reiterated a dramatic uptick in transactions of digital assets, following a Reuters report that showed how more Bolivians were turning to crypto exchanges like Binance and stablecoins like Tether as a hedge against the depreciation of the local boliviano currency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/bolivia-crypto-transactions-up-over-530-amid-currency-woes-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HKZ3AWKU2JJWTPRYJGB2FJFZQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉未能终止佛罗里达州有关 Model S 致命车祸的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉未能说服联邦法官结束对一名妇女在佛罗里达州基拉戈（Key Largo）因一辆配备自动驾驶功能的 Model S 冲出路面后被撞身亡的诉讼，这为下个月可能进行的审判铺平了道路。【原文：Tesla failed to persuade a federal judge to end a lawsuit over the death of a woman struck after an Autopilot-equipped Model S ran off the road in Key Largo, Florida, paving the way for a possible trial next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/tesla-fails-end-florida-lawsuit-over-fatal-model-s-crash-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYCTWFIR6JILZDNL63EUAVJQOI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:44:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国法庭裁定万事达卡和威士卡的商户收费违反了竞争法]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球支付处理商威士卡公司和万事达卡公司向零售商收取的默认多边交换费违反了竞争法，伦敦一家法庭周五在这场旷日持久的法律纠纷中做出了最新裁决。【原文：Global payments processors Visa and Mastercard's default multilateral interchange fees which are charged to retailers infringe competition law, a London tribunal ruled on Friday in the latest round of the long-running legal saga.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mastercard-visas-merchant-fees-breach-competition-law-uk-tribunal-rules-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EHBVRPVKX5MF3MILKVAIHVINHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特：随着谈判的深入，关税协议可能在劳动节前完成]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周五表示，特朗普政府与其他国家达成的各项贸易协议可能会在9月1日劳动节假期前完成，并提到了与美国18个主要贸易伙伴的会谈，以及对与中国达成的旨在加快稀土运输的协议的新修订。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said on Friday the Trump administration's various trade deals with other countries could be done by the Sept. 1 Labor Day holiday, citing talks with 18 main U.S. trading partners and new revisions to a deal with China aimed at expediting rare earths shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/tariff-deals-could-be-wrapped-up-by-labor-day-bessent-says-talks-pick-up-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BD7EPS6M6NOGFGJ2P6R3VPKUPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:28:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[夏季数据为美联储降息铺平道路，或与特朗普发生进一步冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[上个月基本通胀率意外回升，使物价压力进一步偏离美联储设定的2%的目标，从而使今年夏天的数据成为央行能否恢复降息和缓解与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普之间持续紧张关系的焦点。【原文：An unexpected pickup in underlying inflation last month nudged price pressures further from the Federal Reserve's 2% target, putting this summer's data in the spotlight for whether the central bank can resume cutting interest rates and ease ongoing tension with President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/summertime-data-pave-way-fed-rate-cuts-or-further-conflict-with-trump-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTM2IKA5XNOV5HIQ7OLOU33LPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:01:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[即时观点：华尔街在经历数月动荡后再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五开盘时，美国 500 指数和纳斯达克综合指数创下历史新高，从美国总统唐纳德-特朗普以关税为基础的贸易政策引发的动荡期中反弹。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Composite reached all-time highs at the opening bell on Friday, bouncing back from a turbulent period sparked by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies based on tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-wall-street-hits-record-highs-after-turbulent-months-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5ORSUZRLJNENEGHADAY27JPPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:51:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比亚迪将投资 9,400 万美元，将匈牙利电动巴士产量提高两倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[匈牙利外交部长彼得-齐雅尔托（Peter Szijjarto）表示，中国汽车制造商比亚迪将投资 320 亿福林（9400 万美元）在匈牙利北部城镇科马罗姆（Komarom）新建一座工厂，使其年产量增加两倍，达到 1,250 辆电动巴士和卡车。【原文：Chinese automaker BYD will invest 32 billion forints ($94 million) in a new plant in the northern Hungarian town of Komarom, tripling its annual capacity to 1,250 electric buses and trucks, Hungarian Foreign Minister Peter Szijjarto said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/byd-invest-94-million-triple-electric-bus-output-hungary-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SZ2IMBXSQNMQLKCDOVPE4UG334</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Electrek 报道，特斯拉聘请前 Cruise 高管担任人工智能总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新闻网站 Electrek 周四报道，特斯拉已聘请前 Cruise 高管 Henry Kuang 担任该公司的人工智能总监，该公司正寻求在美国扩大机器人出租车业务。【原文：Tesla has hired former Cruise executive, Henry Kuang, as the automaker's AI director, according to a report by news website Electrek on Thursday, as the company looks to expand robotaxi operations in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-hires-former-cruise-executive-ai-director-electrek-reports-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GGV7GCBCTNJSXEAE5ANBVQ63LM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土再次流动，但并不自由]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管汽车制造商和供应商表示生产计划仍面临不确定性和持续的短缺风险，但随着中国稀土磁铁开始流通，整个汽车供应链大规模停产的威胁正在减弱。【原文：The threat of mass shutdowns across the automotive supply chain is fading as Chinese rare earth magnets begin to flow, though automakers and suppliers say production plans still face uncertainties and a continued risk of shortages.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-rare-earths-are-flowing-again-not-freely-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2RCPFHR4FROGRDY77RX674DOLM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:29:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迈阿密布里克尔城市中心以高达 5.487 亿美元的价格出售给西蒙地产公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国购物中心所有者西蒙地产集团（Simon Property Group）周五表示，已从太古地产（Swire Properties）手中收购了迈阿密布里克尔城市中心（Brickell City Centre）的停车场和零售部分，收购价格高达 5.487 亿美元。【原文：U.S.-based shopping mall owner Simon Property Group has acquired the parking and retail segments of Miami's Brickell City Centre for up to $548.7 million from Swire Properties , the Hong Kong-listed company said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/miamis-brickell-city-centre-sold-simon-property-up-5487-million-deal-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWITQXIUQVLPPIY5J5VG7LVKYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《德国商报》报道，保时捷考虑出售 MHP，估值可能超过 10 亿欧元]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业日报《Handelsblatt》周五援引两位知情人士的话报道称，保时捷正在寻求出售其咨询和 IT 服务业务 MHP，该业务的估值可能超过 10 亿欧元（11.7 亿美元）。【原文：Porsche is looking to sell its consulting and IT services business MHP, which could possibly be valued at over 1 billion euros ($1.17 billion), the German business daily Handelsblatt reported on Friday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-considers-selling-mhp-possible-valuation-over-1-bln-euros-handelsblatt-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SWKRD6BGLVLCZHYKXYPH6PP2QA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，微软下一代人工智能芯片生产推迟至 2026 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周五援引三位相关人士的话报道，微软的下一代 Maia 人工智能芯片将面临至少六个月的延期，量产时间将从 2025 年推迟到 2026 年。【原文：Microsoft's next-generation Maia AI chip is facing a delay of at least six months, pushing its mass production to 2026 from 2025, The Information reported on Friday, citing three people involved in the effort.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsofts-next-gen-ai-chip-production-delayed-2026-information-reports-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AZHAY52JIROB5NQYD3WT7LQOPA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:17:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普 500 指数和纳斯达克指数创下历史新高，因人工智能押注重燃，降息希望渺茫]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于人工智能热情重燃以及宽松货币政策的前景推动美国股市从长达数月的颓势中复苏，美国 500 指数和纳斯达克综合指数周五创下历史新高。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 and the Nasdaq Composite hit all-time highs on Friday as renewed AI enthusiasm and the prospect of a looser monetary policy powered a recovery in U.S. stocks from months-long rout.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/sp-500-nasdaq-hit-record-highs-renewed-ai-bets-rate-cut-hope-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">46HCBAXQMJI23PMY2L7RFICQGM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州的纽瑟姆起诉福克斯新闻，就特朗普的通话提出 7.87 亿美元的诽谤索赔]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州州长称，该电视台在报道他与唐纳德-特朗普的通话内容时诽谤了他，因为通话内容与总统打击移民有关。【原文：California's governor said the network defamed him in covering his phone call with Donald Trump related to the president's immigration crackdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/newsom-accuses-fox-news-lying-about-trump-call-787-million-defamation-lawsuit-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AP7IBLJC5BOCBD64XXTZYREGAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行首席执行官称赞特朗普可能取消报复性税收]]></title><description><![CDATA[有迹象表明，美国共和党人可能会从其税收和支出法案中取消第 899 款报复性税收提案，巴克莱银行首席执行官对此表示欢迎。【原文：The CEO of Barclays has welcomed indications that U.S. Republicans may scrap the Section 899 retaliatory tax proposal from their tax and spending bill.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-ceo-hails-possible-scrapping-trump-retaliatory-tax-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NG6HLZHRJNKYNKD47LL223JBSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纳斯达克指数创历史新高，有望进入新一轮牛市]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，纳斯达克指数创下历史新高，因为投资者对人工智能和宽松货币政策的前景持乐观态度，纷纷涌入科技公司，使该指数有望确认牛市。【原文：The Nasdaq hit a record high on Friday, as investors piled into technology companies on optimism around artificial intelligence and the prospect for looser monetary policy, putting the index on track to confirm a bull market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nasdaq-hits-record-high-track-new-bull-market-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PH6GAXCFKVLCJCG7ULNH5Q6CWI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国巴黎银行将收购汇丰银行在德国的托管和存管业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国巴黎银行周五表示，法国巴黎银行与欧洲最大银行汇丰银行达成一致，收购汇丰欧洲大陆在德国的托管和存管银行业务。【原文：BNP Paribas agreed with Europe's biggest bank HSBC to acquire the custody and depositary bank business of HSBC Continental Europe in Germany, BNP Paribas said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bnp-paribas-acquire-hsbcs-custody-depositary-business-germany-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H5DRR6TZZRJEHAJWJXO6DFMN2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员就葛兰素史克撤下儿童哮喘吸入器一事展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国民主党参议员玛吉-哈桑（Maggie Hassan）周五表示，她将对英国制药巨头葛兰素史克公司（GlaxoSmithKline）决定停产一种广泛使用的儿童哮喘吸入剂一事展开调查。【原文：Democratic U.S. Senator Maggie Hassan said on Friday she is launching an investigation into British pharmaceutical giant GlaxoSmithKline's decision to discontinue a widely used asthma inhaler for children.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-senator-investigates-gsk-pulling-childrens-asthma-inhaler-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHQLGV3N3JPJ5C44TRS3EIONBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[各国政府和监管机构加强对 DeepSeek 的审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人工智能初创公司 DeepSeek 今年 1 月表示，它已经开发出一种人工智能模型，可以与 ChatGPT 相媲美，而且成本更低。【原文：Chinese AI startup DeepSeek, which said in January it had developed an AI model to rival ChatGPT at much lower cost, has come under scrutiny in some countries for its security policies and privacy practices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/governments-regulators-increase-scrutiny-deepseek-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWP2EVYKG5NVHO352RLFHSHRR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:58:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿联酋基金购买了 1 亿美元的特朗普世界自由代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家总部位于阿拉伯联合酋长国的基金购买了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普家族的加密企业世界自由金融公司（World Liberty Financial）发行的价值 1 亿美元的数字代币，成为其最大的公开投资者。【原文：A United Arab Emirates-based fund has bought $100 million worth of digital tokens issued by World Liberty Financial, the crypto venture of U.S. President Donald Trump's family, becoming its largest publicly known investor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uae-fund-buys-100-million-trumps-world-liberty-tokens-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LF7XBQ2UZRI7RB7R3G4BWHOUEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 5 月消费者支出意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者支出在 5 月份意外下降，原因是在征收关税之前抢先购买汽车等商品所带来的提振作用逐渐减弱，而月度通胀增幅依然温和。【原文：U.S. consumer spending unexpectedly fell in May as the boost from the pre-emptive buying of goods like motor vehicles ahead of tariffs faded, while monthly inflation increases remained moderate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-spending-falls-unexpectedly-may-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2UNGPCLVRKVHHPFQVBH3US6E4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金连续第六周遭遇资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 6 月 25 日，美国股票基金连续第六周遭遇资金外流，原因是投资者在接近历史高点时获利了结，并在关键的经济增长和通胀数据公布前保持观望。【原文：U.S. equity funds suffered outflows for a sixth straight week through June 25 as investors took profits near record highs and stayed on edge ahead of key growth and inflation data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-suffer-sixth-weekly-outflows-row-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUA6KFFXDZJPVFOIPOONAE2DMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利预计今年将降息两次，并可能暂停降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）坚持他的观点，即通胀降温将允许这家全球最重要的主要央行从今年 9 月开始两次下调政策利率。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari is sticking to his view that cooling inflation will allow the world's most important major central bank to cut its policy rate twice this year, starting in September.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-kashkari-expects-two-rate-cuts-this-year-with-pause-possible-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PI76S7BMJLC7ELQ5PDSYT3K7A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球股票基金连续第二周出现资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至6月25日的七天里，全球股票基金连续第二周出现资金外流，原因是投资者在市场创纪录高点附近获利了结，并在关键的美国经济产出和通胀报告公布前转为谨慎。【原文：Global equity funds saw money outflows for a second straight week in the seven days to June 25 as investors booked profits near record market highs and turned cautious ahead of key U.S. economic output and inflation reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ROUPNYP5ABNDRJE6LQRBEWHKQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，中国时装零售商申银万国将罕见地秘密申请在香港上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，在中国创办的快速时尚零售商申银万国计划以保密方式提交香港上市招股说明书草案，这与公司公开提交首次公开募股文件的惯例大相径庭。【原文：China-founded fast-fashion retailer Shein plans to file a draft prospectus confidentially for its Hong Kong listing, marking a rare departure from the usual practice of companies making public filings of IPO documents, three sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/china-fashion-retailer-shein-file-confidentially-hong-kong-ipo-rare-move-sources-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D4PF35DD5ZLNTHW27DIIFTZBTA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:24:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元问题盘旋在辛特拉顶级央行行长会议上空]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周，世界顶级央行行长将在葡萄牙辛特拉举行会议，届时，一个百万美元的问题将笼罩在他们的心头：以美国货币为中心的货币体系是否开始瓦解？【原文：A million-dollar question will hang over the world's top central bankers when they meet in Sintra, Portugal, next week: Is the monetary system centred on the U.S. currency beginning to unravel?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/dollar-question-hovers-over-top-central-bankers-meeting-sintra-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZQQB4NQ6JLVNH3STFDLZWBEHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普计划颁布行政命令，在与中国的竞争中推动人工智能发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[据四位熟悉规划的消息人士透露，特朗普政府正在准备一揽子行政措施，旨在促进能源供应，为美国人工智能的扩张提供动力。【原文：The Trump administration is readying a package of executive actions aimed at boosting energy supply to power the U.S. expansion of artificial intelligence, according to four sources familiar with the planning.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/trump-plans-executive-orders-power-ai-growth-race-with-china-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIJV6EAJ65NCPMI4O72LN47OZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[暴力扼杀经济增长，犯罪每年给智利造成 80 亿美元损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个多世纪以来，圣地亚哥市中心的 La Piojera 一直是一家热闹非凡的酒吧，以典型的智利美食、饮料和音乐吸引着当地人和游客。【原文：La Piojera in downtown Santiago has been a lively bar for over a century, drawing locals and tourists with typical Chilean foods, drinks and music, but now its doors are shutting earlier and sales are plummeting as rising crime has strangled the country and the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/crime-costs-chile-8-billion-year-violence-chokes-economic-growth-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QEO4ZI54BISRKGLQ4P4FAQOOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价华尔街与新纪录擦肩而过]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-06-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPZGM7I2XVKNVKUSPRYELFLRIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>