<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:37:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:37:15 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的贸易战炮火震撼市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[在唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对美国主要贸易伙伴征收关税后，投资者周一买入美元、抛售股票并担心通货膨胀，争相评估贸易战风险。【原文：Investors bought dollars, sold stocks and fretted about inflation on Monday in a scramble to assess the risk of trade war after Donald Trump put tariffs on top U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-trade-war-salvo-jolts-markets-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CT6NXQ2HOJMH5J35AZR7PYIUZY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受特朗普关税影响，亚洲汽车制造商跌幅居前]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，日本和韩国汽车制造商及其供应商的股票领跌亚洲股市，因为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对墨西哥、加拿大和中国全面征收关税，使整个地区的出口商遭受重创。【原文：Shares of Japanese and South Korean car makers and their suppliers led declines in Asia on Monday, as exporters across the region were walloped by U.S. President Donald Trump's introduction of sweeping tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/asia-automakers-lead-decline-region-takes-beating-trump-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDPEVJS3HVOJZCXNWANGDUXK64</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度誓言避免发出贸易保护主义信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）采取关税举措之际，印度财政部最高官员在削减高端摩托车进口关税后表示，印度不想发出任何保护主义的信号。【原文：India does not want to give any signal that it is protectionist, the top bureaucrat in the finance ministry said, after slashing import duties on high-end motorcycles, amid U.S. President Donald Trump's moves on tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-vows-avoid-protectionist-signals-trade-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7DS46QCSSJLWJPYFH6SMIRLOW4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:59:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税可能对大宗商品和能源行业产生哪些影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周六对加拿大和墨西哥征收25%的关税，对中国征收10%的关税，并称这些措施是打击非法移民和毒品贸易所必需的。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump slapped Canada and Mexico with duties of 25% and China with a 10% levy on Saturday, calling the measures necessary to combat illegal immigration and the drug trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/how-trumps-tariffs-might-affect-commodity-energy-sectors-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQELWI7T4RIPXAAHGCBJ3MAG7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本经济产业省称，尚难预测 DeepSeek 对电力需求的潜在影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本产业省通过电子邮件表示，它知道有一种观点认为，数据中心的扩张可能会增加电力需求，但目前还很难预测随着 DeepSeek 等一项技术的出现，电力需求会发生怎样的变化。【原文：Japan's industry ministry is aware of a view that expansion of data centres may increase demand for electricity, however, it is difficult yet to predict how demand may change with the appearance of one technology such as DeepSeek, it said by email.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/difficult-yet-predict-deepseeks-potential-impact-power-demand-japans-meti-says-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCXHMK3WZFO6TKDL4TJLWEAIKE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球经济 特朗普关税引发情绪波动，亚洲工厂活动疲软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的民间调查显示，由于中国需求疲软以及美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁提高关税，影响了商业情绪，亚洲的工厂活动在1月份有所减弱，从而使该地区的经济前景变得暗淡。【原文：Asia's factory activity weakened in January as soft Chinese demand and threats of higher tariffs by U.S. President Donald Trump weighed on business sentiment, private surveys showed on Monday, darkening the outlook for the region's economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-economy-asias-factory-activity-weakens-trump-tariffs-jolt-sentiment-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GQRDBLX6ZPLDCDCSOQPCN2QJE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财新制造业采购经理人指数显示 1 月份中国工厂活动增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一进行的一项私营企业调查显示，由于贸易不确定性增加，1 月份中国工厂活动增速放缓，员工人数创下近五年来最快降幅。【原文：China's factory activity grew at a slower pace in January, while staffing levels fell at the quickest pace in nearly five years as trade uncertainties increased, a private-sector business survey showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-factory-activity-growth-slows-january-caixin-pmi-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRZCW3DTURJJJMYJL545F2LF3Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚购物者受折扣诱惑，支撑第四季度经济]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚 12 月份的零售额有所下滑，这是对上个月 "黑色星期五 "大肆挥霍的回报，但打折活动帮助购物者在整个第四季度为经济增长做出了急需的贡献。【原文：Australian retail sales dipped in December as pay back for a Black Friday splurge the month before, but discounting helped shoppers make a desperately-needed contribution to economic growth over the whole fourth quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/australia-shoppers-lured-by-discounts-shore-up-economy-4q-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXJIWE4GPJLHZLQMJTIVIZQS7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发贸易战，股市暴跌，美元飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元和比特币暴跌，油价上涨。【原文：The euro and bitcoin plunged while oil prices rose.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1pixtv-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76NVLAILPRLGHH5Z5AB3AC5DMI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，日本工厂活动延续下滑态势，乐观情绪减弱]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，一项私营部门调查显示，由于需求低迷，日本工厂活动以 10 个月来最快的速度下滑，商业信心创下两年多来的新低，这表明制造业正承受着沉重的压力。【原文：Japan's factory activity fell at the fastest pace in 10 months on sluggish demand, a private-sector survey showed on Monday, with business confidence hitting a more than two-year low in a sign that the manufacturing sector is under heavy pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-factory-activity-extends-decline-optimism-weakens-pmi-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORHB3U73QZPW7EQTLC5L7QMNTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摘要显示，日本央行董事会在 1 月会议上讨论了更多加息的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行 1 月份会议的意见摘要周一显示，日本央行决策者讨论了进一步加息的可能性，一些决策者警告通胀上行风险和日元疲软可能对经济造成的损害。【原文：Bank of Japan policymakers discussed the likelihood of raising interest rates further with some warning of upside inflation risks and the damage a weak yen could inflict on the economy, a summary of opinions at their January meeting showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/boj-board-discussed-january-meeting-likelihood-more-rate-hikes-summary-shows-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YRUWEJYONFLNNMV5HKZ6SPQBK4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 推出新的人工智能工具，为研究任务提供便利]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenAI 周日推出了一款名为 "深度研究 "的新型人工智能（AI）工具，并称该工具可在互联网上针对复杂任务开展多步骤研究。【原文：OpenAI launched a new artificial intelligence (AI) tool on Sunday called "deep research", which it said conducts multi-step research on the internet for complex tasks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-launches-new-ai-tool-facilitate-research-tasks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7SYWNWOZYBILHF62CK3TSLEZCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:19:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星首席执行官就有争议的合并案面临裁决]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子（Samsung Electronics）董事长李在镕（Jay Y. Lee）周一将面临首尔一家上诉法院对其 2015 年并购案的裁决。【原文：Samsung Electronics Chair Jay Y. Lee faces a ruling by a Seoul appeals court on Monday over a 2015 merger that prosecutors said was designed to cement his control of the tech giant at the expense of minority shareholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/samsung-chief-faces-ruling-controversial-merger-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A76NF7FEBVMIPBHIZKTGHJJKCU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人民币创历史新低，墨西哥比索和加元因特朗普关税而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国人民币周一在离岸交易中跌至历史新低，墨西哥比索和加拿大元跌至多年低点，此前美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对这些国家征收关税，引发了对贸易战升级的担忧。【原文：China's yuan slumped to a record low in offshore trading on Monday, while Mexico's peso and Canada's dollar tumbled to multi-year troughs after U.S. President Donald Trump slapped the countries with tariffs, triggering fears of an escalating trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/yuan-hits-record-low-mexican-peso-canadian-dollar-tumble-trump-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SOQTDIM6RNLJO3KURP5V2EBMI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税后油价跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税，引发了市场对贸易战和美国最大的两个原油供应国原油供应中断的担忧，油价在周一开盘时跳涨。【原文：Oil prices jumped at the market open on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump imposes tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China, raising fears of a trade war and disruption in crude supply from two of the United States' biggest suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-jump-after-trump-imposes-tariffs-canada-mexico-china-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GFFP63AP7FJFNLF7XBPLWY7VZE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税震荡市场，比特币跌破 10 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球贸易战的阴影让投资者惶惶不安，并将他们挤出风险资产，加密货币价格下滑。【原文：Cryptocurrency prices slid as the spectre of a global trade war put investors on edge and pushed them out of risky assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/bitcoin-slides-below-100000-tariffs-rattle-markets-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQVEMCRP25LR7HKJMI7RDORTPI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:41:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大将对美国关税采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府一位高级官员周日表示，加拿大将根据相关国际机构采取法律行动，挑战美国对大多数加拿大商品征收25%关税的做法，并称美国的关税是非法和不合理的。【原文：Canada will take legal action under the relevant international bodies to challenge the 25% tariffs imposed by the United States on most Canadian goods, a senior government official said on Sunday, calling the tariffs illegal and unjustified.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-take-legal-action-against-us-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5RBDJ2ZPBPG3IQOU5IHMB3YMY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税引发贸易战，墨西哥谢因鲍姆誓言顽强抵抗]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥总统克劳迪娅-希恩鲍姆（Claudia Sheinbaum）在墨西哥政府与美国宣布相互征收关税一天后的周日表示，理智应该占上风。【原文：Mexico's President Claudia Sheinbaum said on Sunday that reason should prevail a day after her government and the U.S. announced tariffs against one another, raising her fist in the air as she said she does not lack courage to respond.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-sheinbaum-vows-resilience-us-tariffs-trigger-trade-war-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VP2WVJINGZOEHCJMBMDSQLMN5M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标特朗普发动贸易战，各方纷纷躲避]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE54RORANPSFN2FO2EP223BOY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大将推出减轻企业关税负担的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大官员周日宣布，他们将为加拿大企业提供一种机制，使其免受未来几天生效的针对美国的报复性关税的影响。【原文：Canadian officials announced Sunday they will provide a mechanism for Canadian businesses to obtain relief from retaliatory tariffs set to take effect against the United States in the coming days.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canada-launch-program-relieve-businesses-tariff-hit-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RK3JYJP6C5PFPNMCORBFCT2UN4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 19:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国人可能在与墨西哥、加拿大和中国的贸易战中感受到 "痛苦]]></title><description><![CDATA["这将是美国的黄金时代！"唐纳德-特朗普在社交媒体上写道。"会有一些痛苦吗？是的，也许会（也许不会！）"。【原文："This will be the golden age of America!" Donald Trump wrote on social media. "Will there be some pain? Yes, maybe (and maybe not!)."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-says-americans-could-feel-pain-trade-war-with-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3NFGKVFGVKE5DTMSHIJYP7TRE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 17:43:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统称已敲定与加拿大的新贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[厄瓜多尔总统丹尼尔-诺沃亚（Daniel Noboa）周日在社交媒体上表示，经过数月谈判，厄瓜多尔和加拿大已敲定一项新的贸易协定。【原文：Ecuador and Canada have finalized a new trade accord following months of negotiations, Ecuadorean President Daniel Noboa said on social media on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ecuador-president-says-new-trade-deal-with-canada-finalized-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7V5HEJX5SNOKLCQMDPCLWIYWV4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 16:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员就运河附近的中国企业向巴拿马施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高外交官马可-卢比奥（Marco Rubio）警告巴拿马立即采取措施，解决美国对在运河附近经营港口的中国企业的担忧，唐纳德-特朗普总统曾说中国企业对美国国家安全构成威胁。【原文：U.S. top diplomat Marco Rubio warned Panama to immediately take steps to address U.S. concerns over Chinese businesses operating ports near the canal, which President Donald Trump has said represent a threat to U.S. national security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/rubio-panama-canal-migration-talks-he-begins-latin-america-trip-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUBW4K5V3ZOB5KDKZGZPEEGWMM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 16:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国肖尔茨谈关税：重要的是不要分裂世界]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收关税后，德国总理奥拉夫-肖尔茨（Olaf Scholz）于周日表示，重要的是不要用新的贸易壁垒来分裂世界，因为每个人都能从全球化中受益。【原文：German Chancellor Olaf Scholz on Sunday said it was important not to divide the world with new trade barriers, as everyone benefits from globalisation, after U.S. President Donald Trump imposed tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/germanys-scholz-tariffs-important-not-divide-world-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F6KY2UV67RLHLIP6ZVISMFULLQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 16:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，美国证券交易委员会共和党领导的委员会加强了对调查的监督]]></title><description><![CDATA[这一变化发生在唐纳德-特朗普上台后美国证券交易委员会新领导层的领导下，尚未对外公布。【原文：The change happened under new leadership at the SEC since Donald Trump took office and has not been made public.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/secs-republican-led-commission-tightens-oversight-probes-sources-say-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N4TROP4DZRIEPAGHTMZZNRRO2E</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 12:06:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税后，大众汽车指望通过谈判避免贸易冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令对来自墨西哥、加拿大和中国的商品征收关税后，欧洲最大的汽车制造商大众汽车公司周日表示，希望通过谈判避免贸易冲突。【原文：Volkswagen is counting on talks to avoid trade conflict, Europe's biggest carmaker said on Sunday, after U.S. President Donald Trump ordered tariffs on goods from Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-counts-talks-avoid-trade-conflict-after-trump-tariffs-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BORIBBQVV5L57B3UTR6U7H2CN4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 11:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[保时捷开始就终止首席财务官和销售主管合同进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国豪华汽车制造商保时捷在周六晚些时候发表声明称，该公司的监事会已开始商讨提前结束财务总监鲁茨-梅施克（Lutz Meschke）和销售主管德特勒夫-冯-普拉滕（Detlev von Platen）的合同，因为该公司正努力提高盈利，但在中国的销售疲软。【原文：Porsche's supervisory board has started talks to end finance chief Lutz Meschke's and sales executive Detlev von Platen's contracts early, the German luxury carmaker said in a statement late on Saturday, as it struggles to boost flagging earnings and weak sales in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/porsche-starts-talks-end-cfo-sales-chief-contracts-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WLHCBW3QOVJUJBQG7MX4VE6QEI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 10:45:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWork 印度特许经营商申请在孟买上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国共享办公空间管理公司 WeWork 的印度特许经营商已在孟买申请首次公开募股，该公司提交的文件草案显示了这一点。【原文：The Indian franchisee of U.S. shared office space manager WeWork has filed for an initial public offering in Mumbai, draft papers filed by the company showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/weworks-india-franchisee-files-mumbai-ipo-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BWRCWXZQJJPZGR5EJSGAYLLGE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:46:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[续集帮助克服经济低迷，中国票房创下收入纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[春节假期期间，中国电影票房收入创下历史新高，因为在经济增长相对疲软的时期，其他类型的消费受到影响，而中国热门影片的续集却吸引了众多影院观众。【原文：China's movie box office took in record revenue during the Lunar New Year holiday, as sequels to popular Chinese hits drew theatregoers at a time when other types of spending have suffered during a period of relatively sluggish economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-box-office-sets-revenue-record-sequels-help-overcome-economic-malaise-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TGLGVJUFMJNSHEP22DEK3X56RA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 09:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度预算选择经济糖衣炮弹而非改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度今年公布的年度财政预算比往年更为重要：作为印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪第三个任期内的第一份全面预算，它将为这个世界第五大经济体如何应对增长放缓和市场下滑定下基调。【原文：India's annual budget announcement was a bigger deal than usual this year: As the first full budget of Prime Minister Narendra Modi's third term, it will set the tone for how the world's fifth-largest economy confronts slowing growth and sagging markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-budget-opts-economic-sugar-rush-over-reform-2025-02-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYAMPGOG2ZJNJPLMXIRD5SQBKQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>