<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-USnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:41:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-US]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 06:41:10 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家航空航天局发射 SPHEREx 望远镜，研究宇宙起源]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，美国国家航空航天局（NASA）的一架望远镜从加利福尼亚发射升空，执行探索宇宙起源的任务，并在银河系中寻找隐藏的水源，水是生命的关键成分。【原文：A NASA telescope was launched into space from California on Tuesday for a mission to explore the origins of the universe and to scour the Milky Way galaxy for hidden reservoirs of water, a key ingredient for life.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/science/nasa-spherex-telescope-is-launched-study-universes-origins-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X77YHMKEKJPPJJEORQA4VKJ5ZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普就变性运动员引发争论后，美国农业部暂停对缅因州大学的资助]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）因缅因州拒绝禁止变性运动员参加女子运动项目而与州长珍妮特-米尔斯（Janet Mills）发生冲突后，缅因大学周二表示，美国农业部已暂停对该校研究和项目的资助。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture has suspended funding for research and programs at the University of Maine, the school said on Tuesday, after President Donald Trump clashed with Governor Janet Mills over the state's refusal to ban transgender athletes from girls' sports.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-suspends-maine-university-funding-after-trump-row-over-transgender-athletes-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2WFVIFTVKNOFTG2XIOFVIKQSZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 弗吉尼亚州州长称美国必须发展核聚变，否则将在能源方面落后于中国]]></title><description><![CDATA[弗吉尼亚州州长格伦-扬金（Glenn Youngkin）周二在休斯敦举行的CERAWeek能源会议上说，美国必须加快聚变能源的开发，否则就有可能在能源主导地位上落后于中国。【原文：The United States must expedite its development of fusion energy or risk falling behind China on energy dominance, said Virginia Governor Glenn Youngkin at the CERAWeek energy conference in Houston on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-virginia-governor-say-us-must-develop-fusion-or-fall-behind-china-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEVPXFQDRRI3XDL6TGUYDGO2DE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 01:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，特朗普政府正考虑削减司法部公共腐败部门的编制]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府正在考虑裁减美国司法部处理公共腐败案件部门的大部分律师。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration is considering cutting most of the lawyers in the U.S. Justice Department unit that handles public corruption cases, four people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-eyes-cuts-justice-department-public-corruption-unit-people-2025-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOESDS7CVFLHZFCJJMS76BGROI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议院确认特朗普的司法部反垄断主管盖尔-斯莱特的任命]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，唐纳德-特朗普总统任命的美国司法部反垄断部门主管盖尔-斯莱特（Gail Slater）获得了美国参议院的确认。【原文：Gail Slater, President Donald Trump's pick to oversee the U.S. Department of Justice's antitrust division, was confirmed by the U.S. Senate on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-confirms-trumps-justice-department-antitrust-head-gail-slater-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FEAILVXNBPNRELZKOVRXIR23Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[证人称特朗普政府仍计划撤销消费者金融局]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周二提供的证人证词，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府仍计划解雇美国消费者金融保护局的所有工作人员，从而有效地使其中立化。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration still plans to fire all workers at the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, effectively neutralizing it, according to witness testimony delivered Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-administration-still-plans-eliminate-consumer-finance-bureau-witness-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O5GWTHC23NPOJNUUQ2SPCV4S7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:50:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[肯尼迪要求美国食品公司去除人工染料]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封电子邮件称，美国卫生部长小罗伯特-肯尼迪在周一的一次会议上告诉包括百事可乐和卡夫亨氏在内的食品公司，特朗普政府希望在肯尼迪卸任前食品供应中不再使用人工染料。【原文：U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. told food companies including PepsiCo and Kraft Heinz in a meeting on Monday that the Trump administration wants artificial dyes out of the food supply before Kennedy leaves office, according to an email seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kennedy-tells-us-food-companies-remove-artificial-dyes-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LNOS6QNXRO7HCIMORHGXP5FAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院通过法案避免政府关门]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党控制的美国众议院周二以 217 票对 213 票的表决结果通过了一项立法，该立法将避免政府在周末关门。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives on Tuesday passed legislation, by a vote of 217-213, that would avert a weekend government shutdown.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-passes-bill-avert-government-shutdown-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZLOK4TDWBOWRID2HU5PWJI454</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[众议院共和党人阻止国会挑战特朗普关税的能力]]></title><description><![CDATA[由共和党控制的美国众议院周二投票决定，阻止国会迅速对唐纳德-特朗普总统征收的关税提出质疑。【原文：The Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives voted on Tuesday to block the ability of Congress to quickly challenge tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump that have rattled financial markets.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/house-republicans-block-congress-ability-challenge-trump-tariffs-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSHWXLWUKBLZDO5OY6GJ3EX5LQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在弹劾法官的 "令人担忧 "的呼声中，美国司法机构发出威胁警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦司法机构的主要成员周二警告说，针对他们同事的威胁数量正在上升，并称因法官的裁决而弹劾他们的呼声 "令人担忧"，因为一些共和党立法者正在推动罢免那些阻挠美国总统唐纳德-特朗普政策的法学家。【原文：Key members of the U.S. federal judiciary warned on Tuesday of a rising number of threats directed at their colleagues and described calls to impeach judges over their rulings "concerning" as some Republican lawmakers push to remove jurists who have blocked U.S. President Donald Trump's policies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judiciary-warns-threats-amid-concerning-calls-impeach-judges-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4ILOAGDIXRN25ERYVZFVB3WURU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法庭文件称，美国国际开发署员工被命令销毁记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[据政府雇员工会周二向法院提交的一份文件显示，美国国际开发署的一名官员已命令雇员销毁大量记录，要求法官阻止这一举动。【原文：An official at the U.S. Agency for International Development has ordered employees to shred a large volume of records, according to a court filing on Tuesday by government employee unions asking a judge to block the move.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usaid-employees-ordered-shred-records-court-filing-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMRBOOHQV5KHNJEEZSXACTPRFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:14:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国交通部称 Verizon 在 24 亿美元 FAA 合同上 "进展不够快]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）表示，Verizon 在与联邦航空管理局签订的为期 15 年、价值 24 亿美元的电信合同方面 "进展不够快"。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said Verizon is "not moving fast enough" in its $2.4 billion 15-year telecom contract with the Federal Aviation Administration.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/usdot-says-verizon-not-moving-fast-enough-24-billion-faa-contract-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKPX3LRG65P5PHR43GETTWCSLQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:56:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国审判中，枪手承认试图杀害伊朗记者]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名自称是俄罗斯有组织犯罪集团成员的人周二说，他曾试图杀害一名伊朗裔美国女记者和活动家，他是在美国对两名同伙的审判中作证时承认这一点的。【原文：A self-professed member of a Russian organized crime group said on Tuesday he once tried to kill an Iranian-American female journalist and activist, making the admission in testimony at a U.S. trial of two associates.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/us-trial-gunman-admits-trying-kill-iranian-journalist-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3ALZ4IPNFPPXESNDRH3RDOOWE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:50:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部称将在周三截止日期前恢复被解雇的试用期员工的工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一份机构声明，美国农业部将遵守联邦委员会周三发布的最后期限，暂时恢复被解雇的试用期员工的工作。【原文：The U.S. Department of Agriculture will comply with the Wednesday deadline issued by a federal board to temporarily reinstate its fired probationary employees, according to an agency statement.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/usda-says-it-will-reinstate-fired-probationary-workers-by-wednesday-deadline-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5666WZYFKVIQVIU52BYJYP3IOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:41:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，美国教育部预计将裁员近一半]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位 Semafor 记者周二在 X 上表示，美国教育部预计将裁减近一半的员工。【原文：Nearly half of the U.S. Department of Education workforce is expected to be eliminated, a Semafor reporter said on X on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/nearly-half-us-education-dept-workforce-expected-be-cut-semafor-reports-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SQS6W2NISVP2RL6DPYAK7GNNYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:33:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会发布通知，撤销工作人员启动正式调查的权力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）本周表示，该机构已决定正式撤销执法人员在未经委员会批准的情况下正式启动调查的授权。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has decided to formally revoke enforcement staff's authorization to formally launch investigations without the commission's approval, the agency said this week.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/us-sec-revokes-staffs-authority-launch-formal-probes-notice-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQ4P4PCZWVMQNJJRQNWSMAJJVI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NTSB 主席将在 3 月 27 日的致命空难听证会上作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会主席珍妮弗-霍门迪（Jennifer Homendy）将在 3 月 27 日参议院商业听证会上就一架陆军黑鹰直升机与美国航空公司支线喷气机空中相撞造成 67 人死亡一事作证。【原文：National Transportation Safety Board Chair Jennifer Homendy will testify at a March 27 Senate Commerce hearing on the mid-air collision of an Army Black Hawk helicopter and American Airlines regional jet that killed 67 people, the panel said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ntsb-chair-testify-march-27-hearing-fatal-air-collision-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBGQWFKZJVJCHI2J42MRZNOVRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国各机构在特朗普规定的裁员截止日期前为员工提供新的买断福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）要求政府机构在本周四的最后期限前提交第二轮大规模裁员计划，多个政府机构正求助于提前退休计划来裁减人员。【原文：Multiple government agencies are turning to early retirement programs to reduce headcount as they scramble to meet President Donald Trump's Thursday deadline for them to submit plans for a second round of mass layoffs.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-agencies-offer-staff-new-buyouts-ahead-trumps-layoff-deadline-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OM3TTKSZNIB3OYVBT7PORI3PM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:56:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普行政令针对的律师事务所起诉政府]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国律师事务所珀金斯柯伊（Perkins Coie）在联邦法院起诉唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府，声称特朗普非法报复该事务所，因为该事务所之前曾为他的前竞选对手、民主党人希拉里-克林顿（Hillary Clinton）工作，而且该事务所的内部政策提倡多元化和包容性。【原文：U.S. law firm Perkins Coie has sued President Donald Trump’s administration in federal court, claiming Trump illegally retaliated against the firm over its prior work for his former opponent, Democrat Hillary Clinton, and its internal policies promoting diversity and inclusion.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/law-firm-targeted-by-trump-executive-order-sues-administration-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GP3AJBZAZKVVGEU7CCEOFAHIA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普提名肖恩-普兰基领导网络机构 CISA]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据国会网站上的通知，唐纳德-特朗普总统已提名肖恩-普兰基（Sean Plankey）担任网络安全和基础设施安全局局长。【原文：President Donald Trump has nominated Sean Plankey to serve as the chief of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency, according to a notice on Congress' website.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/donald-trump-nominates-sean-plankey-head-cyber-agency-cisa-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDXEVTMC6RMJXKVZ2OZK5NPF7M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:43:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将把针对特斯拉经销商的暴力行为称为国内恐怖主义]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，他将把针对特斯拉经销商的暴力行为称为国内恐怖主义，他与特斯拉首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）一起出席了活动，在最近的 "特斯拉拆迁 "抗议活动和该公司股价下滑之际表示支持。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Tuesday he will label violence against Tesla dealerships domestic terrorism as he appeared with Tesla CEO Elon Musk to show support amid recent "Tesla Takedown" protests and the slump in the company's stock price.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-label-violence-against-tesla-dealers-domestic-terrorism-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOJJ6KWJBZIH3OZRXPS4HNTGVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:28:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国喷气式飞机与直升机相撞后，NTSB 紧急提出安全建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封信称，美国国家运输安全委员会将于周二宣布，它将提出一项紧急安全建议，防止在华盛顿里根国家机场使用两条跑道时进行直升机作业。【原文：The National Transportation Safety Board will announce on Tuesday it is making an urgent safety recommendation to prevent helicopter operations when two runways are being used at Washington Reagan National Airport following a mid-air collision in January that killed 67 people, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/us/ntsb-making-urgent-safety-recommendations-after-american-jet-collision-with-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOPSV5X3ZFMDLKMAJAFAN3IYRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[犹他州有望成为首个禁止在公共供水系统中使用氟化物的州]]></title><description><![CDATA[在犹他州州长斯宾塞-考克斯（Spencer Cox）表示将签署相关立法后，犹他州将成为美国第一个禁止在公共供水系统中使用氟化物的州。【原文：Utah is set to become the first U.S. state to ban the use of fluoride in public water systems after Utah Governor Spencer Cox said he would sign legislation to that effect.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/utah-poised-become-first-state-ban-fluoride-public-water-system-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KUABFICQBZJSTC5E7WESQTZUEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 分析 美国电力需求激增之际小型核电举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[从美国能源部长到大型科技公司，每个人都将小型模块化核反应堆作为应对蓬勃发展的电力需求的潜在方案，但由于成本和监管障碍，该技术正努力实现商业化。【原文：Everyone from the U.S. energy secretary to Big Tech touts small modular nuclear reactors as a potential answer to booming power demand, but the technology is struggling to become commercial due to costs and regulatory hurdles.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-analysis-small-nuclear-power-struggles-cusp-us-electricity-demand-boom-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FQACXBZRO5I6NDUDT7TFFXTSAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚大学巴勒斯坦裔学生抗议者向美国联邦法院提出逮捕异议]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于一名被捕的巴勒斯坦活动人士和哥伦比亚大学学生的法律之争已成为特朗普政府移民政策的导火索，将在联邦法院展开，美国政府将于周二就此案的下一步行动提出建议。【原文：A legal battle over an arrested Palestinian activist and Columbia University student that has become a flashpoint of the Trump administration’s immigration policy will play out in federal court, with the U.S. government set to propose the next steps in the case on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/palestinian-columbia-student-protestors-challenge-arrest-turns-us-federal-court-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XGFNY4GSWRPIVOYNTUNDKMHG3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[州卫生局称，得克萨斯州麻疹病例比 3 月 7 日增加 25 例]]></title><description><![CDATA[德克萨斯州卫生部门周二报告了该州 223 例麻疹病例，比 3 月 7 日增加了 25 例，而在此之前近两周，一名未接种疫苗的儿童死于麻疹，这是美国十年来爆发的最大规模的麻疹疫情之一。【原文：The Texas health department reported 223 measles cases in the state on Tuesday, an increase of 25 cases from March 7, nearly two weeks after an unvaccinated child died of the disease amid one of the largest outbreaks the U.S. has witnessed in a decade.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/measles-cases-rise-223-texas-state-health-department-says-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS7R7TG3YZI7LC6N23NLA3R5EA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:18:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱德华-蒙克肖像在伦敦新展中展出]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，一场新的爱德华-蒙克肖像画展在伦敦拉开帷幕，展示了这位挪威画家作品和生活的一个重要方面。【原文：A new exhibition of portraits by Edvard Munch opens in London this week, shining a light on an important aspect of the Norwegian painter's work and his life.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/lifestyle/portraits-by-edvard-munch-go-show-new-london-exhibition-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HOG6TPKSAJKKFFZHW77RECZSOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称将对加拿大金属征收的关税加倍至 50]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二将他计划对所有从加拿大进入美国的钢铁和铝产品征收的关税提高了一倍，使关税总额达到 50%，以回应安大略省对进入美国的电力征收 25% 的关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Tuesday doubled his planned tariff on all steel and aluminum products coming into the United States from Canada, bringing the total to 50%, in response to the province of Ontario placing a 25% tariff on electricity coming into the U.S.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-says-he-will-raise-tariffs-canada-metals-50-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ONVWMUI5RNCXEIIGNJPI3E4SU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 1 月份职位空缺增加；裁员人数下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 1 月份的职位空缺有所增加，但由于人们担心进口关税的不确定性和政府积极削减开支可能会导致经济活动急剧放缓，未来几个月的劳动力需求可能会走软。【原文：U.S. job openings increased in January, but demand for labor is likely to soften in the months ahead amid concerns that uncertainty over import tariffs and aggressive government spending cuts could cause a sharp slowdown in economic activity.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-increase-january-layoffs-decline-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERZUABQTINP4BG233FOQ4MY6N4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[女童子军因饼干中含有重金属和杀虫剂被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[女童子军被消费者起诉，指控其广受欢迎的薄荷糖和其他饼干中含有 "重金属 "和杀虫剂。【原文：The Girl Scouts have been sued by consumers over the alleged presence of "heavy metals" and pesticides in its popular Thin Mints and other cookies.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/legal/girl-scouts-sued-over-alleged-heavy-metals-pesticides-cookies-2025-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJBEVV5R7FOFLOI6OJJQJAKCWY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:48:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>