<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[空中交通管制人员连续第二天受到影响，导致航班延误]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）周二在一份通知中说，随着政府部分停摆进入第七天，空中交通管制人员问题已连续第二天影响到美国众多机场的航班。【原文：Air traffic control staffing issues are impacting flights for a second straight day at numerous U.S. airports as the partial government shutdown reaches its seventh day, the Federal Aviation Administration said in a notice on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/air-traffic-control-staffing-hit-second-day-delaying-flights-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWQEV44VFVLAVCO4EOICOSR4EE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:25:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织强调主权债务重组的进展和复杂性]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织在周二发表的一份文件中说，围绕私营部门拥有的主权债务的法律框架已被证明在很大程度上是有效的，特别是在债券债务方面，但在贷款和抵押债务方面仍存在差距，而且重组变得更加漫长和复杂。【原文：The legal framework surrounding private-sector-owned sovereign debt has proven largely effective, especially for bonded debt, but gaps remain for loans and collateralized debt and restructurings have become longer and more complex, the International Monetary Fund said in a paper published on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/imf-highlights-advances-complexities-sovereign-debt-restructuring-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE7H7DEW7JPWBCFEWSSGCCRHL4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉廉价车型与其他电动汽车的比较]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周二推出了更经济实惠的畅销车型Model Y SUV和Model 3轿车，售价分别为39,990美元和36,990美元。【原文：Tesla unveiled more affordable versions of its best-selling Model Y SUV and Model 3 sedan on Tuesday at $39,990 and $36,990, respectively, as the electric-vehicle maker seeks to reverse falling sales and waning market share amid rising competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/how-teslas-cheaper-models-compare-with-other-electric-vehicles-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZ3MPLGJ4ZPWXG63XJOHE7LZ64</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《巴西日报》报道，America Movil 旗下的 Claro 就收购 Desktop 进行了深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据新闻媒体《巴西日报》周二援引两位消息人士的话报道，墨西哥美国移动公司（America Movil）旗下的电信运营商克拉罗公司（Claro）正在就收购巴西互联网服务提供商 Desktop 进行深入谈判。【原文：Telecom operator Claro, owned by Mexico's America Movil , is in advanced talks to buy Brazilian internet provider Desktop , news outlet Brazil Journal reported on Tuesday, citing two sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/america-movils-claro-advanced-talks-buy-desktop-brazil-journal-reports-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OW4WCLEYERLUTBJL3ITMBCNEV4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 19:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田探索用于越野车的小型无人机系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车周二表示，公司正在探索开发一种小型无人机系统，主要用于支持车辆在未铺设路面的道路和小径上行驶。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Tuesday it is exploring the development of a small drone system primarily to support vehicle operations on unpaved roads and trails.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-exploring-small-drone-system-off-road-vehicle-use-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2MGFCJCOEJPCFMGBMGJKPZ234U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 19:37:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前 FDA 疫苗主管彼得-马克斯加盟礼来公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二报道，今年早些时候被美国食品和药物管理局赶下台的前疫苗监管高层彼得-马克斯（Peter Marks）已加盟礼来制药公司（Eli Lilly）。【原文：Peter Marks, the former top vaccine regulator who was ousted from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration earlier this year, has joined Eli Lilly , the drugmaker told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/former-fda-vaccine-chief-peter-marks-joins-eli-lilly-stat-reports-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QJDS2CRUVMW3N5JWP74SYFHGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 19:16:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 对特斯拉推出更便宜的 Model Y 和 Model 3 的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周二推出了更经济实惠的畅销车型Model Y SUV和Model 3轿车，售价分别为39990美元和36990美元。【原文：Tesla unveiled more affordable versions of its best-selling Model Y SUV and its Model 3 sedan on Tuesday at $39,990 and $36,990, respectively, as the electric-vehicle maker seeks to reverse falling sales and waning market share amid rising competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/view-reactions-teslas-launch-cheaper-model-y-model-3-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6QWEP6CYNL45FA2SQP5QZW2LM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 19:09:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国可能撤销为斯泰兰特、通用汽车提供的 11 亿美元汽车工厂资助]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一份文件显示，美国能源部正在考虑撤销总统乔-拜登政府去年向克莱斯勒母公司斯太朗蒂斯和通用汽车公司发放的近 11 亿美元的改造补助金。【原文：The U.S. Energy Department is considering revoking nearly $1.1 billion awarded in retooling grants to Chrysler-parent Stellantis and General Motors last year by the administration of President Joe Biden, according to a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-may-revoke-11-billion-auto-plant-funding-stellantis-gm-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MX3O5F4DHVJUNLF63GZ42BAQY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:50:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国造船船东面临美国港口费和 30 亿美元成本的威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）正努力应对中国在公海上日益增长的主导地位，美国距离对某些与中国有联系的船只征收港口费还有一周的时间，预计此举将使排名前十的承运商明年损失 32 亿美元。【原文：The U.S. is one week away from imposing port fees on certain vessels with links to China, a move expected to cost the top 10 carriers $3.2 billion next year as President Donald Trump seeks to address China's growing dominance on the high seas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-port-fees-3-billion-costs-loom-owners-chinese-built-ships-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSAEPQSKGNO6XNXHVNTYJCEIXM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普政府考虑再削减 120 亿美元清洁能源资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份目标项目清单显示，除了上周宣布的削减之外，美国政府正在考虑取消国会授权的 120 亿美元清洁能源项目资金。【原文：The U.S. government is considering cancelling $12 billion in Congressionally-mandated funding for clean energy projects beyond the cuts announced last week, a list of targeted projects seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/trump-administration-mulls-additional-12-billion-clean-energy-funding-cut-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IXF6RXQTXFMCDOTGZXNEU4SM2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，摩根大通戴蒙支持放宽季度盈利要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二报道，摩根大通首席执行官杰米-戴蒙（Jamie Dimon）表示，他欢迎为放宽美国证券交易委员会季度财报要求而提出的修改建议。【原文：JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said he would welcome proposed changes to ease the US Securities and Exchange Commission's quarterly earnings report requirements, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgans-dimon-backs-easing-quarterly-earnings-requirement-bloomberg-news-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLPVTHOR5BJYTCMBEQJEYCZVHQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:10:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织就 9.6 万亿美元外汇市场的流动性风险向银行和监管机构发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织周二发布的一份报告称，主导 9.6 万亿美元货币市场的金融机构应持有必要的流动性和资本缓冲，并进行强化的压力测试，以防止金融体系出现混乱。【原文：Financial institutions that dominate the $9.6 trillion currency market should hold the necessary liquidity and capital buffers and run enhanced stress tests to prevent disruptions to the financial system, according to an International Monetary Fund report released on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/imf-warns-banks-supervisors-liquidity-risks-96-trillion-fx-market-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOWCHZ5FGZMFRKWE3ZGLTYKTOQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利表示怀疑人工智能是否会取代工人，但可能会推高利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周二表示，虽然他并不认为人工智能会迅速取代美国工人，但对人工智能数据中心的大规模投资往往会推高借贷成本，即使美联储降低短期政策利率也是如此。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari on Tuesday said that while he doesn't believe artificial intelligence will quickly replace U.S. workers, massive investment in AI data centers will tend to drive borrowing costs higher, even if the Fed reduces its short-term policy rate.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-kashkari-says-hes-skeptical-ai-is-replacing-workers-it-may-push-up-rates-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVPEXXJMIVMXVAM25OLYIRGUKI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:31:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席米兰称债券市场平静表明支持降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事斯蒂芬-米兰（Stephen Miran）周二表示，美国债券市场目前的相对平静支持迅速推动降息。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Stephen Miran on Tuesday said that the U.S. bond market’s current relative calm supports a swift push to lower interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/feds-miran-says-calm-bond-market-shows-support-rate-cuts-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUHPZORZFBIWRLDWETULSWCAYE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客 A320 超越波音 737，成为历史上交付量最多的喷气式飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，欧洲空中客车公司打破了一个重要的商业障碍，其 A320 系列飞机超越波音 737，成为历史上交付量最大的喷气式客机。【原文：Europe's Airbus broke a major commercial barrier on Tuesday when its A320 family of planes overtook the Boeing 737 to become the most-delivered jetliner in history.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-a320-flies-past-boeing-737-most-delivered-jet-history-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LYAD7CWAXRJ7VD2UEUJT6SEK7I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:06:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称 2025 年美国天然气产量和需求量将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（U.S. Energy Information Administration）周二在其《短期能源展望》（Short-Term Energy Outlook，STEO）报告中称，2025年美国天然气产量和需求量将双双创下历史新高。【原文：U.S. natural gas output and demand will both rise to record highs in 2025, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said in its Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-natgas-output-demand-hit-record-highs-2025-eia-says-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DWB272XQJBM4TAWPXP77G6OMIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:06:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车制造商宝马下调 2025 年盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝马汽车公司周二表示，由于中国经济增长放缓和美国征收进口关税，该公司已下调了2025年的盈利预期。【原文：BMW has cut its 2025 earnings forecast due to slow growth in China and U.S. import tariffs, the luxury automaker said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/german-automaker-bmw-cuts-2025-earnings-forecast-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H7Q6IKF66BOTTEDLF65NJ2VEHY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 上调美国石油产量预测，警告供应过剩将导致油价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（Energy Information Administration）周二表示，美国今年的石油产量预计将创下比此前预期更大的纪录，该机构同时警告说，石油供应过剩将在未来几个月对油价造成压力。【原文：U.S. oil production is expected to hit a larger record this year than previously expected, the Energy Information Administration said on Tuesday, even as the agency warned that a glut of oil will weigh on prices in the months ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/eia-hikes-us-oil-output-forecast-warns-oversupply-will-slash-prices-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ED2KX7AQJJI3HEID22PRV6VR7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:03:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Business Insider 报道，英伟达将继续赞助 H-1B 签证]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《商业内幕》（Business Insider）周二报道，芯片制造商英伟达公司（Nvidia）首席执行官黄仁勋（Jensen Huang）表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）上月颁布行政命令，对每份新申请征收10万美元费用后，该公司将继续赞助H-1B签证，并承担所有相关费用。【原文：Chipmaker Nvidia's CEO Jensen Huang said that the company will continue to sponsor H-1B visas and cover all associated costs following U.S. President Donald Trump's executive order last month that imposed a $100,000 fee on each new application, Business Insider reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nvidia-ceo-huang-says-chipmaker-will-continue-sponsor-h-1b-visas-business-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6H6RV5KI5PXNEU54WAUJYHVCU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EIA 称，2025 年和 2026 年美国电力使用量将创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（Energy Information Administration）在本周二发布的短期能源展望报告中称，美国的电力消耗量将在2025年和2026年创下历史新高。【原文：U.S. power consumption will hit record highs in 2025 and 2026, the Energy Information Administration said in its short-term energy outlook on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-power-use-reach-record-highs-2025-2026-eia-says-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7PQNVXBMUJMHFG2UYPOA462LZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Commonwealth LNG 希望有更多时间在路易斯安那州建造计划中的出口设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份监管文件显示，联邦液化天然气公司（Commonwealth LNG）已要求联邦监管机构将其在路易斯安那州卡梅伦教区拟建出口设施的建设和液化天然气出口期限延长四年。【原文：Commonwealth LNG has asked federal regulators for a four-year extension to construct and begin exporting liquefied natural gas from a proposed export facility in Cameron Parish, Louisiana, a regulatory document shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/commonwealth-lng-wants-more-time-build-planned-export-facility-louisiana-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHAEZPXZ5JLG7AWPIPZGSI4KTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：摩科瑞集团和合作伙伴集团承诺投资美国能源，帮助瑞士降低关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位接近此事的人士称，包括能源贸易商摩科瑞（Mercuria）和私募股权公司伙伴集团（Partners Group）在内的一批瑞士公司已承诺向美国能源投资超过60亿美元，作为降低美国对瑞士关税努力的一部分。【原文：A group of Swiss companies including energy trader Mercuria and private equity firm Partners Group has pledged over $6 billion in U.S. energy investments as part of efforts to lower U.S. tariffs on Switzerland, two people close to the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/mercuria-partners-group-pledge-us-energy-investments-help-lower-swiss-tariffs-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z3ZILHBSEJJEVBMBAISX2EH5LA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥集团退出对 Banamex 的竞购战]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥矿业和运输集团墨西哥集团（Grupo Mexico）周二表示，不会参与花旗银行（Citi）在墨西哥的零售业务部门（即 Banamex）的竞购战，因为该集团的出价已经高于此前接受的竞购价。【原文：Grupo Mexico will not enter a bidding war for Citi's retail unit in the country, known as Banamex, as its offer already places the lender at a higher value than a previously accepted competing bid, the miner and transport conglomerate said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/grupo-mexico-wont-raise-banamex-bid-plans-share-stake-with-local-investors-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQYLVCIRW5LSTL2Y4WWIZUJZLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长拉加德再次呼吁加强欧元的作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周二再次呼吁加强欧元在全球的作用，她认为欧元集团现在是一个无辜的旁观者，承受着华盛顿和其他地方造成的冲击。【原文：European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde renewed her call on Tuesday for a beefed-up global role for the euro currency, arguing that the bloc is now an innocent bystander, suffering shocks created in Washington and elsewhere.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ecbs-lagarde-renews-calls-beefed-up-role-euro-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OF2ECO4SLVIIFKH7O3ABO4DM7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资金矿企业的基金价格屡创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资于金矿企业的共同基金在2025年表现领先，甚至超过了高歌猛进的人工智能和科技基金，因为投资者押注创纪录的金价将推动强劲的利润率、现金流和股东回报。【原文：Mutual funds that invest in gold mining firms are leading 2025 performance, overtaking even high-flying AI and tech funds, as investors bet record gold prices will drive strong margins, cashflows and shareholder returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/funds-investing-gold-miners-bask-record-prices-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LUMTXBMCNVPBVEXHOVR5UWIEAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚咖啡获得数十年来最佳收成，警告 2025/26 年收成将减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚全国咖啡种植者联合会周二表示，受有利的天气条件和作物更新的影响，哥伦比亚结束了三十多年来最好的咖啡年，但预计下一个周期的产量将有所下降。【原文：Colombia closed its best coffee year in more than three decades, boosted by favorable weather conditions and the impact of crop renewal, although production is expected to decline in the upcoming cycle, the National Federation of Coffee Growers said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/colombia-has-best-coffee-harvest-decades-warns-lower-202526-crop-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ITRZMOYZJ5I4ZGYAYOK5OJ3KPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府停摆将推迟公布 2026 年社会保障年度平均工资增幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[数百万美国退休人员和其他社会保障金领取者将不得不等待一段时间才能知道 2026 年他们的支票会有多大，因为政府的部分停摆将推迟公布 9 月份的消费者通胀数据。【原文：Millions of U.S. retirees and other Social Security recipients will have to wait for a while to learn how big their checks will be in 2026 as the ongoing partial government shutdown is set to delay the release of September's consumer inflation data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-government-shutdown-will-delay-social-security-2026-cola-announcement-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CT2AQUSHRNUFA4WOO63L3JU6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:38:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟将钢铁进口配额减半以振兴国内产业]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟委员会周二提议将免关税钢材进口配额削减近一半，并对超额货物征收 50%的关税，以保护欧盟的炼钢业。【原文：The European Commission proposed on Tuesday cutting tariff-free steel import quotas by almost half and a 50% duty for excess shipments in a bid to preserve viable steelmaking in the European Union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/eu-halve-steel-import-quotas-revive-domestic-industry-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P5TKV24GQ5KPNNFGEGWSIHMTKU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络犯罪分子声称日本朝日集团遭到黑客攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，Qilin 声称对日本朝日集团控股公司遭黑客攻击事件负责，该事件中断了这家啤酒和饮料巨头的生产。【原文：Qilin, a ransomware group with a track record of cyberattacks on major entities around the world, claimed responsibility on Tuesday for a hack on Japan’s Asahi Group Holdings , which disrupted production at the beer and beverage giant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/cybercriminals-claim-hack-japans-asahi-group-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ESMIPTIXIBJ5DK6PTS3T54G6P4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[第五第三银行首席执行官称 Comerica 交易将扩大在美国中间市场和增长地区的业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[第五第三银行首席执行官蒂姆-斯彭斯（Tim Spence）周二在接受路透社采访时说，收购地区性银行 Comerica 的讨论始于几周前，当时后者的首席执行官柯蒂斯-法默（Curtis Farmer）打电话来商讨交易事宜。【原文：Fifth Third CEO Tim Spence said discussions to buy regional bank Comerica started a few weeks ago when the latter company's CEO Curtis Farmer called to discuss a deal, Spence told Reuters in an interview on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/fifth-third-ceo-says-comerica-deal-will-expand-presence-us-middle-markets-growth-2025-10-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NX3IA5BPINMYDFSHVJPWNQB5U4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>