<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:39:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:39:22 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Zoho 暂停 7 亿美元芯片制造计划，印度遭遇最新挫折]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士透露，印度软件公司 Zoho 已暂停了长达一年之久的斥资 7 亿美元进军芯片制造的计划，这对印度政府雄心勃勃的半导体计划造成了又一次打击。【原文：Indian software firm Zoho has suspended its year-long pursuit of a $700 million plan to foray into chip manufacturing, sources familiar with the matter said, dealing another blow to the Indian government's ambitious semiconductor plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/zoho-suspends-700-million-chipmaking-plan-latest-setback-india-sources-say-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4TJ6RU6EGNNCRC4SJHRTLEB3XM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税后，英国央行可能发出加快降息的信号]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税令全球经济增长前景暗淡，英国央行预计将于5月8日降息四分之一个百分点，一些经济学家认为英国央行很快就需要加快其渐进式降息的步伐。【原文：The Bank of England is expected to lower interest rates by a quarter point on May 8 as U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs darken the global growth outlook, and some economists think the BoE will soon need to speed up its gradual approach to rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-england-could-signal-faster-rate-cuts-after-trump-tariffs-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2S4X2IG2PRN7NB7EEK2CLKVYOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴菲特家居服务公司新任首席执行官称买家和卖家都能应对关税和变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）旗下 HomeServices of America 的新任首席执行官表示，对关税对抵押贷款利率影响的担忧正在拖累房屋买家和卖家，但不太可能显著影响现有房屋的销售。【原文：The new chief executive of Berkshire Hathaway's HomeServices of America said worries about the impact of tariffs on mortgage rates are weighing on home buyers and sellers, but were unlikely to significantly dent sales of existing homes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/new-ceo-buffetts-homeservices-says-buyers-sellers-can-handle-tariffs-changes-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6ROBVG4VNFPHXCAHKSIZ4P4K3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MSCI 表示，特朗普的不确定性使欧洲房地产复苏偏离正轨]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利资本国际公司（MSCI）的数据显示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普第二个任期的最初几个月里，全球经济的不确定性破坏了欧洲房地产市场刚刚开始的复苏，导致交易量在去年的良好势头之后出现萎缩。【原文：A nascent recovery in Europe's real estate market has been derailed by global economic uncertainty in the early months of U.S. President Donald Trump's second term, leading deal volumes to shrink after a positive run last year, MSCI data shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/european-real-estate-recovery-thrown-off-course-by-trump-uncertainty-says-msci-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4AAZQBNRMBPUHGB3Q74LNSOIJM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:19:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合利华将关闭 REN 护肤品业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合利华（Unilever）周四表示，正在采取措施关闭其护肤品业务 REN，理由是内部挑战因市场条件而变得更加严重，"导致该品牌无法长期保持成功"。【原文：Unilever on Thursday said that it was taking steps to close its skincare business REN, citing internal challenges that were made worse by market conditions and "left the brand unable to sustain success in the long term."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/unilever-shut-down-ren-skincare-business-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXTKBKMUYFKDJHOL3N7T2A75PA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能助力云计算，消费电子产品受关税冲击，大科技公司命运各异]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着人工智能需求推动云计算和数字广告的增长，同时消费电子产品受到唐纳德-特朗普总统全球贸易战的冲击，大科技公司的命运在迅速变化的商业环境中出现分化。【原文：The fortunes of Big Tech are diverging in a rapidly changing business landscape, as demand for artificial intelligence fuels growth in cloud and digital ads while consumer electronics take a battering from President Donald Trump's global trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/big-techs-fortunes-diverge-ai-powers-cloud-tariffs-hit-consumer-electronics-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJPF2UTNW5MLLBNV4RBM5PZLLA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅诗兰黛预计全年销售额降幅大于预期，原因是需求放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[化妆品巨头雅诗兰黛周四预计，2025财年销售额的降幅将超过预期，这表明美国市场的增长放缓，而关键的中国地区的需求复苏之路将更加漫长。【原文：Cosmetics giant Estee Lauder forecast a bigger-than-expected drop in fiscal 2025 sales on Thursday, signaling slowdown in the American market and a longer road to recovery for demand in key China region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/estee-lauder-posts-smaller-than-expected-drop-quarterly-sales-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHCCCYAZ6NPM5IM6TWRDELC2SA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:10:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴菲特执掌伯克希尔 60 周年，伯克希尔跑赢大盘]]></title><description><![CDATA[伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）在股市动荡的一年中表现良好，本周末股东们将从沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）那里得到保证，在关税动荡扰乱美国企业的情况下，他们仍能安然无恙。【原文：Berkshire Hathaway has held up well in a rocky year for stocks, and shareholders this weekend will be seeking reassurance from Warren Buffett that they remain in good hands as tariff turmoil disrupts corporate America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/berkshire-outguns-market-buffett-reaches-60-years-charge-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BS7GF7TANFMKFHQLDNSJZAYVZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察力：五角大楼人工智能金属项目私有化，旨在促进西方供应交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个由美国政府创建的旨在预测关键矿物供应和价格的人工智能项目已被移交给一个非营利组织控制，该组织正在帮助矿工和制造商达成供应交易。【原文：A U.S. government-created artificial intelligence program that aims to predict the supply and price of critical minerals has been transferred to the control of a non-profit organization that is helping miners and manufacturers strike supply deals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pentagons-ai-metals-program-goes-private-bid-boost-western-supply-deals-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXF7WZXI3VNMBIONYOM4KQBOAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃伦-巴菲特与伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司概览]]></title><description><![CDATA[数万人将来到内布拉斯加州奥马哈，参加亿万富翁沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）一年一度的股东周末活动。【原文：Tens of thousands of people will descend on Omaha, Nebraska, to attend the annual shareholder weekend for billionaire Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/warren-buffett-berkshire-hathaway-glance-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAXWCBGKSFM6FLU2M5WWJ4RL7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，花旗集团聘用前美国贸易代表罗伯特-莱特希泽]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，花旗集团已聘请前美国贸易代表罗伯特-莱特希泽（Robert Lighthizer）担任全球贸易高级顾问。【原文：Citigroup has hired former U.S. Trade Representative Robert Lighthizer as a senior adviser on global trade, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-hires-former-us-trade-representative-robert-lighthizer-wsj-reports-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3VKNNKPRXVL7DBZGI3RLSJVCBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称，美国已委托 L3Harris 在年底前准备好临时总统专机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国政府已委托国防承包商 L3Harris Technologies 对卡塔尔政府以前使用的一架波音 747 进行大修，以用作临时空军一号。【原文：The U.S. government has commissioned defense contractor L3Harris Technologies to overhaul a Boeing 747 formerly used by the Qatari government to use as an interim Air Force One, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-tasked-l3harris-ready-interim-presidential-plane-by-year-end-wsj-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22CGJHI3PVIRLGRUVAM4YJQAOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:58:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，埃隆-马斯克称，DOGE 应审查美联储的成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四报道，亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）正在考虑向美联储派遣他的政府效率团队，并以美联储华盛顿总部耗资巨大的翻修工程为例，说明政府可能存在浪费现象。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk is considering sending his government efficiency team to the Federal Reserve, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing a costly renovation of the central bank's Washington DC headquarters as an example of potential government waste.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/elon-musk-says-doge-should-examine-federal-reserve-costs-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INTE54DM7ZMJTOLQ753KIUNMRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股指期货反弹，微软和 Meta 在业绩公布后跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国股指期货周四跳涨，原因是微软和 Meta Platforms 的股价大涨，这两家 "华丽七巨头 "的强劲季度业绩表明科技行业的前景依然强劲。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped on Thursday as shares of Microsoft and Meta Platforms surged after strong quarterly results from both the Magnificent Seven heavyweights pointed to a still-strong outlook for the technology sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-index-futures-bounce-microsoft-meta-jump-after-results-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQ53KHEQX5NCJEVDB2LB4M7I7Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[私募股权公司 CVC 将投资《皇家比赛》开发商 Dream Games]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲私募股权公司 CVC 周四表示，将投资 Dream Games，这家以《Royal Match》和《Royal Kingdom》闻名的手机游戏开发商。【原文：European private equity firm CVC will invest in Dream Games, the mobile games developer known for "Royal Match" and "Royal Kingdom" said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/private-equity-cvc-invest-royal-match-developer-dream-games-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GCEW7FMLMRMTVKMKCDGONM6KOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:38:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 WiseTech 公司披露在美国云计算公司 E2open 战略审查中扮演的角色]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚顶级软件企业之一 WiseTech Global 周四表示，它将参与云计算公司 E2open Parent Holdings 之前宣布的战略审查。【原文：WiseTech Global , one of Australia's top software businesses, on Thursday said it was participating in a strategic review previously announced by cloud computing firm E2open Parent Holdings .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-wisetech-discloses-role-us-cloud-firm-e2opens-strategic-review-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D5XAGTEBGRP6DHDGTJKQ2SZNUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WLF 的 Zach Witkoff：1 美元被选为 MGX 在 Binance 投资的官方稳定币]]></title><description><![CDATA[World Liberty 联合创始人 Zach Witkoff 周四表示，1 美元已被选为阿布扎比支持的投资机构 MGX 投资 Binance 的官方稳定币。【原文：USD1 has been selected as official stablecoin for Abu Dhabi backed investment vehicle MGX's investment in Binance, Zach Witkoff, World Liberty's co-founder said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/wlfs-zach-witkoff-usd1-selected-official-stablecoin-mgx-investment-binance-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YEMB5EI7PZKLNMMJPEFFQD2KVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税，日本贸易公司对利润预测持保守态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税威胁全球供应链并增加经济不确定性，日本贸易公司三井物产株式会社、住友商事株式会社和双日株式会社周四发布了谨慎的本财年利润预测。【原文：Japanese trading houses Mitsui & Co , Sumitomo Corp and Sojitz on Thursday issued cautious profit forecasts for the current fiscal year as U.S. tariffs threaten global supply chains and increase economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japanese-trading-houses-conservative-profit-forecasts-amid-us-tariffs-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTZN5KKT2FNK7GEQLNQJXSBMXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:28:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行加剧经济增长阴霾，股市停滞不前，日元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国经济萎缩后，周四全球股市昏昏沉沉，尽管华尔街指日可待，美元也因日本央行下调经济增长预期而走高，日本央行下调经济增长预期的原因被归咎于美国贸易关税，日元因此走低。【原文：World stocks were groggy on Thursday after a contraction in the U.S. economy, although Wall Street was pointing higher and the dollar sprang up as a Bank of Japan growth forecast cut blamed on U.S. trade tariffs yanked the yen lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHYIX2YZJJO75LIRWXEP3YAKYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞安航空公司威胁称，如果关税影响价格，将寻求波音订单的替代品]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞安航空首席执行官迈克尔-奥利里（Michael O'Leary）周四在一封信中表示，如果美国关税对其向波音公司订购的飞机价格造成实质性影响，瑞安航空将寻找其他飞机供应商。【原文：Ryanair would look for an alternative aircraft supplier if U.S. tariffs materially affect the price of planes it has ordered from Boeing , chief executive Michael O'Leary said in a letter on Thursday, adding that he would consider Chinese planemaker COMAC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ryanair-threatens-seek-alternative-boeing-order-if-tariffs-impact-price-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VE37ZPFXXRN7DEBGL47ZQJE4DI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:55:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国制造业采购经理人指数（PMI）显示，美国关税担忧打击了英国 4 月份的工厂出口]]></title><description><![CDATA[一项调查显示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的贸易战和英国增税对雇主产生了影响，4月份英国工厂出口出现了近五年来最大幅度的萎缩，成本压力加剧。【原文：British factory exports shrank at their sharpest pace in almost five years and cost pressures intensified in April, according to a survey that showed the impact of U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war and a UK tax hike for employers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/us-tariff-fears-hit-uk-factory-exports-april-pmi-shows-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HX6235ZL7BPHHK4BKC2RIIPGHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:38:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝业公司称第二季度订单强劲，尽管有关税，但仍在评估西班牙电力风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[铝生产商美国铝业公司（Alcoa）周四表示，其第二季度的订单量依然强劲，尚未出现与美国关税有关的订单下降，同时还指出，本周西班牙的停电事故给其在西班牙的业务带来了风险。【原文：Aluminium producer Alcoa said on Thursday its order book for the second quarter remains robust and it has yet to see a drop in orders related to U.S. tariffs, while also noting that this week's power outage in Spain posed risks to its business there.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/alcoa-says-q2-order-book-strong-despite-tariffs-assessing-spain-power-risks-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XOSTV57IOVN7DHNZYE5G52GQ5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元持续承压，亚洲外汇多头势头强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，由于对唐纳德-特朗普总统领导下的美国贸易政策的担忧继续削弱美元，投资者加大了对大多数亚洲货币的看涨押注。【原文：Investors ramped up their bullish bets on most Asian currencies, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday, as worries about U.S. trade policies under President Donald Trump continued to weaken the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/asian-fx-bulls-gain-momentum-dollar-stays-under-pressure-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SX26JCZYPJK6HINT7WWG2JXNNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约银行沙特地区总部获批，全球银行业务量增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约梅隆银行（Bank of New York Mellon）周四表示，该行已获得在沙特阿拉伯设立地区总部的许可。【原文：Bank of New York Mellon has received a licence to set up a regional headquarters in Saudi Arabia, it said on Thursday, joining others lured by incentives as the kingdom seeks to boost its appeal as a financial hub.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bny-gets-licence-saudi-regional-hq-global-banks-grow-presence-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZDMF5SHSJJHTP2EJXF4L5SLSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:05:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[力拓称 19.35% 的股东投票支持双重上市审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓（Rio Tinto）周四表示，19.35% 的股东投票支持对公司的双重上市结构进行审查。【原文：Rio Tinto , said on Thursday that 19.35% of its shareholders had voted for a review of the company's dual-listed structure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/rio-tinto-says-1935-shareholders-voted-dual-listing-review-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2UVEW3J46ZN57P62Q3IEOGJDCU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰的关键矿产有哪些，我们对与美国的交易了解多少？]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰和美国周三签署了一项由美国总统唐纳德-特朗普大力推动的协议，美国将以优惠条件获得乌克兰新的矿产交易，并为乌克兰的重建提供投资资金。【原文：Ukraine and the United States on Wednesday signed a deal heavily promoted by U.S. President Donald Trump that will give the United States preferential access to new Ukrainian minerals deals and fund investment in Ukraine's reconstruction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/what-are-ukraines-critical-minerals-what-do-we-know-about-deal-with-us-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJOXWCB6Q5MNXHMR7FRBTAPFSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:50:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田在新闻发布会上的讲话]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国关税的不确定性给世界第四大经济体的前景蒙上了阴影，日本央行周四维持利率稳定并下调了经济增长预期。【原文：The Bank of Japan kept interest rates steady and cut its growth forecasts on Thursday, as uncertainty surrounding U.S. tariffs clouds the outlook for the world's fourth-largest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/boj-governor-uedas-comments-news-conference-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3BFICA2I6VJG5FIV2AOL4VYMWA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管关税存在不确定性，英国劳斯莱斯仍对目标充满信心]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国工程公司罗尔斯-罗伊斯（Rolls-Royce）表示，尽管全球关税上涨带来了不确定性，但该公司仍有信心实现 2025 年的利润指导目标。【原文：British engineering company Rolls-Royce said it was confident of meeting 2025 profit guidance despite the uncertainty caused by global tariff rises.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/uks-rolls-royce-confident-targets-despite-tariff-uncertainty-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TXY7O2SUORLIZKB65V24T7J4AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中央人民广播电台称，美国关税将使荷兰经济增长减少一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰经济政策顾问 CPB 周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布的全面贸易关税将使荷兰到 2026 年的经济增长减少一个百分点。【原文：The sweeping trade tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump would reduce economic growth in the Netherlands by a percentage point through 2026, Dutch economic policy adviser CPB said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-tariffs-would-take-percentage-point-off-dutch-economic-growth-cpb-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2GGZPDJMZKMXCLB5W7HZF3KHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国营媒体称美国已与中国就关税问题进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[隶属于中国国家广播公司中央电视台的社交媒体账号 "玉渊潭天 "周四称，特朗普政府已与中国接触，寻求就美国总统唐纳德-特朗普单挑中国政府征收145%关税一事进行谈判。【原文：The Trump administration has approached China seeking talks on U.S. President Donald Trump's singling Beijing out for 145% tariffs, said Yuyuan Tantian, a social media account affiliated with Chinese state broadcaster CCTV said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-has-reached-out-china-talk-tariffs-state-media-says-2025-05-01/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2WQK6AFRIC5GJQ3M7CKJHKPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:48:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>