<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:33:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:33:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[CERAweek: AI leading to faster, cheaper oil production, executives say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is speeding up oil and gas drilling and prompting companies to take a second look at places they had viewed as too difficult or expensive to develop, executives detailed during the CERAWeek conference in Houston.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-ai-leading-faster-cheaper-oil-production-executives-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PENN5ZILEFPYLGUSOYO6PWFQUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brazil's Eletrobras posts 25% rise in fourth-quarter net profit]]></title><description><![CDATA[Brazilian power firm Eletrobras reported on Thursday a near 25% increase in its fourth-quarter net profit from a year earlier to 1.11 billion reais ($191.4 million).]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazils-eletrobras-posts-55-fall-fourth-quarter-net-profit-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YWBRQATPZJD5GVDPF3X55QOQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK, US hold private talks to resolve Apple encryption order, Bloomberg News reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[British officials held private talks with their U.S. counterparts to resolve concerns that UK is trying to force Apple to build a backdoor into Americans' encrypted data, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/uk-us-hold-private-talks-resolve-apple-encryption-order-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3S6ACJ3CJPCVHHX6RLDVGJJPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Foxconn to post higher Q4 profit on AI server demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taiwan's Foxconn , the world's largest contract electronics maker, is expected to report on Friday that fourth-quarter profit rose 2.35% on strong demand for artificial intelligence servers.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-post-higher-q4-profit-ai-server-demand-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3JZXXLPQNMOZBHEKKVYD25UOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US frees up almost $4.7 billion loan to TotalEnergies for Mozambique gas project, FT reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump's administration has released almost $5 billion in funding for a liquefied natural gas project by France's TotalEnergies in Mozambique, the Financial Times reported on Thursday.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-frees-up-almost-47-billion-loan-totalenergies-mozambique-gas-project-ft-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NABSASVBTZISRCNHGOTGBXKS4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Stock Exchange hires top ETF executives from Cboe, Nasdaq]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Texas Stock Exchange (TSXE), still months away from winning regulatory approval to begin operations, said it hired senior exchange-traded funds executives from Cboe Global Markets and Nasdaq to win a share of trading in the $11 trillion U.S. ETF market.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/texas-stock-exchange-hires-top-etf-executives-cboe-nasdaq-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWMOJTDJ4JO2RASNFNXC6TZBQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国大型玩具制造商加快将生产基地迁出中国的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普与中国的贸易战愈演愈烈之际，沃尔玛和塔吉特的一家主要玩具供应商正在加快撤出中国的步伐，重新调整生产。【原文：A major supplier of toys to Walmart and Target is accelerating its shift out of China as it reshapes production amid President Donald Trump's intensifying trade war with the country.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/major-us-toymaker-speeds-up-plan-move-manufacturing-out-china-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">32YHARYX7NPL7ONRYB54EPFT44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：贸易战担忧扼杀复苏希望，熊市开始发力]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GKPR4AP6SZJMZL7DVVCXVOWXHM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，苹果计划推出可实时翻译对话的 AirPods 功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，苹果公司正在计划推出一项新的 AirPods 功能，允许该设备将与人的对话实时翻译成另一种语言。【原文：Apple is planning a new AirPods feature that would allow the device to live-translate conversations with people into another language, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/apple-plans-airpods-feature-that-can-live-translate-conversations-bloomberg-news-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3LIZF46RVKHXAOFZKTPMQZA7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 化妆品和香水假日需求强劲，季度业绩居首]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty 公司周四公布的第四季度销售额和利润均超出预期，这预示着该公司将迎来一个强劲的假日旺季，因为购物者纷纷涌入其门店购买从化妆品到香水等各种产品，这使得该公司股价在盘后交易中上涨了 7%。【原文：Ulta Beauty beat sales and profit expectations for the fourth quarter on Thursday, signaling a robust holiday season as shoppers flocked to its stores for products ranging from cosmetics to perfumes, sending shares up 7% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/ulta-beauty-tops-quarterly-results-strong-holiday-demand-cosmetics-perfumes-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RDKUQN6YNBLVXGU6BZXQSMEGEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》报道，软银和 OpenAI 将在大阪前夏普 LCD 工厂联合运营人工智能代理公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周五报道，软银计划将日本一家前夏普液晶面板工厂改造成一个数据中心，用于运行与美国 ChatGPT 开发商 OpenAI 合作开发的人工智能代理。【原文：SoftBank plans to transform a former Sharp LCD panel plant in Japan into a data center for operating artificial intelligence agents developed in collaboration with U.S.-based ChatGPT creator, OpenAI, according to a Nikkei report on Friday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/softbank-openai-jointly-run-ai-agents-ex-sharp-lcd-plant-osaka-nikkei-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3TT2AI2P45OEFL7DXFSNY2W62E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标准普尔 500 指数调整的六张图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[一年多来，美国股市首次出现调整。现在的问题是，下滑是否会变得更加严重。【原文：For the first time in over a year, the U.S. stock market is in a correction. The question now is whether the slide is set to get worse.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/sp-500-correction-six-charts-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JIBCDBU5VBJQTHTLLFL47MFRBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compass is in talks to buy Buffett's real-estate brokerage unit, WSJ reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[Home brokerage Compass is in advanced talks to acquire Warren Buffett's real-estate brokerage business, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/compass-is-talks-buy-buffetts-real-estate-brokerage-unit-wsj-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RWH5WNCDN5MOZDAWHUYIDWBZGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉称可能成为报复性关税的目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的特斯拉公司在给美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）的一封信中表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的贸易战可能使特斯拉成为美国报复性关税的目标。【原文：Elon Musk's Tesla said in a letter to the US trade representative Jamieson Greer that President Donald Trump's trade war could make it a target for retaliatory tariffs against the U.S.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-warns-trump-administration-it-is-exposed-retaliatory-tariffs-ft-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ECFO4V4Y5JKOTGAY7ETEQYDVEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[燃料短缺影响收成，玻利维亚豆农人心惶惶]]></title><description><![CDATA[在玻利维亚的圣克鲁斯农场地区，日益严重的燃料短缺开始影响农民收割庄稼的能力，这也是这个农业已成为主要经济驱动力的南美国家所担忧的问题。【原文：In Bolivia's farm region of Santa Cruz, a worsening fuel shortage is starting to hit farmers' ability to harvest their crops, a concern for the embattled South American country where agriculture has become a key economic driver.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/bolivias-soy-farmers-edge-fuel-shortage-hits-harvest-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5X7RX6YQJMB3GUIZ7HYVUPHUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:52:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在关税之争中，通用汽车首席执行官周三会见特朗普 -- 白宫]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员告诉路透社，唐纳德-特朗普总统周三会见了通用汽车公司首席执行官玛丽-巴拉（Mary Barra），在关税战持续不断的情况下讨论了这家汽车制造商的投资计划。【原文：President Donald Trump met with General Motors CEO Mary Barra on Wednesday to talk about the automaker's investment plans amid an ongoing tariff war, a White House official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-ceo-met-with-trump-wednesday-amid-tariff-fight-white-house-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUWE3ZVTHNLVFOVMUOCARL3UBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部确认俄罗斯能源融资许可证到期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四证实，根据乔-拜登（Joe Biden）总统任期最后几天实施的严厉制裁措施，允许与俄罗斯金融机构停止能源交易的许可本周如期到期。【原文：The U.S. Treasury on Thursday confirmed that a license allowing a wind-down of energy transactions with Russian financial institutions expired as scheduled this week under stiff sanctions imposed in the final days of Joe Biden's presidency.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-treasury-confirms-expiration-russian-energy-financing-license-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BG56JYV7SBN5XOABP53N72G3QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通工程师使用编码助手后效率跃升 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根大通全球首席信息官 Lori Beer 说，摩根大通数以万计的软件工程师通过使用该银行开发的编码助手工具提高了效率，交付产品的速度提高了 10%至 20%。【原文：Tens of thousands of JPMorgan Chase software engineers increased their efficiency, delivering products 10% to 20% faster by using a coding assistant tool developed by the bank, its global chief information officer Lori Beer said.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/jpmorgan-engineers-efficiency-jumps-much-20-using-coding-assistant-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PWASWVRR7VMP3NKOSV27LOO5S4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:04:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国央行行长：特朗普的经济政策是美国经济的悲剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国欧洲中央银行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周四表示，特朗普政府领导下的美国目前的经济发展对全球经济是一个负面冲击，但首先对美国经济是一个负面冲击。【原文：Current economic developments in the United States under the Trump administration are a negative shock for the global economy but above all for the U.S. economy, French European Central Bank (ECB) policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-economic-policy-is-tragedy-us-economy-says-french-central-banker-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZJHOADDCURJRHOZ4FQXSQJTQYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Blooomberg News 报道，阿联酋将推动更容易获得美国芯片技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，阿拉伯联合酋长国的一位高级官员计划访问华盛顿，要求更容易获得美国的技术，并讨论在美国的投资问题。【原文：A top United Arab Emirates official plans to visit Washington to press for easier access to American technology and discuss investment in the United States, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/uae-push-easier-access-us-chip-technology-blooomberg-news-reports-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZ2E2KA6DZI5XOHT32TC5HQPTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，安联牵头的财团将于下周完成价值 38 亿美元的 Viridium 收购交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位业内消息人士周四称，安联牵头的财团即将赢得对德国最大寿险管理公司 Viridium 的竞购，该公司正在被金融投资者 Cinven 出售，预计下周将敲定一笔 35 亿欧元（38.0 亿美元）的交易。【原文：An Allianz-led consortium is close to winning a bid for Germany's largest life insurance administrator Viridium, being sold by financial investor Cinven in a 3.5 billion euros ($3.80 billion) deal expected to be finalised next week, two industry sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/allianz-led-consortium-close-38-billion-viridium-takeover-next-week-sources-say-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DOAAHUQ465N3ZPI3TOBHUF4KAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国欧盟葡萄酒进口商和零售商警告关税将导致倒闭和裁员]]></title><description><![CDATA[销售法国香槟和意大利葡萄酒的美国进口商、分销商和零售商告诉路透社，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁对欧洲酒精饮料征收 200% 的关税将对他们造成沉重打击。【原文：U.S. importers, distributors and retailers selling French champagne and Italian wines told Reuters that U.S. President Donald Trump's threatened 200% tariff on European alcoholic drinks would hit them hard.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-importers-retailers-eu-wine-warn-closures-layoffs-tariffs-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZMEIXL5ZTNO4VOQCHUDSLFBMQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[D-Wave 发布乐观预测后，量子计算公司股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 D-Wave Quantum 预测季度营收强于预期之后，一些量子计算公司的股票周四反弹，扩大了上一交易日的涨幅，与大盘走势背道而驰。【原文：Shares of some quantum computing companies rallied on Thursday, adding to gains from the previous session and bucking the broader market's trend after D-Wave Quantum forecast stronger-than-expected quarterly revenue.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/quantum-computing-company-shares-jump-after-d-waves-upbeat-forecast-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4MW737FZZNTPNDJF2RMN4NIG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:23:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西推举皮埃特罗-门德斯连任巴西国家石油公司董事长]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西国营石油公司（Petrobras）周四表示，巴西政府已提名皮特罗-门德斯（Pietro Mendes）担任新一届董事长，这是该公司收到的股东提名的董事会成员之一。【原文：Brazilian state-run oil firm Petrobras said on Thursday that the Brazilian government has put forward Pietro Mendes for a new term as chairman, among the board members nominations from its shareholders that the company has received.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/brazil-puts-forward-pietro-mendes-new-term-petrobras-chairman-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D3RTA2OL7NLSVIJ5AWKH23R25Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根士丹利研究认为 2025 年上半年并购活动将在波动中放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩根士丹利研究公司（Morgan Stanley Research）周四在一份报告中称，由于市场波动给首席执行官、董事会和计划谈判和启动交易的保荐人带来了不确定性，预计 2025 年上半年投资银行业务将放缓。【原文：Investment banking is expected to experience a slowdown in the first half of 2025 as market volatility creates uncertainty for CEOs, boards and sponsors planning to negotiate and launch deals, Morgan Stanley Research said in a note on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/markets/deals/morgan-stanley-research-sees-slowdown-ma-activity-first-half-2025-amid-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHB7TRNDXFPJPDHWHPW5UMHPVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CERAWEEK 数据中心建设加剧了对美国最大电网负担过重的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周在休斯顿举行的 CERAWeek 会议上，能源高管和监管者表示，人工智能数据中心的快速发展正在加剧人们对美国老化的电网能否满足这一需求的担忧。【原文：The rapid development of AI data centers is intensifying concerns about how well an aging U.S. electrical grid can hold up to that demand, energy executives and regulators said at the CERAWeek conference in Houston this week.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-data-center-build-out-stokes-fears-overburdening-biggest-us-grid-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OENIVGYZVFPAFMHP7QDBHZE564</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国船东组织称美国港口费提案违反世贸组织规则和美国法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四看到的一份声明称，中国船东协会反对美国向拥有或已从中国订购船只的远洋货运公司征收高额入港费的提议，认为这违反了国际规则和美国法律。【原文：The China Shipowners' Association opposes a U.S. proposal to slap hefty port entry fees on ocean cargo carriers that own or have ordered vessels from China, saying it violates international rules and U.S. laws, according to a statement seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/world/china-shipowners-group-says-us-port-fee-proposal-breaks-wto-rules-us-law-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63ZORPV475JS7K24GCD4YR6YBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kering 任命 Demna 为 Gucci 艺术总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品牌古驰（Gucci）的所有者开云集团（Kering）周四表示，古驰已任命格鲁吉亚设计师德姆纳（Demna）为艺术总监，以重振其陷入困境的旗舰品牌，阻止销售下滑。【原文：Italian luxury brand Gucci has appointed Georgian designer Demna as its artistic director, owner Kering said on Thursday, as it tries to revitalise its struggling flagship label and stop a slide in sales.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/kering-appoints-demna-artistic-director-gucci-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4ANVCJVABOXPEWVY4ONQBCTAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:12:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尔巴尼亚开始关闭 TikTok，关注青少年暴力问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心社交媒体助长校内外的青少年暴力，阿尔巴尼亚政府周四开始实施为期一年的禁令，TikTok 用户在访问这款流行的短视频应用时遇到了困难。【原文：TikTok users in Albania are experiencing difficulties accessing the popular short video app after a one-year government ban took effect on Thursday, prompted by concerns that social media is fuelling youth violence in and outside school.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/technology/albania-starts-turning-off-tiktok-amid-concern-over-youth-violence-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SIVEXLLWVNKRBFTE35R6WFQFY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cucinelli 预计 2024 年营业利润增长 13%，并确认了指导目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利奢侈品集团布鲁内罗-库奇内利（Brunello Cucinelli）周四表示，去年其营业利润增长了 12.9%，并确认了 2025 年和 2026 年销售额增长约 10%的预期。【原文：Italian luxury group Brunello Cucinelli on Thursday said its operating profit had risen 12.9% last year and confirmed expectations for sales growth of around 10% in 2025 and 2026.】]]></description><link>www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/cucinelli-sees-operating-profit-increase-13-2024-confirms-guidance-2025-03-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O7J2MDLYBVLODOSZEL7FSCI6V4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>