<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:39:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:38:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月制造业生产停滞]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 7 月份的工厂生产没有变化，表明制造业活动停滞不前，因为企业要应对进口关税带来的更高成本。【原文：U.S. factory production was unchanged in July suggesting manufacturing activity was stalling as businesses navigate higher costs from import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-manufacturing-production-stalls-july-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C5COVMT6ZJLA7DH5EK6TMX5TOY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[U-Blox 称正在与收购方 Advent 商谈收购事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士汽车导航微芯片和软件制造商 U-Blox 控股公司周五表示，该公司正在与安宏资本国际公司（Advent International）商谈被该私募股权公司收购的事宜。【原文：Switzerland's U-Blox Holding , a maker of microchips and software for car navigation, said on Friday that it was in talks with Advent International about being taken over by the private equity firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/u-blox-says-it-is-talks-with-suitor-advent-over-takeover-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPF5V7YLCRND7MY2ZA253JBBWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:28:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月消费者情绪疲软；通胀预期上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于家庭预期进口关税会导致商品价格上涨，8 月份美国消费者情绪有所疲软。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment softened in August as households anticipated higher goods prices because of import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-consumer-sentiment-weakens-august-inflation-expectations-rise-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLAD67WVYJMPHFLO7JPS6CB7IM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泄漏后 Seaway 原油管道系统全面恢复运行]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业产品合伙公司周五表示，本周早些时候该公司位于休斯顿东南部的石油码头发生原油泄漏后，Seaway 原油管道系统已恢复全面运营。【原文：Enterprise Products Partners said on Friday the Seaway crude oil pipeline system resumed full operations after a crude oil leak from the company's oil terminal in southeast Houston earlier this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/seaway-crude-oil-pipeline-system-resumes-full-operations-after-leak-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TA6PYCWQMBIL7JRJKEUGJV62TA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普政府正考虑为英特尔股份提供芯片法案基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的政府正在考虑为英特尔提供芯片法案基金，以换取该芯片制造商的股份。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is eyeing Chips Act funds for Intel in exchange for a stake in the chipmaker, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-administration-eyeing-chips-act-funds-intel-stake-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PFJE4GUFMRPVLM7DMU2GMOLZCE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西鸡肉出口商协会（BRF）预计中国和欧洲将恢复鸡肉进口]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西食品加工商 BRF SA 希望中国和欧洲 "在几天或几周内 "恢复购买鸡肉产品，因为当地政府控制了引发第二季度贸易禁令的禽流感疫情。【原文：Brazilian food processor BRF SA is hopeful China and Europe will resume buying chicken products "in a matter of days or weeks" as local authorities controlled a bird flu outbreak that triggered trade bans in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/brazils-brf-expects-china-europe-resume-chicken-imports-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAFEWHTY3VOK5J37ZIVWXOHUZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息、贸易协议有望达成，道指再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，道琼斯工业平均指数创下盘中历史新高，成为美国三大股指中最后一个创下历史纪录的股指，华尔街在宽松货币政策、贸易紧张局势缓和以及企业盈利向好的前景推动下反弹。【原文：The Dow Jones Industrial Average hit an all-time intraday high on Friday, making it the last of the three major U.S. indexes to clinch a record in Wall Street's rally fueled by the prospect of a looser monetary policy, easing trade tensions and upbeat corporate earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dow-scales-record-high-hopes-fed-rate-cuts-trade-deals-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KT34KVWXQZPWRKYWFVV4UGUWSM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称未来几周将对钢铁和半导体芯片征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，他将在未来几周内宣布对进口钢铁和半导体芯片征收关税。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he would announce tariffs on imports of steel and semiconductor chips in coming weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-he-will-set-tariffs-steel-semiconductor-chips-coming-weeks-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KJWZM23XSFPSRDANLFJUI73RTI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国初创公司 "陆地空间 "的火箭试飞失败]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，中国商业火箭开发商陆地空间技术公司（LandSpace Technology）的一枚甲烷动力火箭试飞失败，运载火箭出现 "异常"，该公司表示正在调查原因。【原文：A flight test of one of Chinese commercial rocket developer LandSpace Technology's methane-powered rockets failed on Friday after the carrier rocket experienced an "anomaly", the company said, adding that it is investigating the cause.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/flight-test-chinese-start-up-landspaces-rocket-fails-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ2IJYFJOJJUZDSGOAPSG24GW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月进口价格因消费品成本上升而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[受消费品成本上升的推动，美国 7 月份进口价格出现反弹，这是关税导致通胀回升的最新迹象。【原文：U.S. import prices rebounded in July, boosted by higher costs for consumer goods, the latest indication that inflation was poised to pick up because of tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-import-prices-rebound-july-higher-consumer-goods-costs-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2I7QX75ZBNNKDNSNHE2AXU6BMA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 7 月零售额稳健增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管劳动力市场疲软和商品价格上涨可能会抑制第三季度消费支出的增长，但汽车需求强劲以及亚马逊和沃尔玛的促销活动还是推动了美国零售销售的增长。【原文：U.S. retail sales were boosted by strong demand for motor vehicles as well as promotions by Amazon and Walmart, though a softening labor market and higher goods prices could curb growth in consumer spending in the third quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-retail-sales-increase-solidly-july-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52I3NYPCLBIO5GFCRQMVDJLUKQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望升温，美国股票基金每周吸引资金流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至8月13日的一周内，美国股票基金获得了大量资金流入，原因是投资者扭转了因美联储可能在9月份降息的希望而抛售股票的立场，同时中美关税休战进一步提振了市场情绪。【原文：U.S. equity funds gained substantial inflows in the week through August 13 as investors reversed a selling stance on hopes of a potential Federal Reserve rate cut in September, while a U.S.-China tariff truce further lifted sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-equity-funds-draw-weekly-inflows-rate-cut-hopes-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JQYIMX6HSJLY3NB5FQVOUFOTTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:26:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数经济学家表示，美国联邦储备委员会将在 9 月降息，并在今年再降息一次：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[在对全球最大经济体健康状况的担忧日益加剧之际，路透社调查的大多数经济学家的基本预测仍然是，美联储将在 9 月份降息，这是今年的首次降息，随后可能在年底前再次降息。【原文：A Federal Reserve interest rate cut in September, the first this year, followed perhaps by another before year-end remains the base forecast for most economists polled by Reuters amid rising concerns about the health of the world's biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-fed-cut-rates-september-once-more-this-year-say-most-economists-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ED5HXC5HFJL6ZNNMWBRUFKMQVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻加息热潮退去，阿拉斯加成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6QSRZ5AKFPCPJQV4PDT2MOORY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据天空新闻报道，贾里德-库什纳的公司购买了英国贷款公司 OakNorth 8%的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[据天空新闻周五援引业内消息人士的话报道，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的女婿贾里德-库什纳（Jared Kushner）创办的私募股权公司 Affinity Partners 已签署协议，收购英国贷款公司 OakNorth 8%的股份。【原文：Affinity Partners, a private equity firm founded by U.S. President Donald Trump's son-in-law Jared Kushner, has signed a deal to buy an 8% stake in British lender OakNorth, Sky News reported on Friday, citing industry sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jared-kushners-firm-buys-8-stake-uk-lender-oaknorth-sky-news-reports-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EF5JBSDOR5KRHAPA3RZMLTBR5E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:56:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息预期影响，标普 500 指数和道指期货攀升；联合健康跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受 9 月降息预期支撑，周五道指和 S&amp;P 500 指数期货走高；伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）增持联合健康保险公司（UnitedHealth）股份后，该公司股价大涨。【原文：Futures tracking the Dow and the S&amp;P 500 were higher on Friday, underpinned by expectations of an interest rate cut in September, while UnitedHealth surged after Berkshire Hathaway raised its stake in the health insurer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/sp-500-dow-futures-climb-rate-cut-expectations-unitedhealth-jumps-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3ZECOPOVNKMBD4IGQBCLPIS4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对高盛的攻击可能促使华尔街的独立分析被淡化]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者和学术界人士表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对高盛（Goldman Sachs）关税风险研究的批评可能会促使一些分析师淡化他们的研究，这一结果可能会使投资者获得的信息更不可靠。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's criticism of Goldman Sachs' research on tariff risks could prompt some analysts to water down their research, investors and academics said, an outcome that could leave investors with less reliable information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trumps-attack-goldman-could-prompt-watering-down-wall-streets-independent-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MDFEVQESI5PUJPORYHWPPCHFKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T1 与康宁达成协议，生产全美国制造的太阳能电池板]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国太阳能公司 T1 Energy 和特种玻璃制造商康宁周五表示，双方已达成一项协议，将建立一个完全国产化的太阳能供应链，将在美国生产的多晶硅、硅片、电池和电池板连接起来。【原文：U.S. solar company T1 Energy and specialty glass maker Corning have reached a deal that will establish a fully domestic solar supply chain, connecting polysilicon, wafers, cells, and panels manufactured in the United States, they said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/t1-corning-reach-deal-make-fully-american-made-solar-panels-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BGVNVWQUHFKMTAUFYYZUBKTUKY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀疲软，关税休战，全球股票基金流入量创六周新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至8月13日的一周，全球股票基金创下六周来最大单周流入量，原因是美国通胀数据低于预期，以及中美延长关税休战期提振了投资者情绪。【原文：Global equity funds logged their largest weekly inflows in six weeks in the week to August 13, lifted by a softer-than-expected U.S. inflation print and an extension of a tariff truce between the United States and China which boosted investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-flows-graphic-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VWBTWKVQJO4JK6DPUSCAD5BUQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国蚂蚁金服集团称 "灵通智能 "交易正按计划进行，此前有报道称该交易被推迟]]></title><description><![CDATA[有报道称，中国蚂蚁金服集团收购光明智能证券与大宗商品集团的相关程序正在按计划推进，该报道回应称，该交易可能面临更严格的监管审查，并可能被推迟。【原文：China's Ant Group said relevant procedures regarding its acquisition of Bright Smart Securities & Commodities Group are moving forward as planned, in response to a report that said the deal may face higher regulatory scrutiny and could be delayed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-ant-group-says-bright-smart-deal-track-following-report-delay-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYVY44RWY5KXFA3UTAQQOD6JAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:45:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[科技出口强劲，台湾上调 2025 年 GDP 增长预期至 4.45]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾统计机构周五表示，随着科技和人工智能相关产品需求旺盛，台湾经济在2025年的增长速度有望超过此前的预测。【原文：Taiwan's economy is expected to grow faster in 2025 than previously forecast, the statistics agency said on Friday, as the island continues to reap the benefits of strong demand for tech and artificial intelligence-related products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-raises-2025-gdp-growth-forecast-445-strong-tech-exports-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73ICPMQJUZJ5DBAA2UEJ36EIMQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kyivstar 首席执行官称俄乌和平协议将提升在美上市后的价值]]></title><description><![CDATA[乌克兰移动运营商 Kyivstar 首席执行官 Oleksandr Komarov 周五在该公司纽约上市前表示，俄乌战争的和平解决将 "极大地 "提升该公司的价值。【原文：A peaceful resolution to the war between Russia and Ukraine would boost the value of Ukrainian mobile operator Kyivstar "quite significantly", its CEO Oleksandr Komarov said on Friday ahead of the company's New York listing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kyivstar-ceo-says-russia-ukraine-peace-deal-would-boost-value-after-us-listing-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZY3OTNKRVLTFESDXGGWRSLH2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯的乌克兰战争如何影响全球市场？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔-普京周五晚些时候将在阿拉斯加会晤，以达成一项可能的乌克兰停火协议，世界市场对此密切关注。【原文：World markets are watching closely as U.S. President Donald Trump and Russia's Vladimir Putin meet in Alaska later on Friday to seal a possible ceasefire agreement in Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/here-is-how-russias-war-ukraine-has-shaped-global-markets-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IN5B2RGHBFMJXDYFCHMLMJX5IA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[应用材料公司股价因中国需求疲软和关税风险而下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[芯片设备制造商应用材料公司因中国需求低迷发布了疲软的第四季度业绩预期，加剧了市场对关税相关风险的担忧，周五该公司股价在盘前交易中暴跌近14%。【原文：Shares of Applied Materials tumbled nearly 14% in premarket trading on Friday after the chip equipment maker issued weak fourth-quarter forecasts on sluggish China demand, fueling concerns over tariff-related risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/applied-materials-shares-sink-weak-china-demand-tariff-risks-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E2LQMEMWKNPIJI7WWGPZ26URCA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国天然气公司所有者 Centrica 与美国德文能源公司达成天然气交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国天然气公司（British Gas）的所有者 Centrica 周五表示，它已与德文能源公司（Devon Energy）签订了一项天然气协议，该美国公司将在自 2028 年起的 10 年内每年供应相当于五船液化天然气的天然气。【原文：British Gas owner Centrica said on Friday it has entered into a natural gas agreement with Devon Energy , in which the U.S.-based firm will supply an equivalent to five LNG cargoes per year over a 10-year term from 2028.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/british-gas-owner-centrica-enters-natural-gas-deal-with-us-based-devon-energy-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNQ44DAUENNCXJ6OD2WXZ5XB5U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:20:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伯克希尔哈撒韦公司收购新股份后，联合健康跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在沃伦-巴菲特（Warren Buffett）的伯克希尔-哈撒韦公司（Berkshire Hathaway）透露对联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）的新投资后，该公司股价在盘前交易中大涨超过 12%。【原文：Shares of UnitedHealth Group surged more than 12% in premarket trading on Friday after Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway revealed a new investment in the health insurer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-jumps-after-berkshire-hathaway-buys-new-stake-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HANBQZAU6ZIRDONAN6KF6HFJAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:19:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔法兰克福上市股票在报道美国可能入股芯片制造商后上涨 3.6]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔在法兰克福上市的股票周五上涨了 3.6%，此前一天彭博新闻社报道称，特朗普政府正在与这家陷入困境的芯片制造商谈判，希望美国政府能入股该公司。【原文：Intel's Frankfurt-listed shares rose 3.6% on Friday, a day after Bloomberg News reported the Trump administration is in talks with the struggling chipmaker to have the U.S. government potentially take a stake in the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/intels-frankfurt-listed-shares-rise-36-after-report-us-could-take-stake-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHWGRXTHR5NJNF5KPB6WMOG4VI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银的 PayPay 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[软银周五表示，支付应用运营商 PayPay Corp 已申请在美国上市美国存托股票。【原文：SoftBank said on Friday that payments app operator PayPay Corp has applied to list American depositary shares in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbanks-paypay-applies-us-listing-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZJRG7QPYJKG5FBVO35RFSAIKM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五点钟方向北上阿拉斯加，大家期待已久的会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前似乎没有什么阻碍股市多头的因素，但在阿拉斯加举行的具有里程碑意义的美俄峰会、怀俄明州的央行shin-dig会议和玻利维亚的选举等，可能会让他们变得谨慎一些。【原文：There seems to be very little standing in the way of stock-market bulls right now, but a landmark U.S./Russia summit in Alaska, a central bank shin-dig in Wyoming and elections in Bolivia, among other things, may imbue them with some caution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-themes-corrected-graphic-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJWEGJNLFJLO5LPQI7SL2EBZ6A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲销售疲软导致珠宝制造商潘多拉股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦珠宝制造商潘多拉（Pandora）周五股价暴跌，因为该公司指出其主要欧洲市场销售疲软，而美国市场的强劲销售仅部分抵消了这一影响。【原文：Shares in Danish jewellery maker Pandora plummeted on Friday after the company flagged weakening sales in its key European markets, only partially offset by robust sales in the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/shares-jewellery-maker-pandora-plummet-weakening-european-sales-2025-08-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6IQUQU5QXZOEPJJKJ26OMFOTD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>