<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:04:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:04:21 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[作者称，Meta 知道自己用盗版书训练人工智能]]></title><description><![CDATA[一群作者在最新披露的法庭文件中指控，Meta Platforms 在其首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）的批准下，使用盗版版权书籍来训练其人工智能系统。【原文：Meta Platforms used pirated versions of copyrighted books to train its artificial intelligence systems with approval from its CEO Mark Zuckerberg, a group of authors alleged in newly disclosed court papers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/meta-knew-it-used-pirated-books-train-ai-authors-say-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZGNS4Q3KCZJLTECTJE3EJBNDAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:44:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业部冬小麦播种的贸易估算历史]]></title><description><![CDATA[以下是路透社对分析师对美国农业部年度美国冬小麦播种报告数据预期的调查历史。【原文：Below is a history of Reuters polls of analysts' expectations for figures in the U.S. Department of Agriculture's annual U.S. winter wheat seedings report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/history-trade-estimates-usda-winter-wheat-seedings-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQ25QX44TNOLPNIDBHVFG5Q444</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日产汽车愿意联合排放二氧化碳以避免在欧洲被罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[日产汽车公司欧洲发言人周四向路透社表示，日产汽车公司愿意与其他汽车制造商合作，以在2025年实现二氧化碳减排目标。【原文：Nissan Motor Co Ltd is open to pooling with other carmakers in order to reach its CO2 targets in 2025, a spokesperson for the Japanese carmaker in Europe said to Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-open-pooling-co2-avoid-fines-europe-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RBT3ZDPD45PG5AEOAM2WLEFYEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德退出气候组织，华尔街最新一次环保倒退]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球最大的资产管理公司贝莱德（BlackRock）周四表示，它将退出 "净零资产管理公司"（Net Zero Asset Managers）计划，这是华尔街在共和党政客提出反垄断担忧的背景下在环保方面的最新退步。【原文：BlackRock , the world's biggest asset manager, said on Thursday it will leave the Net Zero Asset Managers initiative, Wall Street's latest environmental step-back amid antitrust concerns raised by Republican politicians.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/blackrock-quits-climate-group-wall-streets-latest-environmental-step-back-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AAKG4E53OBJOLARKGO66XR76SA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 19:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，美国参议院计划于 1 月 16 日举行特朗普财政部长人选贝森特的听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Politico周四援引三位熟悉参议院财政委员会计划的未具名消息人士的话报道，美国参议院财政委员会计划于1月16日就当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提名的美国财政部部长人选斯科特-贝森特举行听证会。【原文：The U.S. Senate Finance Committee is planning a Jan. 16 hearing on President-elect Donald Trump's nominee to lead the U.S. Department of Treasury, Scott Bessent, Politico reported on Thursday, citing three unnamed sources familiar with the panel's plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-senate-planning-jan-16-hearing-trump-treasury-pick-bessent-politico-reports-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I6WMPUXT35JWLFVVKZBWY2U7Z4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 19:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼：支持将 12 月降息作为 "最后 "调整步骤]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周四表示，她支持上个月的降息，认为这是美国央行货币政策调整的 "最后一步"，通胀风险的上升决定了未来的谨慎态度。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman on Thursday said she supported last month's interest-rate cut as the "final step" in the U.S. central bank's monetary policy recalibration, with rising inflation risks dictating a cautious approach ahead.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bowman-supported-dec-rate-cut-final-recalibration-step-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YV6W2ZPLEVNHZLRPCSH3SSPJJI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:38:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DirecTV 就驳回 Fubo 对 Venu Sports 的索赔提出质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国卫星电视供应商 DirecTV 周四对驳回 FuboTV 针对华特-迪士尼、福克斯和华纳兄弟 Discovery 计划推出的流媒体服务 Venu Sports 的诉讼提出质疑，称这并不能解决围绕合资企业的反垄断问题。【原文：U.S. satellite TV provider DirecTV on Thursday challenged a dismissal of FuboTV's lawsuit against Venu Sports, the streaming service planned by Walt Disney, Fox and Warner Bros Discovery, saying it does not resolve antitrust issues around the joint venture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/directv-challenges-dismissal-fubos-claims-against-venu-sports-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TA2FSNJ235MQJA3XTTISDCB7H4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德称央行 "接近 "中性利率水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）周四表示不愿再次降息，因为美国央行在新的一年里将面临经济复苏和通胀率仍高于2%目标的局面。【原文：Kansas City Federal Reserve President Jeff Schmid signaled on Thursday a reluctance to cut interest rates again as the U.S. central bank comes into the new year facing a resilient economy and inflation that remains above its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-schmid-says-central-bank-near-neutral-interest-rate-level-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5LLDIDZEVNWNDMCSR574ALXPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:35:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[太平洋帕利塞德大火可能意味着加州廉价房主保险的终结]]></title><description><![CDATA[遭受野火肆虐的洛杉矶太平洋帕利塞德地区是美国最昂贵的社区之一，好莱坞明星和数百万美元的豪宅都在这里。根据路透社对保险和房地产行业数据的分析，在本周的灾难发生之前，该地区的保险费用是全美最实惠的地区之一。【原文：The Pacific Palisades area ravaged by wildfires in Los Angeles is one of the most expensive neighborhoods in the U.S., home to Hollywood A-Listers and multimillion dollar mansions. And ahead of this week's disaster, its insurance costs were among the most affordable in the country, according to a Reuters analysis of insurance and real estate industry data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/pacific-palisades-fire-may-spell-an-end-cheap-homeowners-insurance-california-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZTB7RDA4KRP3BGYH4F7CEGLRAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格公司将支付 1.1 亿美元解决肯塔基州有关阿片类药物流行的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[肯塔基州指控克罗格连锁超市的药店助长了致命的阿片类药物流行，向其所在社区灌输了数亿剂量的成瘾性止痛药，克罗格公司已同意支付 1.1 亿美元解决该诉讼。【原文：Kroger has agreed to pay $110 million to resolve a lawsuit by the state of Kentucky alleging the supermarket chain's pharmacies helped fuel a deadly opioid epidemic by flooding its communities with hundreds of millions of doses of addictive painkillers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/kroger-pay-110-million-resolve-kentucky-lawsuit-over-opioid-epidemic-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZFJQ6PQHGJOQBM5XVYSYZNQXYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 18:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空公司首席财务官塔米-罗莫将于 4 月 1 日退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空公司周四表示，该公司执行副总裁兼首席财务官塔米-罗莫（Tammy Romo）将于 2025 年 4 月 1 日退休。【原文：Southwest Airlines on Thursday said its Executive Vice President &amp; Chief Financial Officer Tammy Romo will retire from the role effective April 1, 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-airlines-cfo-tammy-romo-retire-april-1-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBIF7SVS25OETIM5EUKIBO46UE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[评级机构称洛杉矶野火保险损失总计数十亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[评级机构周四表示，洛杉矶有史以来破坏力最大的野火可能会造成数十亿美元的保险损失，尽管许多房屋可能没有投保。【原文：The most destructive wildfires ever for Los Angeles may cause billions of dollars in insured losses, ratings agencies said on Thursday, though many homes are likely uninsured.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/la-wildfire-insured-losses-total-billions-dollars-ratings-agencies-say-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIEV4PJ4DRLEDGQV7OF4TC43MM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷蒙多称美国将于下周敲定中国汽车打压规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部长吉娜-雷蒙多（Gina Raimondo）告诉路透社，即将卸任的拜登政府计划在下周敲定打击中国汽车软件和硬件的规定。【原文：The outgoing Biden administration plans to finalize rules next week cracking down on Chinese vehicle software and hardware, U.S. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-finalize-chinese-vehicle-crackdown-rules-next-week-raimondo-says-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMD4BK7QRZJ37OKB7N7S2B2VLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:43:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国预测 2025 年世界经济增长率将保持在 2.8]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据联合国周四发布的一份报告，2025 年全球经济增长率预计将保持在 2.8%，与 2024 年持平，受制于前两大经济体美国和中国。【原文：Global economic growth is projected to remain at 2.8% in 2025, unchanged from 2024, held back by the top two economies, the U.S. and China, according to a United Nations report released on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/un-predicts-world-economic-growth-remain-28-2025-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QO2W3AFQBZIYZLGDUV5ITFAXBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:38:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司 2024 年将交付 766 架喷气机，继续稳居榜首]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周四公布的数据显示，2024年该公司将交付766架客机，有望在第六年继续保持在喷气式飞机制造行业的领先地位，因为头号竞争对手波音公司正从长期的内部危机中谨慎复苏。【原文：Airbus delivered 766 airliners in 2024 and looked certain to maintain leadership of the jetmaking industry for a sixth year as arch-rival Boeing recovers cautiously from a prolonged internal crisis, company data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-keeps-top-spot-with-766-jet-deliveries-2024-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTXK5774GZMLLKYPSEMIUVJJ3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 30 年期固定利率抵押贷款利率徘徊在 7% 以下]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，美国抵押贷款利率升至六个月来的新高，这一趋势加上房价上涨可能会进一步将潜在买家挤出市场。【原文：U.S. mortgage rates increased to a fresh six-month high this week, a trend that together with elevated house prices could further squeeze potential buyers from the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-30-year-fixed-rate-mortgage-rate-hovers-just-under-7-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IO6HUTUU7RNHTLSQUYSKW5F2GQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:04:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[育碧将《刺客信条：阴影》延期至 3 月 20 日发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国最大的视频游戏制造商育碧公司（Ubisoft）周四表示，该公司已决定将其大片《刺客信条》（Assassin's Creed）系列最新游戏的发布时间从2月14日推迟到3月20日。【原文：France's largest video game maker Ubisoft has decided to postpone the release of the newest game in its blockbuster franchise Assassin’s Creed to March 20 from Feb. 14, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ubisoft-postpones-release-assassins-creed-shadows-march-20-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S3EFEQ7O7NJJTF4QHOHFHSHAXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空客 2024 年交付 766 架喷气式飞机，稳居行业首位]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司周四公布的数据显示，2024年该公司交付了766架飞机，同比增长4%，有望连续第六年蝉联全球最大喷气式飞机制造商的宝座，而竞争对手波音公司正从长期的内部危机中谨慎复苏。【原文：Airbus delivered 766 planes in 2024, up 4%, and looked certain to remain the world's largest jetmaker for the sixth year in a row as rival Boeing recovers cautiously from a prolonged internal crisis, company data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-delivered-766-jets-2024-hold-industry-top-spot-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JFDKV2FPJBLVDAJ4WJ3UZTZVPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:55:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西总统卢拉称梅塔对事实核查的修改 "极其严重]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西总统路易斯-伊纳西奥-卢拉-达席尔瓦（Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva）周四表示，社交媒体公司 Meta 决定取消其在美国的事实核查项目是 "极其严重的"，他将在与政府官员的会晤中讨论此事。【原文：Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said on Thursday that social media company Meta's decision to scrap its fact-checking program in the U.S. was "extremely serious," and that he would discuss the matter in a meeting with government officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazils-lula-calls-meta-fact-checking-changes-extremely-serious-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NIDYVWXIZPDBGNIUHU4UKV2PY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国公司准备第四季度报告，特朗普和更广泛的增长成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国企业准备公布华尔街今年又一突出业绩的最后一个季度报告之际，投资者正在关注科技公司和相关重量级企业是否会增加近期强劲的利润增长，以及增长是否会扩大到其他行业。【原文：Investors are watching to see if technology companies and related heavyweights will add to recent strong profit gains and whether growth is broadening to other sectors as corporate America prepares to report on the final quarter of another standout year for Wall Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trump-broader-growth-focus-us-companies-prepare-q4-reports-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V33HBZXCHBKDDCL4HU7BAU24EA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球债券摇摆不定，欧元区也难幸免]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在英国和美国面临投资者担心债务增加和通胀持续的压力时，欧元区似乎在很大程度上躲过了市场的怒火--尽管平静背后的原因并不令人愉快。【原文：Just as Britain and the United States come under pressure from investors worried about growing debt and sticky inflation, the euro zone seems to be largely escaping the market's wrath -- even if the reasons behind that calm are not all pleasant.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/good-reasons-bad-global-bond-wobble-passes-over-euro-zone-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RE7LOPRU7NIPBKYSYPRBNKXKIM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:16:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港司法网站显示，开发商融创中国收到清盘申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四晚些时候，香港司法部门网站显示，已对负债累累的房地产开发商融创中国提出清盘申请。【原文：A liquidation petition has been filed against indebted property developer Sunac China , the Hong Kong judiciary's website showed late on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/developer-sunac-china-gets-liquidation-petition-hong-kong-judiciary-website-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VMJBPLMVPZOI3ETCF3GT4W5AIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iconiq Growth 在最新扩张中聘用了分析公司 Datadog 的 Amit Agarwal]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资公司Iconiq Capital的风险投资部门Iconiq Growth告诉路透社，该公司已聘请云分析公司Datadog总裁阿米特-阿加瓦尔（Amit Agarwal）担任普通合伙人，这是该公司领导团队的最新扩充。【原文：Iconiq Growth, the venture arm of investment firm Iconiq Capital, has hired cloud-based analytics firm Datadog's President Amit Agarwal as a general partner in the latest expansion of its leadership team, the company told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/iconiq-growth-hires-analytics-firm-datadogs-amit-agarwal-latest-expansion-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3M7LZFTDH5LPBA7XOHARXKKFZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:35:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储哈克仍预计降息，但认为不确定性很大]]></title><description><![CDATA[费城联储主席帕特里克-哈克（Patrick Harker）周四表示，他仍预计美国央行将降息，但他补充说，政策路径被相当大的经济不确定性所笼罩。【原文：Philadelphia Federal Reserve President Patrick Harker said on Thursday he still expects the U.S. central bank to cut interest rates but added that the policy path is clouded by considerable economic uncertainty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-harker-still-expects-rate-cuts-sees-considerable-uncertainty-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLZZL3JMGVL63DCNDHOJANVPQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:09:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯表示，现在是耐心、渐进式降息的时候了]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周四表示，经济前景的巨大不确定性要求央行谨慎推进未来的降息措施。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins said Thursday that significant uncertainty over the outlook calls for the central bank moving forward cautiously with future rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-collins-says-now-is-time-patient-gradual-approach-rate-cuts-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X7CCCHAIWFJCNAQ3B6FM5YR4OE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁弗兰克-麦考特的自由计划提议竞购 TikTok 的美国资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业家、前洛杉矶道奇队老板弗兰克-麦考特（Frank McCourt）的自由计划（Project Liberty）及其 "人民竞标"（The People's Bid）合作伙伴财团周四表示，他们提议向字节跳动正式出价收购 TikTok 的美国资产。【原文：Entrepreneur and former Los Angeles Dodgers owner Frank McCourt's Project Liberty and its consortium of partners in The People's Bid said on Thursday they proposed to make a formal bid to ByteDance to buy TikTok's U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/billionaire-frank-mccourts-project-liberty-proposes-bid-tiktoks-us-assets-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIWEHUZFSNLIBAEO3R4J6TWM6U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：瑞银接近就瑞士信贷逃税案达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，瑞银集团将支付至少数亿美元，以解决瑞士信贷违反早前与美国司法部就美国客户逃税问题达成的协议的问题。【原文：UBS is set to pay a minimum of hundreds of millions of dollars to settle Credit Suisse's violations of an earlier agreement with the U.S. Department of Justice over customers in the U.S. who evaded tax, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-nears-settlement-over-credit-suisse-tax-evasion-case-wsj-reports-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PS5DJECJ3ZIKJLAVQIXSQX75IU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 13:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲股市回升，债券继续承压]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲股市扭转了早盘的跌势，政府债券继续承压，美元在一年多以来的最高水平附近持稳。【原文：Government bonds remained under pressure on Thursday and the dollar held steady near its highest levels in more than a year as European stocks reversed early losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TKFP2P3VBMFDIDW5NY7LNH7LE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 13:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国市场正处于全球债券风暴的中心地带]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，全球债券大跌波及货币和股票，英国市场是最大的受害者之一。【原文：British markets are among the biggest victims of a global bond selloff that has spilled over into currencies and stocks this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-markets-are-eye-global-bond-storm-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2K77TBFEZJOARDNEQWZXEICESI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 13:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2024 年美国招聘公告数量为九年来最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份报告显示，去年美国雇主发布的招聘公告创下了自2015年以来的最低水平，证实了在此期间就业增长的急剧放缓。【原文：Hiring announcements by U.S. employers last year were the lowest since 2015, a report showed on Thursday, confirming a sharp moderation in job growth over that period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-hiring-announcements-2024-lowest-nine-years-2025-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UFH2YBDXNJL55KE7X2JD2WB6VI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>