<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:05:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:05:09 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长维勒鲁瓦称美联储鲍威尔是央行行长典范]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲中央银行（ECB）决策者弗朗索瓦-维勒鲁瓦-德-加尔豪（Francois Villeroy de Galhau）周五表示，美国联邦储备委员会主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔是一位堪称典范的央行行长，他对美国经济说出了不光彩的事实，而且没有向政治压力低头。【原文：U.S. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell is an exemplary central banker, telling the unflattering truth about the U.S. economy and not bowing to political pressure, European Central Bank (ECB) policymaker Francois Villeroy de Galhau said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-powell-is-an-exemplary-central-banker-ecbs-villeroy-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IQPX2JSTERJBPPSHJ6F25XCWY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:26:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰表示将在一周内完成矿产交易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[双方的目标是在 4 月 26 日之前完成最终协议的讨论。【原文：The aim of both sides is to complete discussions on the final deal by April 26.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/ukraine-says-aiming-wrap-up-mineral-deal-talks-within-week-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYUFDUVRCBLY3EFAKUM2S6W3QE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 08:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国在与美国的紧张关系中推进反 "霸凌 "议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国外交部长王毅警告全球南方国家说，"单边霸凌 "正在伤害一个以规则为基础的世界，同时中国政府继续对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普施加外交压力，要求他收回其惩罚性贸易关税。【原文：China's Foreign Minister Wang Yi warned Global South nations that "unilateral bullying" was hurting a rules-based world, as Beijing kept up the diplomatic pressure on U.S. President Donald Trump to roll back his punitive trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-pushes-anti-bullying-agenda-amid-tensions-with-us-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LQEOCB257RKRPNQEPVCL7AMVUA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度莫迪与马斯克讨论技术合作潜力]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度总理纳伦德拉-莫迪（Narendra Modi）周五在 X 上发帖称，他与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）进行了交谈，并谈到了 "各种问题，包括我们今年早些时候在华盛顿特区会晤时涉及的话题"，但没有说明谈话是何时进行的。【原文：Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi spoke to Elon Musk and talked about "various issues, including the topics we covered during our meeting in Washington DC earlier this year," he said in a post on X on Friday, without saying when the conversation took place.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/indias-modi-musk-discussed-potential-collaboration-technology-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXPJ2AVNLJOXPDO2ZTLVA3AXC4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，越南公安部旨在获得互联网公司的多数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一份文件显示，越南公安部计划收购该国最大的互联网服务提供商之一 FPT Telecom 的多数股权，作为其加强国家网络安全努力的一部分。【原文：Vietnam's Ministry of Public Security plans to take a majority stake in FPT Telecom, one of the country's largest internet providers, as part of its efforts to boost national cybersecurity, according to a document seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vietnams-public-security-ministry-aims-take-majority-stake-internet-firm-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54QV4OIZWRPQFNH5IRBO4FAFT4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 07:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易协议有望达成，日本日经指数创 3 个月来最佳一周表现]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普能够促成与包括日本在内的一些主要贸易伙伴的贸易协议抱有更大的希望，日本日经平均股价周五上涨了1%，创下三个月来最好的一周。【原文：Japan's Nikkei share average rose 1% on Friday to clock its best week in three months, as investors turned more hopeful that U.S. President Donald Trump would be able to broker trade deals with some of its top trading partners, including Japan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japans-nikkei-notches-best-week-3-months-trade-deal-hopes-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QL75D4XI6RJALCSTJ5QCNNZXIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称丰田考虑在美国增产新款RAV4以应对关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟知内情的人士称，丰田公司正在考虑在美国生产其最畅销的 RAV4 SUV 的下一代车型，成为最新一家重新考虑供应链以减轻美国对进口汽车征收关税的冲击的汽车制造商。【原文：Toyota is considering producing the next version of its top-selling RAV4 SUV in the United States, three people familiar with the matter said, becoming the latest automaker to rethink supply chains to lessen the hit from U.S. tariffs on imported vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-weighs-adding-us-production-new-rav4-response-tariffs-sources-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QD7JKTSQLFIIZPMUKKGKSNIYFI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着日本电产收购战的白热化，凯雷正在与牧野进行白武士谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[四位知情人士透露，私募股权巨头凯雷正在与日本牧野铣床公司谈判，希望将其作为潜在的白武士买家，以应对日本电产 18.1 亿美元的恶意收购。【原文：Private equity giant Carlyle is in talks with Japan's Makino Milling Machine as a potential white knight buyer to counter a $1.81 billion hostile takeover bid from Nidec , four people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/carlyle-white-knight-talks-with-makino-say-sources-nidec-takeover-battle-heats-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TITPHDYFX5NXJPL42OO43JT5AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 06:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国将保持贷款利率稳定，但关税引发宽松押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项调查显示，市场普遍预计中国将在周一的月度定盘会上维持基准贷款利率不变，但面对不断升级的中美贸易战，市场正在赌中国会很快推出更多的刺激措施。【原文：China is widely expected to leave its benchmark lending rates unchanged at the monthly fixing on Monday, a Reuters survey showed, but markets are wagering on more stimulus being rolled out soon in the face of an escalating Sino-U.S. trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/china-set-leave-lending-rates-steady-tariffs-raise-easing-bets-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z52TACX6AZOSPMKXQFQJ4MGFV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 05:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：消息人士称印度计划放宽核责任法以吸引外国公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位政府消息人士称，印度正计划放宽其核责任法，对设备供应商的事故相关处罚设定上限，此举主要是为了吸引那些因无限风险而裹足不前的美国公司。【原文：India is planning to ease its nuclear liability laws to cap accident-related penalties on equipment suppliers, three government sources said, in a move mainly to attract U.S. firms that have been holding back due to the risk of unlimited exposure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-plans-ease-nuclear-liability-laws-attract-foreign-firms-sources-say-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOJNGJYU4NKINJEKBOASN7OKZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本财政部长称日本不会操纵外汇来削弱日元]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣加藤胜信周五对国会表示，日本不会操纵货币市场以削弱日元，他反驳了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于日本故意让本国货币贬值以帮助出口商的指责。【原文：Japan does not manipulate the currency market to weaken the yen, Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato told parliament on Friday, countering accusations from U.S. President Donald Trump that Japan intentionally depreciates its currency to help exporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/japan-does-not-manipulate-fx-weaken-yen-finmin-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HLEIMK5ANO2NGTQEXUQLH2THM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 02:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼称增加美国进口将转移其他地方的订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼首席经济部长艾尔朗加-哈塔托（Airlangga Hartarto）在华盛顿对记者说，印尼增加进口美国食品和商品将意味着印尼目前向其购买这些产品的国家的订单减少。【原文：Increased imports of U.S. food and commodities by Indonesia would mean lower orders from countries that Indonesia currently buys the products from, chief economic minister Airlangga Hartarto told reporters in Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-says-increase-us-imports-would-divert-orders-elsewhere-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCRD732T6VIURHFVLLE4PU4YDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 02:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[IDC 称中国第一季度智能手机出货量同比增长 3.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 IDC 表示，中国第一季度智能手机出货量同比增长 3.3%。【原文：China's smartphone shipments in the first quarter by 3.3% from a year earlier, research firm IDC said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-q1-smartphone-shipments-rise-33-year-earlier-idc-says-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMD3CUPQDBM3XEB2ZZJ3TIR7NE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 02:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将批准美国原住民反对的力拓铜矿土地置换计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普政府周四表示，将批准力拓和必和必拓建设世界最大铜矿之一所需的土地交换，尽管美国原住民担心这会破坏一个具有宗教价值的场所。【原文：The Trump administration said on Thursday it would approve a land swap needed for Rio Tinto and BHP to build one of the world's largest copper mines, despite concerns from Native Americans that it would destroy a site of religious value.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-approve-land-swap-rio-tinto-copper-mine-opposed-by-native-americans-2025-04-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HRFDC6M5DNNZXBBOOHUBBLAJBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本核心通胀加速，使日本央行的利率路径复杂化]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于食品成本持续上升，日本3月份的核心通胀率加速上升，这使得日本央行在权衡价格上涨压力与美国提高关税给经济带来的风险之间的任务变得更加复杂。【原文：Japan's core inflation accelerated in March due to persistent rises in food costs, data showed on Friday, complicating the central bank's task of weighing mounting price pressures against risks to the economy from higher U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/japans-core-inflation-accelerates-complicates-bojs-rate-path-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAZKMSK2UNLI7P5YVUCVMCK5JM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:37:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：备忘录称英特尔首席执行官陈立武精简领导团队，任命新技术主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份陈立武的备忘录，英特尔新任首席执行官陈立武正在精简这家半导体巨头的领导团队，让重要的芯片组直接向他汇报。【原文：Intel's new CEO, Lip-Bu Tan, is streamlining the semiconductor giant's leadership team, with important chip groups reporting directly to him, according to a memo from Tan seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-ceo-lip-bu-tan-streamlines-leadership-team-names-new-technology-chief-memo-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOL4TKELQFMRJFJSGBEQRJWDMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普下令放松对美国渔业的监管]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国白宫周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普发布了一项行政命令，旨在通过指示商务部放松监管和向商业捕捞开放海洋纪念碑来增加国内海产品产量。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump issued an executive order aimed at increasing domestic seafood production by directing the Commerce Department to loosen regulations and by opening up marine monuments to commercial fishing, the White House said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-order-seeks-looser-regulation-us-fishing-industry-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MJCTNGZGIBNBJBFWH33BXKLMNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 22:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉就黑人员工指控其受到普遍骚扰的诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名黑人女员工声称，特斯拉加利福尼亚州弗里蒙特工厂的一名经理有时会用 "欢迎来到种植园 "或 "欢迎来到奴隶屋 "来问候工人，特斯拉已就该员工的种族歧视诉讼达成和解。【原文：Tesla has settled a racial discrimination lawsuit by a Black female employee who claimed a manager at its Fremont, California, plant sometimes greeted workers by saying "welcome to the plantation" or "welcome to the slave house."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-settles-black-employees-lawsuit-alleging-pervasive-harassment-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3THAWNTTPJN7XCADCMTBAYH5DY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 22:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储建议平均大型银行压力测试结果以降低波动性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周四全面启动了对大型银行的年度压力测试的改革工作，建议在制定资本要求时采用两年的平均结果。【原文：The Federal Reserve kicked off a sweeping effort to overhaul its annual stress tests of large banks on Thursday, proposing to average results over two years in setting capital requirements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-proposes-averaging-large-bank-stress-test-results-reduce-volatility-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5EOS5Q2NVPLRKFQM46U5M5EOY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康的盈利表现值得信赖--直到其周四发布令人震惊的财报]]></title><description><![CDATA[自 2008 年全球金融危机以来，UnitedHealth 的盈利从未低于预期，在投资者眼中一直是一家值得信赖的公司。【原文：UnitedHealth has traditionally been a company investors saw as reliable, having not missed earnings estimates since the 2008 global financial crisis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-was-reliable-earnings-performer-until-its-shocking-thursday-results-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D2KRLPCQXNJR7COWLNQWSKENFQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者称摩根大通和美国银行应停止中国 CATL 的首次公开募股工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位共和党议员周四表示，摩根大通和美国银行应退出中国电动汽车电池巨头CATL的首次公开募股工作。【原文：JPMorgan Chase & Co and Bank of America should withdraw from working on the initial public offering of Chinese electric vehicle battery giant CATL , a Republican lawmaker said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-bofa-should-stop-work-ipo-chinas-catl-lawmaker-says-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EE6LO7FTRNIZHDDUBLH46SIERQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国诉讼称特斯拉加速里程表以避免保修维修]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉面临一项集体诉讼提案，该提案声称特斯拉加快了其电动汽车上里程表的速度，使其更快地超出保修期，从而使埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的公司免于支付维修费用。【原文：Tesla faces a proposed class action claiming it speeds up odometers on its electric vehicles so they fall out of warranty faster, saving Elon Musk's company from having to pay for repairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-speeds-up-odometers-avoid-warranty-repairs-us-lawsuit-claims-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RSHYQOZTJ5ITPFQLKOEIXJ45WY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国已就关税问题伸出援手，TikTok 协议或将再等等]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，自美国对从中国进口的商品加征关税以来，中国已主动与美国进行了谈判。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday that China has reached out to talk since the U.S. imposed tariffs on imports from the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/trump-says-china-has-reached-out-tariffs-tiktok-deal-may-wait-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TSMVITWYCFPDPO7HIHIZWUJR74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示怀疑美国钢铁与日本的协议是否会成为与日本贸易谈判的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四表示，美国钢铁公司和新日本制铁公司之间的交易可能是与日本进行关税谈判的一部分，但他补充说，他怀疑会是这样。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday that a deal between U.S. Steel and Nippon Steel could be a part of tariff negotiations with Japan, but added he doubted it would be.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/trump-says-he-doubts-us-steel-nippon-deal-will-be-part-trade-talks-with-japan-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OO6YMALJLVNO5H324FTLIU45WQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：欧洲央行采取行动，特朗普发起攻击]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-graphics-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJ67OGBWJFJVVE23GCKUEH5IKI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体敦促美国监管机构调查其股票空头头寸]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）拥有多数股权的媒体公司特朗普媒体与科技集团（Trump Media & Technology Group）周四表示，已要求美国证券交易委员会（SEC）调查其股票最近的空头头寸。【原文：The media company majority owned by President Donald Trump, Trump Media & Technology Group , said on Thursday it had asked the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to investigate a recent short position in its stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-presses-us-regulator-investigate-short-positions-its-stocks-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4UQ42FPYF5KQ5IKQVNVXVQKJT4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:06:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 季度业绩超出华尔街目标，收入前景乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Netflix 的季度业绩超出华尔街预期，并提出了乐观的收入展望，在唐纳德-特朗普总统反复无常的关税计划所带来的经济不确定性中显示出信心。【原文：Netflix exceeded Wall Street expectations for quarterly results and offered a bullish revenue outlook on Thursday, signaling confidence amid the economic uncertainty surrounding President Donald Trump's erratic tariff plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-quarterly-results-beat-wall-st-targets-revenue-outlook-upbeat-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MNMUDQNSTVM5LISXBEVME3JONQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackstone 另类投资部门 BXMA 第一季度报告增长 2.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为全球最大的对冲基金投资者，黑石集团的多元资产投资部门 BXMA 在第一季度获得了 2.3% 的扣除费用后回报率，远远超过 HFRX 全球对冲基金指数 0.53% 的回报率。【原文：Blackstone Group's multi-asset investing BXMA unit, the world's largest investor in hedge funds, posted a 2.3% return after fees in the first quarter, handily outpacing the HFRX Global Hedge Fund Index 0.53% return.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackstones-alternatives-unit-bxma-reports-23-gain-q1-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6WGLA4SC5L45FIKCT2RGMM7A4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说：对谷歌非法广告技术垄断的裁决意味着什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国法官裁定谷歌在广告技术领域存在非法垄断，这为美国检察官寻求与谷歌分手埋下了伏笔。以下是此案涉及的内容以及谷歌所有者 Alphabet 今后将面临的问题。【原文：A U.S. judge's ruling that Google has illegal monopolies in ad technology sets up the possibility of U.S. prosecutors seeking a breakup. Here's what the case involves and what Google owner Alphabet faces from here.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/what-does-ruling-googles-illegal-ad-tech-monopoly-mean-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RENT7HIMCVNNVDX6TC4YI7GEZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Coindesk 报道，Kraken 在首次公开募股前裁员数百人]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Coindesk 周四报道，加密货币交易所 Kraken 在过去几个月中已在其所有业务领域裁员数百人，以便在计划上市前精简业务。【原文：Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken has laid off hundreds of employees in the past several months across all areas of its business to streamline its operations ahead of its planned IPO, Coindesk reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kraken-lays-off-hundreds-ahead-ipo-coindesk-reports-2025-04-17/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WQH6TOHBGRJM7N222AN6TFZZOU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>