<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:04:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:04:56 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马主计长办公室就长江和记续约一事提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马总审计长周一表示，巴拿马总审计长办公室将对授权香港长江和记在 2021 年延长巴拿马运河附近两个重要港口 25 年特许经营权的官员提起诉讼。【原文：Panama's Comptroller General office will introduce a lawsuit against the officials who authorized the renewal in 2021 of a 25-year concession to Hong-Kong based CK Hutchison for the operation of two key ports near the Panama Canal, the comptroller general said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/panamas-comptroller-office-sue-over-renewal-ck-hutchison-contract-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZSIJQLWUBPBJMZNLGXYYXNUYM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国环保局批准得克萨斯州第一口二氧化碳注入井]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国环保署周一向西方石油公司（Occidental）颁发了得克萨斯州首张允许钻井注入和储存二氧化碳的许可证。【原文：The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency on Monday issued Texas' first permit to allow drilling to inject and store carbon dioxide to oil company Occidental .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-epa-approves-texas-first-co2-injection-well-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B3U7B4S45RI2BOVGM24P5LO6UY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融科技公司陷入关税动荡]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 和 "先买后付 "服务提供商 Affirm 等金融科技公司卷入了美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面关税漩涡，在对消费者财务状况恶化的担忧中股价大幅下挫。【原文：Financial technology companies like Robinhood and buy now, pay later provider Affirm have been caught in the whirlwind of President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs, sending shares sharply downward amid fears about worsening consumer finances.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/fintech-companies-caught-up-tariff-turmoil-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DO5YLUSL3ZMCJMDNUAVJCGPK6M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[布伦特原油期货和期权交易量创历史新高，石油市场陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[洲际交易所（ICE）的布伦特原油期货和期权合约交易量周五创下历史新高，超过了 COVID-19 大流行期间的水平，因为投资者正在为全球贸易战和欧佩克+石油增产做准备。【原文：Brent crude futures and options contracts traded on the Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) hit record volumes on Friday, surpassing levels seen during the COVID-19 pandemic as investors braced for a global trade war and OPEC+ oil output hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brent-futures-options-volumes-surpass-pandemic-record-oil-market-reels-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F7VGRZRY7ZPAXA2CK7PA2NQRZM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:47:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：特朗普的关税大棒仍在挥舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BTTRR52YG5LNBAZ5HICPPN5SXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在供应商提出质疑后，航空航天公司就关税问题审查合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内消息人士周一表示，在一家美国主要供应商引发了关于谁应为新出现的贸易战买单的争论后，飞机制造商、航空公司和供应商正在梳理价值数十亿美元的合同，以检查他们所面临的关税风险。【原文：Planemakers, airlines and suppliers are combing through billions of dollars worth of contracts to check their exposure to tariffs after a major U.S. supplier sparked debate over who should pay for an emerging trade war, industry sources said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/aerospace-firms-scour-contracts-over-tariffs-after-supplier-challenge-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFF6D6SLCJOG7I6ZX5HY5LTVN4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与印度讨论关税问题及 "公平 "贸易的进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院表示，美国国务卿马尔科-卢比奥（Marco Rubio）和印度外交部长苏布拉哈曼亚姆-杰尚卡尔（Subrahmanyam Jaishankar）周一举行了电话会谈，讨论美国对印度征收关税的问题以及如何朝着 "公平和平衡的贸易关系 "迈进。【原文：U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio and Indian Foreign Minister Subrahmanyam Jaishankar held a call on Monday to discuss U.S. tariffs on India and how to make progress towards a "fair and balanced trade relationship," the State Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-india-discuss-tariffs-progress-towards-fair-trade-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNM2W5Y6CZKSHOFH4VZMYAPFRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:51:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫命令各机构任命首席人工智能官，以扩大人工智能的使用范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫管理和预算办公室周一表示，它正在命令联邦机构任命首席人工智能官，以扩大政府对人工智能的使用。【原文：The White House Office of Management and Budget said on Monday it is ordering federal agencies to name chief AI officers as it looks to expand the government's use of artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/white-house-orders-agencies-name-chief-ai-officers-it-expands-use-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFZ5ZABB6VLPBD533LIWX7UXYA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[遭受关税打击的华尔街不禁要问：特朗普会眨眼吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的最新关税政策导致华尔街股市暴跌超过 10%，投资者正试图找出他对股市损失的容忍度，一些投资者仍对最终的宽松抱有希望。【原文：Investors are trying to game out how much tolerance U.S. President Donald Trump has for stock market losses after his latest tariff policies ignited a more than 10% wipeout on Wall Street, with some still holding out hope of eventual relief.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-tariffs-trump-analysis-pix-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBQ7KW3T3RKHPOHKAROMABHDUE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:38:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MercadoLibre 今年将在巴西投资 58 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[拉丁美洲电子商务巨头 MercadoLibre 周一表示，计划今年在其第一大市场巴西投资 340 亿雷亚尔（约合 58 亿美元），支出比去年同期增长 47.8%。【原文：Latin American e-commerce giant MercadoLibre said on Monday it plans to invest 34 billion reais ($5.8 billion) this year in its top market, Brazil, representing a 47.8% increase in spending from a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mercadolibre-invest-58-billion-brazil-this-year-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZRJS3ELUZVPHXPRZCXU5IZ4VBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:36:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英飞凌科技将以 25 亿美元收购 Marvell 的自动以太网业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国芯片制造商英飞凌科技公司（Infineon Technologies）周一表示，将以约 25 亿美元现金收购 Marvell Technology 公司的汽车以太网业务，以扩大其微控制器业务部门。【原文：German chipmaker Infineon Technologies said on Monday it would buy Marvell Technology's automotive ethernet business for about $2.5 billion in cash, to expand its microcontroller segment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/infineon-technologies-buy-marvells-auto-ethernet-business-25-billion-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DATDDQ66LJN23K4CJZVDS7SRZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[博通宣布 100 亿美元股票回购计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[博通公司（Broadcom）周一表示，将启动一项新的股票回购计划，在 12 月 31 日前回购高达 100 亿美元的股票。【原文：Broadcom said on Monday it was launching a new share buyback program of up to $10 billion through December 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/broadcom-announces-10-billion-share-buyback-plan-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WBJKD4T35VNAVEMLCLRD4MNFQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[牛仔布需求稳定，Levi Strauss 季度销售额超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[李维-施特劳斯（Levi Strauss）周一公布的第一季度营收超过预期，并维持全年业绩预期，该公司寄希望于其牛仔服装的稳定需求和多样化的供应链，以应对不断升级的贸易战对鞋类和服装零售商的冲击。【原文：Levi Strauss beat first-quarter revenue estimates on Monday and maintained its full-year forecast, betting on steady demand for its denims and a diverse supply chain to navigate an escalating trade war that has hit footwear and apparel retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/levi-strauss-beats-quarterly-sales-estimates-steady-denim-demand-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5VIRSR6ONZL6LN3A5KZ6HXZBSQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西能源部长要求巴西国家石油公司首席执行官考虑下调柴油价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位知情人士周一告诉路透社，巴西矿产和能源部长要求巴西国家石油公司（Petrobras）首席执行官考虑对出售给巴西经销商的柴油平均价格进行新一轮下调。【原文：Brazil's mines and energy minister asked Petrobras Chief Executive to have the state-run oil firm consider a new cut in the average price of diesel sold to distributors in Brazil, a source with knowledge of the matter told Reuters on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazils-energy-minister-asks-petrobras-ceo-consider-diesel-price-cut-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOMFX2ALDZIA7HGUKPWOZ5QYF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:15:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称日本将派团队参加会谈，日本敦促他重新考虑关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示，日本将派出一个团队就贸易问题进行谈判，并补充说他在周一早些时候与日本首相石破茂（Shigeru Ishiba）进行了会谈，石破茂曾单独表示他让特朗普重新考虑关税政策。【原文：Japan is sending a team to negotiate on trade, U.S. President Donald Trump said, adding that he spoke earlier on Monday with Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba, who separately said he told Trump to rethink tariff policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/trump-says-japan-sending-team-talks-japan-urges-him-rethink-tariffs-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPK3Y3F6BVJZTPTLNRQXQJZZVY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普表示不会暂停关税，将与中国谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周一表示，他不希望暂停征收关税，以便与贸易伙伴进行谈判，但他表示将与中国、日本和其他国家就关税问题进行谈判。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday he was not looking at a pause on tariffs to allow for negotiations with trading partners but said he would talk to China, Japan and other countries about the duties.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-not-looking-tariff-pause-will-talk-china-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S45P3E4GCJJXNOYFV5E67O662Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 19:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部长贝森特将主持与日本的贸易谈判 - 日经新闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《日经新闻》周二报道，美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特将领导与日本的贸易谈判。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent will lead trade negotiations with Japan, the Nikkei newspaper reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-treasury-secretary-bessent-head-trade-talks-with-japan-nikkei-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I4CXLFSZMBJGPHVPEWCYHWGABU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 19:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利 Codelco 公司提高铜产量，董事长看好贸易战前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国有铜生产商科德尔科公司（Codelco）董事长马克西莫-帕切科（Maximo Pacheco）周一表示，尽管中美贸易战不断升级，但该公司在2025年前三个月提高了产量，并仍然看好全球需求的长期前景。【原文：Codelco, Chile's state-owned copper producer, boosted production in the first three months of 2025 and was still bullish about long-term prospects for global demand despite an escalating trade war between the U.S. and China, Chairman Maximo Pacheco said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chiles-codelco-boosts-copper-output-chairman-bullish-despite-trade-war-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5VYI4XFHZPQFLHECPYTDQYY74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 19:03:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与巴基斯坦讨论关税、重要矿产和移民问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务院和巴基斯坦外交部分别发表声明说，美国国务卿马可-鲁比奥周一与巴基斯坦外交部长伊沙克-达尔就关税、贸易关系、移民和关键矿产的接触前景等问题进行了交谈。【原文：U.S. Secretary of State Marco Rubio spoke to Pakistani Foreign Minister Ishaq Dar on Monday about tariffs, trade relations, immigration and prospects for engagement on critical minerals, the State Department and Pakistan's foreign ministry said a separate statements.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-discusses-tariffs-critical-minerals-immigration-with-pakistan-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHVRH7LITRPD7C4GKUTRF4AXPM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，欧盟委员会建议对部分美国进口商品征收 25% 的反关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份文件显示，欧盟委员会周一提议对一系列美国商品征收25%的反关税，以回应唐纳德-特朗普总统征收钢铝关税。【原文：The European Commission proposed counter-tariffs of 25% on a range of U.S. goods on Monday in response to President Donald Trump's tariffs on steel and aluminium, a document seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/eu-commission-proposes-25-counter-tariffs-some-us-imports-document-shows-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GV2Z5YZ4B5IKNDYAIMNOMC557I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[分析师报告称，Traton 警告美国卡车司机因担心经济衰退而推迟订单]]></title><description><![CDATA[据伯恩斯坦研究公司（Bernstein Research）的一份分析报告称，大众汽车的卡车部门Traton周一在与投资者的通话中表示，由于担心全球经济衰退，美国的卡车司机正在推迟订单。【原文：Truckers in the United States are deferring orders over fears of a global recession, Volkswagen's truck unit Traton said in a call with investors on Monday, according to an analyst note by Bernstein Research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/traton-warns-us-truckers-deferring-orders-over-recession-fears-analyst-note-says-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBYJV2OOHVNIDI4H5U3ICXRESI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[智利监管机构：中美贸易战迫在眉睫，铜价可能已见顶]]></title><description><![CDATA[智利国家铜业委员会（Cochilco）周一表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要进一步提高对中国的关税，在贸易战不断升级的情况下，红色金属的价格很可能已经在今年达到顶峰。【原文：Chile's state copper commission Cochilco on Monday said that prices for the red metal have likely already peaked this year amid an escalating trade war, as U.S. President Donald Trump threatened to further increase tariffs on China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chile-regulator-copper-prices-have-likely-peaked-us-china-trade-war-looms-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSRHWQVMHRJ5NCNWD4AEB6ETNM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:12:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[希腊股市可能重获梦寐以求的 "发达市场 "徽章]]></title><description><![CDATA[希腊股票本周可能重新获得指数提供商富时罗素（FTSE Russell）梦寐以求的发达市场地位--这是该国在长达十年的债务危机后恢复正常的关键一步，此举可能刺激数百万美元的资金流入。【原文：Greek equities could regain the coveted developed market status by index provider FTSE Russell this week - a key step on the country's return to normalcy following a decade-long debt crisis and a move that could spur millions of dollars in inflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/greek-stocks-could-regain-coveted-developed-market-badge-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UYJYPGWZOBLQFHPOTVV5JR2WXU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官称股市跌幅可能扩大 20%，经济可能陷入衰退]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德首席执行官拉里-芬克（Larry Fink）周一表示，由于美国征收巨额关税，股市可能会扩大20%的跌幅，并指出经济很可能已经陷入衰退。【原文：BlackRock CEO Larry Fink on Monday said stock markets could extend their decline by 20% as the U.S. imposes steep tariffs, noting the economy is probably already in a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/blackrock-ceo-says-stocks-could-extend-fall-by-20-economy-probably-recession-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRJ57ZYQLVMEFOHAEQOT2Z5UGA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球市场陷入崩溃：图表为证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收关税对经济造成破坏的担忧不断升温，一场规模空前的股市暴跌席卷全球，主要市场损失超过 10 万亿美元。【原文：A stock market rout, historic in scale, has swept across the globe wiping more than $10 trillion off major markets, as concerns about the economic damage unleashed by U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs spiral.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/breakingviews/global-markets-selloff-graphic-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEGA47OOPRMGHIQNCTVAKXFJRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:24:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒：确保通胀率不上升是首要任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周一表示，近期商品和市场服务通胀的部分上升可能是对特朗普政府当前政策效果的 "预期"，并补充说，控制通胀是美联储的 "首要任务"。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler on Monday said that some of the recent rise in goods and market-services inflation may be "anticipatory" of the effect of the Trump administration's current policies, adding that it's a "priority" for the Fed to keep inflation in check.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kugler-making-sure-inflation-doesnt-rise-is-priority-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSKEYSAQHVJT3OTK7Y2YW625RY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DailyPay 在纽约提起诉讼，以挫败因工人薪资产品而面临的诉讼威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[DailyPay公司提供了一种让工人更快地领取工资以换取费用的产品，该公司周一起诉了纽约州总检察长莱蒂西亚-詹姆斯（Letitia James），以阻止一项声称该产品是非法贷款的潜在诉讼。【原文：DailyPay, which offers a product that lets workers collect paychecks faster in exchange for a fee, sued New York Attorney General Letitia James on Monday to thwart a potential lawsuit claiming the product is an illegal loan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/dailypay-sues-new-york-thwart-threatened-lawsuit-over-worker-pay-product-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L4RCC22FQFKI5BDQKNUKP44ONE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼日利亚法院延期至 4 月 30 日审理 Binance 高管逃税案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Binance 的一名律师周一表示，尼日利亚一家法院已将针对 Binance 的逃税案延期至 4 月 30 日，以允许当地税务机关回应该加密货币交易所提出的一项请求，即废除通过电子邮件向其送达法庭文件的命令。【原文：A Nigerian court has adjourned a tax evasion case against Binance to April 30 to allow the local tax authority to respond to a request by the cryptocurrency exchange to annul an order for court documents to be served on it by email, a lawyer for Binance said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/nigerian-court-adjourns-binance-executives-tax-evasion-trial-april-30-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B2VQDXMKVBMIVPRSQYPFPFDACQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称银行业高层就特朗普关税影响举行会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的消息人士称，包括摩根大通和美国银行在内的一些全球顶级银行的首席执行官周日举行了一次电话会议，讨论美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）公布的巨额关税所带来的影响。【原文：The CEOs of some of the top global banks, including JPMorgan Chase and Bank of America , held a call on Sunday to discuss the repercussions of the hefty tariffs unveiled by President Donald Trump, sources familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/top-banking-chiefs-held-talks-over-trump-tariff-fallout-sources-say-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">H46FQIRFT5PB3KXJSVUZD2JWYQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国商务部长卢特尼克在关税宣布一天后与银行首席执行官讨论了关税问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉此次会议的消息人士透露，美国最大银行的负责人周四与商务部长霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）举行了会晤，讨论了唐纳德-特朗普总统在关税计划宣布一天后提出的全面关税计划。【原文：The heads of the U.S.'s largest banks met with Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick on Thursday to discuss President Donald Trump's sweeping tariff plans a day after they were announced, according to a source familiar with the meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-discussed-tariffs-with-bank-ceos-one-day-after-2025-04-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OEQRLWTHRNKZ5ABV5DS4WDG2JM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>