<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:17:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:17:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Workday预测2027年年度订阅收入低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Workday周二预测其2027财年订阅收入将低于华尔街预期，因经济不确定性导致企业削减技术支出，拖累新客户获取。【原文：Workday forecast its fiscal 2027 subscription revenue below Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, as corporations cut technology spending amid economic uncertainty, weighing on new client wins.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/workday-forecasts-2027-annual-subscription-revenue-below-estimates-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UMPZIN3MSVNUZHXU3PDV2XYU4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:09:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucid第四季度营收超预期，预测2026年产量将大幅增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[电动汽车制造商Lucid周二公布的第四季度营收超出华尔街预期，并预测今年产量增幅可能超过50%。该公司正加速生产新近推出的Gravity运动型多功能车，同时准备推出一款全新中型车型。【原文：Electric vehicle maker Lucid beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter revenue on Tuesday and forecast a production rise that could top 50% this year as it ramps up its recently launched Gravity sport utility vehicles and prepares to roll out a new, mid-sized vehicle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lucid-beats-fourth-quarter-revenue-forecasts-jump-2026-production-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B4P2UKAHPFJMZK74W5NHLND43I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 21:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻报道称，Stripe正考虑收购PayPal全部或部分业务。]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻周二援引知情人士消息报道称，支付公司Stripe正考虑收购PayPal全部或部分业务。【原文：Payments firm Stripe is considering an acquisition of all or parts of PayPal , Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/stripe-is-considering-acquisition-all-or-parts-paypal-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DT2A2YTVSZMQFDQYR6FKFPQ3HQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片初创企业SambaNova在由Vista领投的融资轮中筹集3.5亿美元，并与英特尔达成合作协议。]]></title><description><![CDATA[桑巴诺瓦系统公司周二宣布，已完成新一轮3.5亿美元融资，并与英特尔达成合作协议，旨在把握人工智能应用领域对推理芯片激增的需求。【原文：SambaNova Systems said on Tuesday it has raised $350 million in a new funding round and struck a partnership with Intel as it seeks to capitalise on surging demand for inference chips used in artificial intelligence applications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-chip-startup-sambanova-raises-350-million-vista-led-round-signs-intel-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GLOFBHTBRBLFHFNRUQM4LQRO5A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:42:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽蒙特将向阿根廷Cerro Negro项目投资8亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷经济部长路易斯·卡普托周二表示，黄金生产商纽蒙特公司将向该国塞罗内格罗矿投资约8亿美元。【原文：Gold producer Newmont will invest approximately $800 million in Argentina's Cerro Negro mine, the country's Economy Minister, Luis Caputo, said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/newmont-invest-800-million-argentinas-cerro-negro-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBA6KYLCK5NX7E5WUROCAUFO6A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅、戴森、博视眼科成为最新申请特朗普关税退税的企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[法庭文件显示，法国美妆集团欧莱雅、英国吸尘器制造商戴森以及隐形眼镜制造商博视眼科成为最新一批要求退还关税的企业。此前美国最高法院裁定特朗普总统实施的紧急贸易措施所征收的关税违法，这些企业紧随其后提起诉讼。【原文：French beauty group L'Oreal , British vacuum manufacturer Dyson and contact lens maker Bausch + Lomb became the latest corporations to sue for refunds of tariffs paid under President Donald Trump’s emergency trade measures, days after the U.S. Supreme Court ruled the duties unlawful, court filings showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/loreal-dyson-bausch-lomb-become-latest-sue-trump-tariff-refunds-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNOMPLIOVJMVFPYLX633SHML2U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高露洁棕榄公司计划捍卫董事会遴选中的DEI标准，信函显示]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社获得的一封信函显示，高露洁棕榄公司告知国家法律与政策中心，其计划呼吁投资者投票反对保守派股东团体提出的提案。该提案旨在删除公司在董事会成员遴选过程中与多元化、公平与包容（DEI）相关的标准。【原文：Colgate-Palmolive told the National Legal and Policy Center that it intends to ask investors to vote against the conservative shareholder group's proposal to remove DEI-related criteria in the company's selection process for its board members, according to a letter viewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/colgate-palmolive-plans-defend-dei-criteria-board-selection-letter-shows-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCN4X6YSNRM35CQ7UJZ2TTHH24</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，人类中心论在与五角大楼的争执中坚持己见]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周二透露，人工智能实验室Anthropic无意放宽其军事用途的使用限制。此前该公司与五角大楼举行会议，商讨其未来发展方向。【原文：Artificial intelligence lab Anthropic has no intention of easing its usage restrictions for military purposes, a person familiar with the matter said on Tuesday, following a meeting to discuss its future with the Pentagon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/anthropic-digs-heels-dispute-with-pentagon-source-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAJQFKP3FZIQBKQOO37XKHYMY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永利度假村称黑客窃取员工数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[永利度假村周二表示，黑客已获取员工数据，公司正在调查此次数据泄露事件。【原文：Wynn Resorts on Tuesday said hackers had obtained employee data and that the company was investigating the breach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/wynn-resorts-says-hackers-acquired-employee-data-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEACZRNTOJIFLHOPSHTE3RUKN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员称，中国尚未收到任何英伟达H200芯片。]]></title><description><![CDATA[None of Nvidia's second most advanced AI chips, known as the H200, have been sold to Chinese customers so far, a U.S. Commerce Department official said on Tuesday.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/china-has-not-yet-received-any-nvidia-h200-chips-us-official-said-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSCWUHKJPFLHXABN4WXPT7CKMU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官暂时驳回xAI针对竞争对手OpenAI的商业秘密诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[加州一名联邦法官周二驳回了埃隆·马斯克旗下人工智能初创公司xAI的诉讼请求，该诉讼指控竞争对手山姆·阿尔特曼的OpenAI窃取其商业机密。【原文：A federal judge in California on Tuesday dismissed a lawsuit from Elon Musk's artificial intelligence startup xAI that accused rival Sam Altman's OpenAI of stealing its trade secrets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-judge-dismisses-xai-trade-secrets-lawsuit-against-rival-openai-now-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62KY4PDDLNO2VOK2IJUHJGXPGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 20:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为可能加剧焦虑的国情咨文演讲做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[特朗普总统周二晚间的国情咨文演讲正值投资者处于关键时刻——他们近月来饱受市场动荡冲击，亟需稳定局面。【原文：The State of the Union speech from President Donald Trump on Tuesday evening comes at a pivotal point for investors, sideswiped by market turbulence in recent months and craving stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/investors-brace-state-union-speech-that-may-fuel-anxiety-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZ6EDZ3OCBL3RHAIDYF47ODP7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:53:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国液化天然气霸主地位持续巩固，首船货运十周年之际]]></title><description><![CDATA[自首船液化天然气（LNG）从得克萨斯州出口以来，十年的时间里，美国已迅速发展成为全球消费者最主要的超低温燃料供应国。【原文：In the ten years since the first export cargo of liquefied natural gas (LNG) left Texas, the United States has grown rapidly into the top supplier of the ultra-cooled fuel to world consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ten-years-after-first-cargo-us-lng-dominance-set-keep-growing-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LTR32WYTZBMS3DUARWEREIZ7LY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能会计初创公司Basis以11.5亿美元估值完成1亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能会计初创公司Basis在B轮融资中筹集了1亿美元，公司估值达11.5亿美元。随着投资者纷纷向能够自主处理复杂任务的智能代理系统注入资金，该领域正迎来发展热潮。【原文：AI accounting startup Basis has raised $100 million in a Series B round valuing the company at $1.15 billion, as investors pour money into agentic AI systems designed to operate autonomously on complex tasks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ai-accounting-startup-basis-raises-100-million-115-billion-valuation-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PM2IBUPPRJLYXBMQU5VBYHW6D4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据Axios报道，赫格塞斯要求Anthropic在周五之前撤回其人工智能安全措施。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据Axios周二报道，美国国防部长皮特·赫格塞斯已要求人工智能公司Anthropic在周五之前撤回其军用产品的安全保障措施。【原文：U.S. Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has given artificial intelligence company Anthropic until Friday to back down on safeguards for its products used by the military, Axios reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hegseth-gives-anthropic-until-friday-back-down-ai-safeguards-axios-reports-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4MNM7BKOVNA5OBZ7TT7XMRPFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:37:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银任命戈利亚领导美国财富管理顾问团队]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周二获得的一份内部备忘录显示，瑞银集团（UBS）于3月1日任命丽莎·戈利亚（Lisa Golia）领导其美国财富管理顾问团队，此前她已担任该业务首席运营官两年。【原文：UBS promoted Lisa Golia to lead its U.S. wealth management advisers in the field on March 1 after serving as chief operating officer for the business over the last two years, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-promotes-golia-lead-wealth-management-advisers-us-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VHPVTTGH6VJGPKETADSGEDMYY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲人工智能芯片初创企业Axelera再获2.5亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[Axelera AI has secured $250 million in a funding round led by Innovation Industries that included BlackRock and SiteGround Capital as new investors, it said on Tuesday, marking one of the largest investments to date in a European AI chipmaking firm.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-ai-chip-startup-axelera-raises-additional-250-million-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZHIBFRRSROPJFC2DW3RVEERRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:16:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士央行行长表示，全球多数经济体应对关税的状况好于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长马丁·施莱格尔周二表示，美国关税政策和不确定性因素已对全球经济增长构成压力，但经济诸多领域展现出超出预期的韧性。【原文：U.S. tariffs and uncertainty have weighed on global economic growth, but many parts of the economy have proved more resilient than expected, Swiss National Bank Chairman Martin Schlegel said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/much-world-economy-has-coped-better-than-expected-with-tariffs-snb-chairman-says-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KHCRF2FKWNJDDKZGNQEIJ7NPHI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对印度、印尼和老挝的太阳能产品征收初步关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周一宣布，对印度、印度尼西亚和老挝企业进口的太阳能电池和太阳能电池板征收反补贴税。【原文：The U.S. Commerce Department on Monday announced anti-subsidy countervailing duties on solar cells and panels imported by companies in India, Indonesia and Laos.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-sets-preliminary-duties-solar-imports-india-indonesia-laos-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGRHQ3B4IRM4NOMBHSU5J2LQNY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，资产管理公司纽伯格伯曼正探索保险业务，此举是行业推动的一部分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，纽伯格伯曼正考虑扩大其保险业务能力，这凸显了保险资产对寻求新收入来源和提升回报的资产管理公司持续具有吸引力。【原文：Neuberger Berman is exploring a potential expansion of its insurance capabilities, people familiar with the matter said, highlighting the ongoing allure of insurance assets for money managers seeking new revenue streams and boosted returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/money-manager-neuberger-berman-explores-insurance-venture-part-industry-push-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33EWPUIOMNOGLJ76PNWTM5U7RY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:42:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利监管机构禁止亚马逊物流部门使用员工个人数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利隐私监管机构周二表示，已禁止亚马逊意大利物流公司（AMZN.O）使用其位于罗马东北部帕索科雷塞物流中心1800名员工的个人信息。【原文：Italy's privacy authority said on Tuesday it had banned Amazon Italia Logistica AMZN.O from using personal information of 1,800 workers at its Passo Corese logistics centre, north-east of Rome.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/italy-watchdog-bans-amazon-unit-using-staff-personal-data-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KINUQAIOARMT3PDEHJGJSXLGCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[标普500指数有望年底前上涨10%，但贸易和人工智能颠覆性影响的担忧依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，尽管市场持续担忧美国总统特朗普的贸易政策及人工智能带来的冲击，但受强劲盈利和经济稳步增长推动，标普500指数将在今年剩余时间内上涨约10%。【原文：The S&amp;P 500 stock index will gain about 10% between now and the end of the year, driven by strong earnings and steady economic growth despite ongoing worries about U.S. President Donald Trump's trade policies and disruption from artificial intelligence, according to a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sp-500-poised-gain-10-by-year-end-trade-ai-disruption-concerns-persist-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QQ3LV6LZ3NP5BCG5EWNIUJXUDU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大会在校园枪击案后向OpenAI安全官员施压]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大政府部长表示，在发现ChatGPT开发商OpenAI未就其封禁的涉嫌大规模枪击案嫌疑人账户向警方通报后，加拿大将于周二就安全协议问题向OpenAI官员施压。【原文：Canada will press OpenAI officials on Tuesday about their safety protocols after it emerged the ChatGPT maker did not contact police about an account it banned belonging to an alleged mass shooter, a government minister said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-press-openai-safety-officials-wake-school-shooting-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNHLUCCTUZJNPNB3ETH6EFSECY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铝业巨头美国铝业公司寻求将10处厂区出售给数据中心运营商]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国铝业公司（Alcoa Corp）首席执行官周二表示，该公司正计划向数据中心行业出售10处已关闭或缩减产能的工厂，首笔交易将于6月底前完成。【原文：U.S. aluminium company Alcoa Corp is looking to sell 10 of its closed or curtailed sites to the data centre industry, with the first sale set to be completed by the end of June, its CEO said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/aluminium-maker-alcoa-seeks-sell-10-sites-data-centres-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SH74CRSMJNMVZHZTGKNHRYKRAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国坚信其与美国的贸易协议依然有效，尽管特朗普政府最新采取了关税措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[British trade minister Peter Kyle said he was confident the trade deal Britain struck last year with the United States would still stand despite U.S. President Donald Trump's latest move to apply a 10% global import tariff.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-confident-its-trade-deal-with-us-still-stands-despite-latest-trump-tariff-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RRY2P6CFWNKZRL25HCN4DGXH4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[精神航空公司与贷款方达成协议，成功脱离破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司周二表示，已与贷款方达成协议，这将帮助其在今春晚些时候或初夏摆脱破产困境。【原文：Spirit Airlines said on Tuesday it has reached an agreement with its lenders that will help it emerge from bankruptcy by late spring or early summer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spirit-airlines-seals-deal-with-lenders-emerge-bankruptcy-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WYLC3LZQLZO4XAZ4NDHZEIEDFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[若价格僵局持续，科特迪瓦未售可可库存将激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业专家和全球贸易高管表示，除非政府下调国家监管的农民收购价以促进农民向贸易商销售，否则到3月底主要可可作物收成结束时，科特迪瓦将积压约20万吨未售出的可可。【原文：Ivory Coast will have accumulated about 200,000 metric tons of unsold cocoa by end-March when its main crop concludes unless the government cuts state-regulated farmer prices in order to unlock sales from farmers to traders, industry experts and global trading executives said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/ivory-coast-unsold-cocoa-stocks-set-soar-if-price-standoff-persists-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDJFRTGIEZLRFFBEBAUCQHKS7Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国软件股上涨，Anthropic公告引发市场反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shares of U.S. software companies that entered into partnerships with AI startup Anthropic on Tuesday helped lead a rebound in the sector that has been hammered by fears about the disruptive impact of artificial intelligence.]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-software-stocks-climb-anthropic-announcement-sparks-relief-rally-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OU7JHEIJ2FKVFAJOE3RHUT4WJM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:46:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员称，在特朗普加征关税后，欧盟将面临与美国的过渡期]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易专员马罗什·谢夫乔维奇周二表示，在特朗普总统实施新的进口附加费后，欧盟与美国的关系将面临为期数月的"过渡期"，这可能危及双方去年达成的贸易协议。【原文：The European Union is facing a "transitional period" of a few months in relations with the U.S. after President Donald Trump's new import surcharge, which threatens to undermine the trade deal the two sides struck last year, European Trade Commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-faces-transition-period-with-us-after-trump-tariff-move-says-eu-trade-chief-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYLGJGWJT5NWBI6IIX2RCMDYCM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉被控招聘存在反美偏见，美国法官裁定必须应诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国一名法官拒绝驳回指控特斯拉在招聘中歧视美国公民、以便支付更低薪资给外国工人的诉讼，但表示对提起诉讼的软件工程师能否胜诉持怀疑态度。【原文：A U.S. judge has refused to dismiss a lawsuit accusing Tesla of discriminating against American citizens in hiring so it can pay less to foreign workers, but said he was skeptical that the software engineer who sued would prevail.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/tesla-must-face-lawsuit-alleging-anti-american-bias-hiring-us-judge-rules-2026-02-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERVAA7DF4NKDDFXSDOLHVW7254</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>