<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:06:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:06:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[吉尔吉斯斯坦禁止网络色情，打击互联网自由]]></title><description><![CDATA[吉尔吉斯斯坦总统萨迪尔-贾帕罗夫的办公室周二表示，根据总统签署的新法律，吉尔吉斯斯坦已禁止访问网上色情内容，并对互联网流量实施国家控制。【原文：Kyrgyzstan has banned access to online pornography and imposed state control over internet traffic under new laws signed by President Sadyr Japarov, his office said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/kyrgyzstan-bans-online-porn-crackdown-internet-freedoms-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F76OVUM7FRPY7KVUJVJAGYT4Z4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:52:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[皇家加勒比因邮轮需求稳定而上调年度利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[皇家加勒比公司周二上调了年度利润预期，原因是市场对该游轮运营商的高端私人岛屿目的地和优质航次的需求具有弹性。【原文：Royal Caribbean raised its annual profit forecast on Tuesday, banking on resilient demand for the cruise operator's high-end private island destinations and premium sailings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/royal-caribbean-lifts-annual-profit-forecast-steady-cruise-demand-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZA7JAEMTRIRJIB73WHIZUAZ6E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝克休斯将以 136 亿美元收购 Chart Industries]]></title><description><![CDATA[石油和天然气设备供应商贝克休斯周二表示，将以 136 亿美元的全现金交易（包括债务）收购 Chart Industries，击败竞争对手 Flowserve .【原文：Oil and gas equipment supplier Baker Hughes said on Tuesday it would acquire Chart Industries in a $13.6 billion all-cash deal, including debt, edging out rival suitor Flowserve .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/baker-hughes-buy-chart-industries-136-billion-deal-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCCFJM2SINODPO7TJDD5GQUFKA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[微软的人工智能优势受到质疑，OpenAI 转向竞争对手寻求云服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[在周三的财报中，微软的投资者将面临一个大问题：随着合作伙伴OpenAI转向竞争对手谷歌、甲骨文和CoreWeave寻求云服务，微软的人工智能优势是否面临风险？【原文：Microsoft investors head into Wednesday's earnings with one big question: is the company's artificial intelligence edge at risk as partner OpenAI turns to rivals Google, Oracle and CoreWeave for cloud services?】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/microsofts-ai-edge-under-scrutiny-openai-turns-rivals-cloud-services-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72G3OE2IRVMPJEIOQNORN6QZN4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:41:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富士康将于 7 月 30 日暂停股票交易，等待重大公告]]></title><description><![CDATA[富士康（又称鸿海精密工业）表示，将于 7 月 30 日暂停股票交易，以待发布重大公告。【原文：Foxconn, also known as Hon Hai Precision Industry , said it will suspend share trading on July 30 pending a major announcement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/foxconn-suspend-share-trading-july-30-pending-major-announcement-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZF6VYLQIRKZ5HUX6TAYOJZSRE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[捷蓝航空与美联航合作获美国交通部批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空（JetBlue）和美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）周二表示，美国运输部（DOT）已通过对其蓝天合作计划的审查，允许它们继续实施蓝天合作计划。【原文：JetBlue and United Airlines have cleared a review of their planned Blue Sky partnership by the U.S. Department of Transportation (DOT) allowing them to proceed with the implementation, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/jetblue-united-partnership-gets-go-ahead-us-transportation-department-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZP6F3SLLUFP6BH2RJRCLRNCEGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美元重新焕发活力]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国和全球市场的重要事件【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZKSR3IK6ZROM3KQPCSVN6OQK7U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于中国市场对加卫苗的需求依然疲软，默克将裁员减支]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中国市场对加卫苗（Gardasil）的需求持续疲软，默克公司周二公布了第二季度业绩，并宣布裁员和削减成本，称这将每年节省 30 亿美元。【原文：Merck & Co on Tuesday announced job and cost cuts it said will save $3 billion a year as it posted lower second-quarter results due to continuing weak demand for its Gardasil vaccine in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/merck-cut-jobs-costs-demand-gardasil-china-remains-weak-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57U4WNJSBNJ2LJLLECZDDDSCDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:36:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本官员称，美日贸易协议保证芯片和制药业关税税率最低]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本主要贸易谈判代表周二表示，东京上周与美国达成的贸易协议保证了日本将始终获得华盛顿谈判的所有协议中最低的芯片和药品关税税率。【原文：Japan's leading trade negotiator said on Tuesday that the trade deal Tokyo agreed with the United States last week guarantees Japan will always receive the lowest tariff rate on chips and pharmaceuticals of all the pacts negotiated by Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-japan-trade-deal-guarantees-lowest-tariff-rates-chips-pharma-japanese-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2SB7FZGMUVPBXP37SS3V5P2EEU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:25:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[债券投资者热衷风险，美联储在 "金发姑娘 "经济中按兵不动]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券投资者在经历了长期的谨慎之后正在增加投资组合风险，他们认为美国经济正处于 "金发期"，不会太热也不会太冷，因为他们押注美联储将在连续第五次政策会议上维持利率不变。【原文：Bond investors are adding portfolio risk after a long period of caution, seeing the U.S. economy in a "Goldilocks" moment, not too hot nor too cold, as they bet the Federal Reserve will leave rates unchanged for a fifth straight policy meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bond-investors-warm-risk-with-fed-staying-put-goldilocks-economy-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGL2HVEJ5BOYTK5SLX4Z2ZE5T4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江和记出售中国港口股份可缓解北京压力，但美国地缘政治风险依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士和分析师称，中国航运巨头中远集团拟加入香港企业集团长江和记颇具争议的全球港口出售计划，这是中国政府在战略领域的一次潜在胜利，但该交易远非最终结果，而且可能面临来自华盛顿的阻力。【原文：The proposed inclusion of Chinese shipping giant COSCO in Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison's contentious global ports sale is a potential win for Beijing in a strategic sector, but the deal is far from final and could face resistance from Washington, sources and analysts say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-stake-ck-hutchison-port-sale-could-ease-beijing-pressure-us-geopolitical-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BLHO4OUN7RIL3C3DC55PZUM3AA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙监管机构扩大对苹果公司应用程序商店定价问题的调查范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙反垄断监管机构周二表示，正在扩大对苹果公司可能存在的反竞争行为的调查，因为苹果公司涉嫌对在其应用市场上销售移动应用的开发商施加不平等的商业条件。【原文：Spain's antitrust regulator said on Tuesday it was expanding its investigation into possible anti-competitive behaviour by Apple for allegedly imposing unequal commercial conditions on developers of mobile applications sold at its app marketplace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/spains-watchdog-expands-probe-into-apple-over-app-store-pricing-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EP7V7JXFOFNSLAGMCBGCRGONMM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:14:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储的政策工具包或将发生根本性变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位美国参议员最近推动剥夺美联储控制利率的一个关键环节，以及关于谁将接替美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔的争论，都预示着未来决策者用来影响经济的一些工具将受到更严格的审查。【原文：A U.S. senator's recent push to strip the Federal Reserve of a key aspect of how it controls interest rates and the battle over who will succeed Fed Chair Jerome Powell point to a future where some of the tools policymakers use to influence the economy come under greater scrutiny.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/feds-policy-toolkit-may-be-headed-fundamental-changes-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FVFCZ2WZVOHJAIZPL72B3EPQ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[太空探索技术公司的火箭外交如何在巴哈马适得其反？]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉此事的人士透露，去年 SpaceX 公司与巴哈马谈判允许其猎鹰 9 号火箭助推器在巴哈马领土内着陆时，埃隆-马斯克的公司提供了一个甜头：为该国的国防舰艇提供免费的星链（Starlink）互联网终端。【原文：When SpaceX was negotiating a deal with the Bahamas last year to allow its Falcon 9 rocket boosters to land within the island nation's territory, Elon Musk's company offered a sweetener: complimentary Starlink internet terminals for the country's defense vessels, according to three people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/how-spacexs-rocket-diplomacy-backfired-bahamas-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSVZI4DDHFKAJKHZ6OC2R3RUWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合健康预计年度利润低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合健康（UnitedHealth）周二恢复了两个月前下调的全年利润预期，但其指导性预期低于分析师已经下调的预期，因为这家美国医疗保险公司正在与政府支持计划中不断上涨的成本作斗争。【原文：UnitedHealth on Tuesday reinstated full-year profit forecast that it pulled over two months ago, but its guidance fell short of analysts' already-lowered expectations, as the U.S. health insurer battles rising costs in its government-backed plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-forecasts-annual-profit-below-estimates-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XHV235KEEVO6ZCWGTKFCN66OJY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易政策变化拖累 UPS 季度业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合包裹服务公司（United Parcel Service）周二公布第二季度利润和收入下降，原因是对中国低价值货物征收新的 "微量 "关税，以及唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统贸易政策带来的风险不断增加，导致需求受到打击。【原文：United Parcel Service reported a decline in second-quarter profit and revenue on Tuesday, as demand took a hit from new "de minimis" tariffs on low-value Chinese shipments and mounting risks from President Donald Trump's trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/ups-posts-downbeat-quarterly-results-shifting-trade-policies-weigh-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7VZK5YDDQROHNJ6JZ2G7JDB7AY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:06:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify 预测利润低于预期，原因是税收增加，股价下挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，Spotify 预计第三季度利润低于市场预期，原因是与员工工资相关的税费增加，超过了对其优质音乐流计划的乐观需求。【原文：Spotify forecast third-quarter profit below Street estimates on Tuesday as higher taxes related to employee salaries outweigh upbeat demand for its premium music-streaming plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/spotify-forecasts-profit-below-estimates-higher-taxes-shares-sink-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ONBCO242D5LMDN7M3FY4NKYFUU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 大胆押注 "超级智能 "的一年不太可能带来丰厚利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在是马克-扎克伯格的紧要关头，他要使出浑身解数，在硅谷愈演愈烈的先进人工智能竞赛中保持优势。【原文：It's crunch time for Mark Zuckerberg as he pulls out all the stops to stay relevant in Silicon Valley's intensifying advanced artificial intelligence race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/metas-year-bold-superintelligence-bets-unlikely-pump-profits-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MGKCMP2ZZLERMJSSYK5YOFRUM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街期货上涨，焦点转向主要财报和美联储会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货走高，因为投资者在等待多家公司的财报以及当天晚些时候开始的美联储政策会议。【原文：U.S. stock index futures edged higher on Tuesday as investors awaited earnings reports from a number of companies and the Federal Reserve's policy meeting that starts later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-street-futures-rise-focus-shifts-major-earnings-fed-meeting-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KA4EJDZRKFKJTLUCD7FAPEUJNA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息：消息人士称，波音/萨博正在与 BAE 就英国喷气教练机竞标进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士透露，波音和瑞典萨博公司正在与英国 BAE 系统公司谈判，商讨未来联手研制英国鹰式教练机的替代品，以填补快速喷气机行业日益增长的空白。【原文：Boeing and Sweden's Saab are in talks with Britain's BAE Systems about teaming up on a future replacement of Britain's Hawk trainer in a growing niche of the fast jet industry, three people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeingsaab-talks-with-bae-uk-jet-trainer-bid-sources-say-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">54I2U2UYLVOA3HEYND5LUDUTKY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯国际航空公司取消更多航班，但称网络攻击后航班计划已 "稳定 "下来]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯航空公司周二又取消了数十个航班，但表示在一天前遭受重大网络攻击后，该公司现已稳定了航班计划。【原文：Russian airline Aeroflot cancelled dozens more flights on Tuesday but said it had now stabilised its schedule after a major cyberattack a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russias-aeroflot-cancels-more-flights-says-schedule-is-now-stabilised-after-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UONU5PN7Q5ODTLFQNK6KFQLBXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波兰总理称美国关税可能导致波兰损失超过 20 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[波兰总理唐纳德-图斯克周二表示，据初步估计，美国对欧洲产品征收的新关税可能使波兰损失约80亿兹罗提（合21.6亿美元）。【原文：The new U.S. tariffs on European products could cost Poland around 8 billion zlotys ($2.16 billion), according to preliminary estimates, Polish Prime Minister Donald Tusk said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/poland-could-lose-over-2-billion-due-us-tariffs-pm-says-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6DZ5G22QJNNTJMVTQGFOQUUPUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者组织称，美国联邦消费者保护委员会超过 3.6 亿美元的消费者赔款 "面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[据支持消费者的组织周二发布的一份分析报告称，美国消费者金融保护局推翻了数十项执法行动，导致据称受到金融公司伤害的消费者损失超过 3.6 亿美元的赔偿金。【原文：The reversal of dozens of enforcement actions by the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau has jeopardized more than $360 million in compensation to consumers allegedly harmed by financial companies, according to an analysis released Tuesday by pro-consumer organizations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/more-than-360-mln-cfpb-consumer-payouts-at-risk-consumer-groups-say-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JD4Z46LUVNOK7G3MN6UMGPQ4JM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 8 月旅游预订量反弹，企业收入前景看好]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司和西南航空公司等航空公司以及希尔顿全球酒店集团和温德姆酒店集团等酒店运营商集体松了一口气，因为在今年早些时候许多人暂停度假计划后，有预算意识的美国人又开始预订旅行了。【原文：U.S. travel companies including air carriers United Airlines and Southwest Airlines and hotel operators Hilton Worldwide and Wyndham Hotels have issued a collective sigh of relief as budget-conscious Americans have started booking travel again after many put vacation plans on pause earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-travel-bookings-rebound-august-boosting-companies-revenue-outlook-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K2KHZUMDKRKFFM4UVCBYC6JQOI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:08:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 Telegram 群组中分享中国妇女的剥削性图片的报道在中国引起愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国媒体报道，中国女性的性剥削图片在加密的 Telegram 聊天群组中被数十万用户分享，在网上引发了广泛的愤怒。【原文：Sexually exploitative images of Chinese women were shared in encrypted Telegram chat groups with hundreds of thousands of users, Chinese media reported, triggering widespread outrage online.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/outrage-china-after-reports-exploitative-images-chinese-women-shared-telegram-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDM3PHOCA5K3TKL2KPH5MZL6BA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:42:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美在斯德哥尔摩恢复谈判以缓解关税敌对状态]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和中国官员周二在斯德哥尔摩开始了第二天的会谈，以解决长期存在的经济纠纷，从世界两大经济体之间不断升级的贸易战中后退。【原文：U.S. and Chinese officials began a second day of talks in Stockholm on Tuesday to resolve longstanding economic disputes and step back from an escalating trade war between the world's two biggest economies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-china-resume-talks-stockholm-ease-tariff-hostilities-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODMYJWOGTVKJBFW7OEJWLTTTEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能需求强劲，Advantest 将全年营业利润预期上调 24]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本芯片测试设备制造商 Advantest 周二将全年营业利润预期上调了 24%，原因是人工智能所用半导体的需求强劲。【原文：Japanese chip testing equipment maker Advantest raised on Tuesday its full-year operating profit forecast by 24% due to robust demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/advantest-raises-full-year-operating-profit-forecast-by-24-strong-ai-demand-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKHLFW6IEBNGLBVUFDS6IZOCTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本称美国贸易协议缓解了关税不确定性，但风险依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本周二表示，它与美国达成的贸易协议消除了美国贸易政策的不确定性，但需要继续关注这些政策给日本经济带来下行压力的风险。【原文：Japan said on Tuesday the trade agreement it struck with the U.S. cleared uncertainties on U.S. trade policies but continued attention needs to be given to risks of those policies putting downward pressure on the Japanese economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-says-us-trade-deal-eases-tariff-uncertainties-risks-remain-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HZ6R4TGLPJPJDMJ4QMNKKVEL6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉称仅美国关税不会引发欧盟评级下调]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉（Fitch）周二表示，美国大幅提高对欧盟成员国的贸易关税不会立即引发主权评级下调，但会加剧现有压力。【原文：The sharp increase in U.S. trade tariffs on European Union member countries won't trigger immediate sovereign rating cut, but could compound existing pressures, Fitch said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fitch-says-us-tariffs-alone-wont-trigger-eu-rating-downgrades-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODI3EI5SVRKXPNFWPGMNQ4EA3I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙黑橄榄出口商在美国新关税下举步维艰]]></title><description><![CDATA[自美国总统唐纳德-特朗普上任以来，西班牙的黑橄榄出口商一直被征收苛刻的关税，他们警告说，根据欧盟与美国达成的最新贸易协议，他们现在将面临额外 15%的关税，这将使他们难以生存。【原文：Spain's black olive exporters, subject to harsh tariffs since U.S. President Donald Trump's first term, are warning it will be difficult to survive an extra 15% they now face under the European Union's latest trade deal with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spains-black-olive-exporters-struggle-under-fresh-us-tariffs-2025-07-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RVGAKW3ARZKWXKQ2I2MSYRNXIU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>