<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 23:04:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 23:04:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉经济学家称美国关税率飙升至 22%，为 1910 年以来最高]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）的美国经济研究主管周三表示，根据美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）实施的新的全球征税措施，美国对所有进口商品征收的关税税率已从2024年的2.5%飙升至22%。【原文：The U.S. tariff rate on all imports has rocketed to 22% from just 2.5% in 2024 under the new global levies imposed by President Donald Trump, Fitch Ratings' U.S. economic research chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-tariff-rate-rockets-22-highest-since-1910-fitch-economist-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SM3RVL2VYZJBHJXXBJBFGFQDTQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:55:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚称美国加征关税 "非朋友所为"，但排除采取对等行动的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内塞周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收关税的决定 "不是朋友的行为"，但排除了对美国征收对等关税的可能性。【原文：Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said on Thursday the decision by U.S. President Donald Trump to impose tariffs was "not the act of a friend," but ruled out placing reciprocal tariffs against the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/australia-says-us-tariffs-not-act-friend-rules-out-reciprocal-move-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LK2OSDXFFFKBNDHGJJY2RTYL4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:52:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡尼表示加拿大将对美国采取反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大总理马克-卡尼（Mark Carney）周三表示，加拿大将以反制措施对抗美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的关税。【原文：Canada will fight U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs with countermeasures, Prime Minister Mark Carney said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-will-impose-counter-measures-united-states-says-carney-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNREBVW6I5ML5PI4IXBR7U6NPA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油进口免受特朗普全面关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[白宫周三表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的全面新关税豁免了石油、天然气和精炼产品的进口。【原文：Imports of oil, gas and refined products were exempted from U.S. President Donald Trump’s sweeping new tariffs, the White House said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-imports-exempted-trumps-sweeping-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2YRUE4ICZVKP5CHHAICKXJOWZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税给疲软的世界经济带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国周三公布的最新一轮贸易关税将进一步削弱世界经济的活力，因为世界经济刚刚从大流行后的通胀飙升中恢复过来，又被创纪录的债务所拖累，并受到地缘政治纷争的困扰。【原文：The latest round of U.S. trade tariffs unveiled on Wednesday will sap yet more vigour from a world economy barely recovered from the post-pandemic inflation surge, weighed down by record debt and unnerved by geopolitical strife.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-tariffs-pile-stress-ailing-world-economy-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZJZX77YKRLPBJJXXUUJDRWTYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大和墨西哥在芬太尼和边境令生效期间不受新的全球税率限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据白宫周三发布的一份情况说明，唐纳德-特朗普总统不会对来自加拿大和墨西哥的商品征收 10%的新全球关税，而他之前因边境控制和芬太尼贩运问题而对来自这两个国家的许多商品征收高达 25% 关税的命令仍然有效。【原文：President Donald Trump is not imposing his new 10% global tariff rate on goods from Canada and Mexico while his previous order remains in place for up to 25% tariffs on many goods from the two in connection to border control and fentanyl trafficking issues, according to a White House fact sheet released on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-mexico-not-subject-new-global-rates-while-fentanyl-border-order-place-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTTAL4FU5ZO6FPJT5DIZF5KRIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税令附带的白宫概况介绍]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三宣布对从大多数美国贸易伙伴进口的商品全面征收至少 10%的全球关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Wednesday unveiled sweeping global tariffs of at least 10% on goods imported from most U.S. trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-fact-sheet-accompanying-trumps-new-tariff-orders-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HGMMSUUY4VOFLPCXN56QWZSX6M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，甲骨文公司告知客户最近第二次遭到黑客攻击，登录数据被盗]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三援引两位熟悉此事的人士的话报道，甲骨文公司已告知客户，一名黑客入侵了计算机系统，并盗取了旧的客户登录凭证。【原文：Oracle has told customers that a hacker broke into a computer system and stole old client log-in credential, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday, citing two people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/oracle-tells-clients-second-recent-hack-log-in-data-stolen-bloomberg-news-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3JOROTHM5VIJBOL3VMITEPOM34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界各国领导人对特朗普的全球关税作出反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四公布全球互惠关税后，世界各国领导人开始作出回应。【原文：World leaders began responding after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled global reciprocal tariffs on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/world-leaders-react-trumps-global-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GRZZJYMTRJLFBFDKQK5ILR6HEU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:57:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司第一季度交付 30 架飞机]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周三表示，2025 年第一季度交付了 30 架飞机，同比增长 20%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer said on Wednesday it delivered 30 aircraft in the first quarter of 2025, a 20% increase from a year earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-delivers-30-aircraft-1st-quarter-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBI2WMGUURJGVJRCDIDNWJHSM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街对特朗普互征关税的反应]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三表示，他将对所有进口到美国的商品征收10%的基准关税，并对美国的一些最大贸易伙伴征收更高的关税，此举可能会使贸易战升级并颠覆全球经济。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he would impose a 10% baseline tariff on all imports to the United States and higher duties on some of the country's biggest trading partners, a move that could escalate a trade war and upend the global economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-reacts-trumps-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A7UNBFQ5XNOHTBKOTQTFFNQ74A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，关闭对来自中国的廉价货物的关税豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的一位助手说，他于周三签署了一项行政命令，关闭了一个用于从中国免税运输低价值包裹的贸易漏洞，即所谓的 "微量免税"（de minimis）。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Wednesday that closes a trade loophole used to ship low-value packages duty-free from China, known as "de minimis," an aide said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-signs-order-that-closes-duty-exemptions-cheap-shipments-china-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2QM4VHALXBM2LGFCV6UTCFBJFI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普对包括笔记本电脑在内的 6000 亿美元进口汽车征收关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社对周三联邦注册公告中的关税代码进行的分析，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的25%汽车关税将涵盖价值近6000亿美元的汽车和汽车零部件，并扩展至包括笔记本电脑在内的所有进口到美国的电脑。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% autos tariffs will cover nearly $600 billion worth of vehicles and auto parts and extend to all computer imports into the U.S., including laptops, according to a Reuters analysis of tariff codes included in a federal register notice on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trumps-autos-tariffs-cover-600-bln-imports-including-laptop-computers-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DVIP6LXM5RJOZD5OTY7JHSDMNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构接受澳新银行修复风险文化的承诺；提高资本附加值]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚审慎监管机构周四表示，已接受澳新银行集团（ANZ Group）做出的可由法院强制执行的承诺，以解决该银行的非财务风险管理实践和风险文化问题。【原文：Australia's prudential watchdog said on Thursday it had accepted a court-enforceable undertaking from ANZ Group to address the lender's non-financial risk management practices and risk culture.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australia-regulator-accepts-anzs-undertaking-fix-risk-culture-hikes-capital-add-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LF5AT3KG4VLJHJ3VO7AWPKJXM4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：T 日到来，市场上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-trading-day-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DURE3XVSO5LW3MILXXGRXVSAGI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 特朗普巨额关税令市场大吃一惊，标普指数期货下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三宣布将征收对等关税，以配合其他国家对美国商品征收的关税，从而使贸易战进一步升级。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump further escalated a trade war on Wednesday by announcing he would impose reciprocal tariffs to match duties put on U.S. goods by other countries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/view-investors-react-trump-tariff-announcement-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQI537W4OJMF5HNCEL66EGBC5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[前瑞波公司员工承认为竞争对手 Deel 从事间谍活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰一家法院周三公开的一份宣誓书显示，人力资源软件公司 Rippling 的一名前雇员承认，他在竞争对手 Deel Inc 首席执行官的指示下为该公司从事间谍活动。【原文：A former employee of HR software company Rippling has confessed to spying for Deel Inc under the directive of the rival firm's CEO, an affidavit made public in an Irish court showed on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/former-rippling-employee-admits-spying-rival-firm-deel-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXOUCSRHRJM6VPI74FPT37DQRM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征新关税，交易员押注美联储六月开始降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布对进口商品征收新的关税，经济学家们认为这可能会刺激通胀，但也可能会拖累经济，因此交易商们加大了对美联储将于6月份开始降息并在10月份之前将政策利率总共下调三个季度点的押注。【原文：Traders boosted bets the Federal Reserve will start cutting interest rates in June and deliver a total of three quarter-point reductions to the policy rate by October, as U.S. President Donald Trump announced new tariffs on imports, which economists say could boost inflation but could also slow the economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/traders-boost-bets-june-start-fed-rate-cuts-trump-puts-new-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAK7VKVUUJLLTP5A2TDBJMXRQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:48:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普公布全球互惠关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三在白宫举行的一次活动中公布了全球互惠关税。【原文：President Donald Trump on Wednesday unveiled global reciprocal tariffs during an event at the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-unveils-global-reciprocal-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CM25WIVKFRMR7LC2FFMCNLFAEI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席库格勒称通胀进展可能停滞，支持稳定利率政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事阿德里安娜-库格勒（Adriana Kugler）周三表示，美国央行实现2%通胀目标的进展最近有所放缓，可能已经停滞不前，这也是维持利率不变的一个理由。【原文：Progress towards the U.S. central bank's 2% inflation target has slowed recently and may have stalled, Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler said on Wednesday, a reason to keep interest rates where they are.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-kugler-says-inflation-progress-may-have-stalled-backs-steady-rate-policy-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3SCTV52NYFNPBNBH3RPAMQXPVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:32:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布加征关税，美元兑日元转为升值]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美元兑欧元走软，兑日元走高，因为美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）开始宣布人们期待已久的全面新关税，这看起来肯定会使与全球伙伴的贸易战升级、物价上涨并颠覆已有几十年历史的贸易秩序。【原文：The dollar weakened against the euro and turned higher against the yen on Wednesday as U.S. President Donald Trump began a long awaited announcement of sweeping new tariffs that look certain to escalate a trade war with global partners, increase prices and upend a decades-old trade order.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-turns-higher-against-yen-trump-announces-tariffs-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQ6PS4HSXNOSZHLNR3LYMLE6H4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[初级保健公司 knownwell 加入礼来直销公司，提供体重管理服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[初级保健公司 knownwell 周三表示，它将在礼来公司直接面向消费者的在线保健平台 LillyDirect 上提供健康和体重管理服务。【原文：Primary care company knownwell said on Wednesday it will provide health and weight-management services on Eli Lilly's direct-to-consumer online healthcare platform, LillyDirect.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/primary-care-firm-knownwell-joins-lillydirect-offer-weight-management-services-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RIEFHWRZH5MKNCFGADJGYZXAYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：Meta 首席执行官扎克伯格游说特朗普避免反垄断审判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周三援引知情人士的话报道，Meta Platforms 首席执行官马克-扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）正在游说美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）和白宫官员同意一项和解协议，以避免该公司在本月晚些时候面临反垄断审判。【原文：Meta Platforms CEO Mark Zuckerberg is lobbying U.S. President Donald Trump and White House officials to agree to a settlement that would prevent the company from facing an antitrust trial later this month, the Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/meta-ceo-zuckerberg-lobbies-trump-avoid-antitrust-trial-wsj-reports-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WRUBYL6VQ5LGHHUTEIZH2FHCTE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[里士满联储称，特朗普进口税对中西部和东南部的影响可能最大]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储（Richmond Federal Reserve）的一项新分析得出结论，特朗普政府征收或可能征收的新进口税可能会将进入美国的商品的平均有效关税率从目前的 2.2% 提高到 17% 左右，同时对中西部和南部各州的制造业造成 "广泛的破坏"。【原文：New import taxes imposed or potentially in the offing from the Trump administration could raise the average effective tariff rate on goods coming into the U.S. from the current 2.2% to around 17%, while posing "widespread disruptions" focused on manufacturing industries in Midwestern and Southern states, a new analysis from the Richmond Federal Reserve has concluded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-import-taxes-could-fall-heaviest-midwest-southeast-richmond-fed-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VR5NVOZ5RRLFRABMKXFGKW3OOU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，特朗普顾问华尔兹的团队针对世界危机建立了 20 个信号群聊]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的国家安全顾问迈克-华尔兹的团队在商业应用程序Signal上建立了至少20个群聊，以协调涉及中国、加沙、中东政策、非洲和欧洲等问题的官方工作。【原文：The team of President Donald Trump's national security adviser, Mike Waltz, set up at least 20 group chats on the commercial Signal app to coordinate official work on issues involving China, Gaza, Middle East policy, Africa and Europe, Politico reported on Wednesday, citing four people who were added to Signal chats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-adviser-waltzs-team-set-up-20-signal-group-chats-world-crises-politico-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4US7OSTFJFKDLECU3ETCQWFD5U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[律师称印第安纳大学网络安全教授未遭逮捕或拘留]]></title><description><![CDATA[印第安纳大学的一位著名教授突然被解雇并失踪，引起了网络安全界的关注，他的代理律师告诉路透社记者，他没有被拘留，他和他的妻子也没有受到任何未决的刑事指控。【原文：A prominent Indiana University professor whose abrupt firing and disappearance drew interest in the cybersecurity community has not been detained and there are no pending criminal charges against him or his wife, a lawyer representing him told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/indiana-university-cybersecurity-professor-has-not-been-arrested-or-detained-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2CFETUGNGNN5BK4ROSNRQ4VRDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:36:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子将以 51 亿美元收购 Dotmatics]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子公司周三表示，将以 51 亿美元的价格从 Insight Partners 手中收购总部位于美国的 Dotmatics 公司。【原文：Siemens AG said on Wednesday it will acquire U.S.-based Dotmatics for $5.1 billion from Insight Partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siemens-acquire-dotmatics-51-billion-deal-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNXCEQTK75JCHNC25DHDBYHHJQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦公报显示，特朗普 25% 的汽车关税将于美国东部时间 4 月 3 日上午 12:01 生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据《联邦公报》（Federal Register）上的一则公告，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）25%的汽车关税将于美国东部时间周四上午12:01生效。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's 25% automobile tariffs are due to take effect at 12:01 a.m. ET on Thursday, according to a post in the Federal Register.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-25-automobile-tariffs-due-take-effect-1201-am-et-april-3-federal-register-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QH3LRJ34ROQTAXJ7EM6KAIWYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:26:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，特朗普考虑取消对中国廉价货物的关税豁免]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉计划的消息人士称，作为周三关税声明的一部分，特朗普政府正在考虑取消对来自中国的低价值货物的关税豁免。【原文：The Trump administration is considering revoking tariff exemptions for low-value shipments from China as part of Wednesday's tariff announcement, a source familiar with the plans said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/trump-considering-revoking-tariff-exemptions-cheap-shipments-china-source-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHWPQW42V5NEBOUQTF4R7GOHHY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官表示，波音正与司法部合作修改 737 MAX 欺诈案的认罪协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司首席执行官凯利-奥特伯格（Kelly Ortberg）周三表示，波音公司正在与美国司法部商讨，以就该公司涉嫌就737 MAX飞机上的一个关键系统向监管机构作出虚假陈述而引发的刑事欺诈案达成修订认罪协议。【原文：Boeing is in discussions with the U.S. Department of Justice to reach a revised plea agreement in a criminal fraud case stemming from the planemaker's alleged misrepresentations to regulators about a key system on the 737 MAX, company CEO Kelly Ortberg said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-working-with-doj-revised-plea-deal-737-max-fraud-case-ceo-says-2025-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNDQN5YIHBIB5C37AWAKS276DQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:22:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>