<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:39:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:39:55 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街和主街推动美国预算法案重新考虑外国税收问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表房地产、金融和跨国公司等行业的行业团体正在推动减少或排除共和党税收法案中针对在美外国投资者的报复性税收，因为他们认为这是对其业务以及更广泛的市场和经济的威胁。【原文：Industry groups representing sectors including real estate, finance and multinational companies are pushing for the reduction or exclusion of a retaliatory tax targeting foreign investors in the U.S. in the Republican tax bill, as they see it as a threat to their businesses and to the broader markets and economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wall-street-main-street-push-foreign-tax-rethink-us-budget-bill-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIK2JUYABFMMHJDQ474UDYZB6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[共和党人无视债务警告，推进特朗普税收议程]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和他在国会的共和党盟友决心在政治推动中实施他的减税议程，这在很大程度上放弃了该党长期以来声称的财政纪律，他们只是否认了有关该措施将使联邦债务膨胀的警告。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and his Republican allies in Congress are determined to enact his tax-cut agenda in a political push that has largely abandoned longtime party claims of fiscal discipline, by simply denying warnings that the measure will balloon the federal debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/defying-debt-warnings-republicans-push-forward-trump-tax-agenda-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCCSNNLPJLPHH4RSGI3PBGJRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国铝生产商从特朗普关税中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的原铝生产商世纪铝业公司（Century Aluminum）和顶级回收商 Matalco 将成为唐纳德-特朗普总统对进口金属征收更高关税的大赢家，因为国内铝价飙升。【原文：Century Aluminum, the largest primary aluminium producer in the U.S., and top recycler Matalco will be among the big winners from President Donald Trump's higher tariffs on imports of the metal as domestic prices surge, four industry sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/aluminium-producers-us-win-trumps-tariffs-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EKP3F3ZXBJKF5IKQAVFFWGYOHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:19:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[透视：对油菜籽征收关税将促使加拿大农民转向种植春小麦]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国大平原，春小麦曾一度在田间占据主导地位，农民们正在放弃种植春小麦。但在边境另一侧的加拿大，中国和美国对油菜籽征收关税的压力和前景促使农民转而种植小麦。【原文：In the U.S. Great Plains, where spring wheat once dominated fields, farmers are turning away from the crop. But across the border in Canada, the pinch and prospect of Chinese and U.S. tariffs on canola have prompted farmers to pick up the slack on wheat.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/tariffs-canola-seen-supercharging-canadian-farmers-shift-spring-wheat-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VV7TVDJJKJNJZC2BFXHPZZ65M4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，随着保险公司重新专注于美国市场，联合健康（UnitedHealth）希望通过 10 亿美元的交易退出拉丁美洲市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位直接了解此事的人士透露，联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）正在权衡对其拉美业务的多个竞标，因为这家保险公司在经历了一系列前所未有的失误（包括首席执行官下台和据报道的刑事会计调查）之后，正处于低谷。【原文：UnitedHealth Group is weighing multiple bids for its Latin American operations, according to two people with direct knowledge of the matter, as the insurer buckles down after a series of unprecedented missteps that include the ouster of its CEO and a reported criminal accounting probe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-eyes-1-billion-deal-exit-latin-america-insurer-refocuses-us-sources-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDLXEFIWSFLCBDJ74QJXC5K52Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷领导人米莱在十月大选前舔舔嘴唇]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷火热的右翼总统哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）通过无情的紧缩计划在很大程度上抑制了失控的通货膨胀，他的目标是在 10 月份的立法选举中，当他的政党及其盟友与分裂的反对党交锋时巩固政权。【原文：Argentina's firebrand right-wing President Javier Milei has largely tamed runaway inflation with a ruthless austerity plan and he aims to solidify power when his party and its allies take on a divided opposition in legislative elections in October.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/argentine-leader-milei-licking-his-chops-ahead-october-elections-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R4UTFVXVRVK7HDNCIUAPW3ZTUA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WWDC：苹果在招揽软件开发者时面临人工智能和监管挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，苹果公司的一些主要高管将在公司年度软件开发者大会上发言，苹果公司正面临着一系列前所未有的技术和监管挑战。【原文：Apple is facing an unprecedented set of technical and regulatory challenges as some of its key executives are set to take the stage on Monday at the company's annual software developer conference.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wwdc-apple-faces-ai-regulatory-challenges-it-woos-software-developers-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVJYJBYBTBJGTDZ2KMPW5YP624</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道雪佛龙首席执行官在安哥拉平台发生致命火灾前警告员工安全问题日益严重]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Wirth 于 4 月 29 日发布了一条内部视频消息，就在该公司位于安哥拉的一个石油平台发生火灾导致三名工人死亡的几周前。【原文：Mike Wirth issued an internal video message on April 29, just weeks before three workers died due to a fire on one of the company's oil platforms in Angola.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/chevron-ceo-warned-staff-rising-safety-issues-before-fatal-angola-platform-fire-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIJVIQT7XZKJZK4WZD4DNXCWUM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国 B. Grimm Power 公司和新加坡 Digital Edge 公司将投资 10 亿美元建设泰国数据中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国 B. Grimm Power Pcl 和新加坡数字基础设施公司 Digital Edge 周一发表声明称，两家公司将投资 10 亿美元在泰国建设一个 100 兆瓦的数据中心。【原文：Thai B. Grimm Power Pcl and Singaporean digital infrastructure firm Digital Edge will invest $1 billion in a 100-megawatt data centre in Thailand, the companies said in a statement on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailands-b-grimm-power-singapores-digital-edge-invest-1-billion-thai-data-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6H6WRNYBHZL7JOOSHB2Z2JFXAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:09:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受人工智能需求和美国关税影响，台湾 5 月出口创历史新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于人工智能需求的蓬勃发展，以及客户在美国关税生效前下订单，台湾的出口在 5 月份飙升至创纪录水平。【原文：Taiwan's exports surged to a record in May on booming demand for artificial intelligence and as customers placed orders ahead of U.S. tariffs which could take effect next month after a suspension period expires.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/taiwan-may-exports-hit-record-ai-demand-ahead-us-tariffs-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3HTPQC6QZND3OVSD3WPOP4VSE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 5 月汽车销量增长，但价格战给前景蒙上阴影]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 5 月份汽车销量连续第四个月增长，但主要汽车制造商的销量增长速度放缓，凸显了人们对全球最大汽车市场激烈价格竞争的担忧。【原文：China's May car sales rose for a fourth consecutive month, but slower sales rises across major automakers, although the pace of growth slowed, highlighting concerns over aggressive price competition in the world’s largest auto market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-car-sales-rise-may-price-wars-cloud-outlook-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LURPH4652NIYLHL5BO2RD2GEGY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[量子计算公司 IonQ 将以 10.8 亿美元收购英国牛津离子公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[总部位于马里兰州的量子计算公司 IonQ 周一表示，将以 10.75 亿美元的价格收购英国量子计算初创公司 Oxford Ionics。【原文：IonQ will acquire British quantum computing startup Oxford Ionics for $1.075 billion, the Maryland-based quantum computing firm said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/quantum-computing-firm-ionq-acquire-uk-based-oxford-ionics-108-billion-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADJH42TBCROTHMO74CAXHABXRM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗集团放弃美国 7 月降息押注，将预期下调至 75 个基点]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团（Citigroup）将美国降息预期从 7 月份推迟到了 9 月份，现在预计今年将降息三次，而不是四次，因为在劳动力市场降温的情况下，5 月份就业报告强于预期。【原文：Citigroup has pushed back its U.S. rate cut forecast to September from July and now expects three cuts this year instead of four, after a stronger-than-expected May jobs report in an otherwise cooling labor market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/citigroup-drops-july-rate-cut-bets-us-trims-forecast-75-bps-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SD3ZVGPNDBJCHJY4CC7S3CBYOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:20:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rednote 加入中国企业发布开源人工智能模型的浪潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最受欢迎的社交媒体平台之一红记发布了一个开源的大型语言模型，加入了中国科技公司免费提供人工智能模型的浪潮。【原文：China's Rednote, one of the country's most popular social media platforms, has released an open-source large language model, joining a wave of Chinese tech firms making their artificial intelligence models freely available.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/rednote-joins-wave-chinese-firms-releasing-open-source-ai-models-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EUN7HCH4BVOBFFHGANUBVUMOAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国金融监管机构与英伟达合作开发人工智能 "沙盒]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国金融监管部门周一推出了一个监管 "沙盒"，今年晚些时候，英国的金融公司将可以在 "沙盒 "中测试人工智能工具，这是政府支持创新和经济增长的更广泛战略的一部分。【原文：Financial firms in Britain will be able to test artificial intelligence tools later this year in a regulatory "sandbox" launched on Monday by the country's financial watchdog, part of a broader government strategy to support innovation and economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uk-financial-regulator-partners-with-nvidia-ai-sandbox-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDIHDEUSVNJ73FETFLJUY45TZI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 07:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅收购英国护肤品牌 Medik8]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧莱雅的所有者、英国私募股权公司 Inflexion 周一表示，欧莱雅将收购英国护肤品牌 Medik8，这将增强这家法国化妆品巨头在快速增长的皮肤科护肤品市场上的实力。【原文：L'Oreal is to acquire British skincare brand Medik8, its owner, Britain-based private equity firm Inflexion, said on Monday, boosting the French cosmetics giant's offering in the fast-growing dermatological skincare market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/loreal-buys-british-skincare-brand-medik8-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WR5YBASMZRLUHJ7Z4WGYWDXSCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：消息人士称，Shein 和 Reliance 的目标是在一年内将印度制造的服装销往国外]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士称，时装零售商 Shein 和合作伙伴 Reliance Retail 计划迅速扩大其印度供应商基地，并在 6 至 12 个月内开始在海外销售印度制造的 Shein 品牌服装。【原文：Fashion retailer Shein and partner Reliance Retail plan to rapidly expand their Indian supplier base and start overseas sales of India-made Shein-branded clothes within six to 12 months, said two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/shein-reliance-aim-sell-india-made-clothes-abroad-within-year-sources-say-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MKW5EIHPYBI6LEF2Q2KXAH26UA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:44:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司以 24 亿美元收购 Alphawave，加强人工智能产品组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国芯片制造商高通公司（Qualcomm）周一同意以约 24 亿美元的价格收购英国半导体公司 Alphawave，以加强其人工智能技术。【原文：U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm on Monday agreed to acquire British semiconductor company Alphawave for about $2.4 billion as part of efforts to strengthen its artificial intelligence technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/qualcomm-acquire-uks-alphawave-24-billion-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OXEHUXK3OBPXDDXLYKBLHQXEMA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联系汇率飞涨：特朗普引发的动荡冲击港元和利率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普反复无常的政策正在动摇经受住了时间考验并被视为中国和亚洲锚的货币联系。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's erratic policies are rattling a currency peg that has withstood the test of time and is seen as an anchor for China and Asia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/when-pegs-fly-trump-induced-turbulence-hits-hong-kong-dollar-interest-rates-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSRDBWBCONL2BBIC4JUINKS5FU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:20:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国五月贷款因货币措施和贸易休战而增加三倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于中美之间暂时的贸易休战和政府的新措施帮助刺激了信贷需求，5 月份中国新增人民币贷款比一个月前增加了两倍多，与去年同期的借贷需求相当。【原文：China's new yuan loans more than tripled in May compared with a month ago, matching the borrowing appetite in the same period last year, as a temporary trade truce between China and the United States and new government measures helped boost credit demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-may-lending-seen-tripling-monetary-measures-trade-truce-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LA7W3EGGN5ONLBQZLZQMNAC55E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 05:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[盖蒂在英国就版权和人工智能提起的具有里程碑意义的诉讼即将开庭]]></title><description><![CDATA[盖蒂图片公司（Getty Images）对人工智能公司 Stability AI 提起的具有里程碑意义的版权诉讼周一在伦敦高等法院开庭，这家图片提供商的案件可能会为人工智能法律开创一个重要先例。【原文：Getty Images' landmark copyright lawsuit against artificial intelligence company Stability AI begins at London's High Court on Monday, with the photo provider's case likely to set a key precedent for the law on AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/gettys-landmark-uk-lawsuit-copyright-ai-set-begin-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P2IFVDMLJZJMTF27TZ575KOPOY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 05:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汽车公司因稀土瓶颈 "陷入全面恐慌]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近几周，德国一家磁铁制造商的首席执行官弗兰克-艾卡德（Frank Eckard）接到了大量电话。气急败坏的汽车制造商和零部件供应商迫切希望找到磁铁的替代货源，因为中国的出口限制导致磁铁供不应求。【原文：Frank Eckard, CEO of a German magnet maker, has been fielding a flood of calls in recent weeks. Exasperated automakers and parts suppliers have been desperate to find alternative sources of magnets, which are in short supply due to Chinese export curbs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/auto-companies-in-full-panic-over-rare-earths-bottleneck-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CNHZPWH27BPT5F5XUC22PECURU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 05:08:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价市场寄希望于伦敦贸易谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[洛基-斯威夫特对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rocky Swift】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IQBZWWH2BI6DMFCQ2FITRXSFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿优先事项发生变化，美国太阳能增长放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一家顶级太阳能贸易集团周一发布的一份报告称，由于美国联邦政策转向倾向于化石燃料、关税和其他挑战，预计未来五年美国太阳能新装机量将下降。【原文：New U.S. solar energy installations are expected to fall over the next five years as the industry grapples with a shift in federal policy that favors fossil fuels, tariffs and other challenges, according to a report published on Monday by a top solar trade group.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/us-solar-energy-growth-slow-washington-priorities-shift-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RX7EFJ7ONJMMJGUTHAKG4AJWLI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管有出口限制，中国 5 月稀土出口仍猛增 23]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 5 月份稀土出货量环比增长 23%，达到一年来的最高水平，尽管中国政府对部分关键矿产的出口限制导致一些海外销售停止，但稀土短缺已波及全球制造业。【原文：China's outbound shipments of rare earths in May jumped 23% on the month to their highest in a year, though Beijing's export curbs on some of the critical minerals halted some overseas sales, with shortages rippling through global manufacturing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-rare-earth-exports-jump-23-may-despite-export-curbs-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2JMJ7PWJR5O3ZGJKFK7S4AYM2M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 5 月份大豆进口量较 4 月份增加；原油、煤炭和石油进口量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的海关数据显示，中国 5 月份的大豆进口量环比上升，而原油、煤炭和铁矿石的进口量则有所下降。【原文：China's imports of soybeans rose in May from a month earlier, while those of crude oil, coal, and iron ore dropped, customs data showed on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-may-imports-soybeans-rise-april-crude-oil-coal-oil-fall-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LBBTDMUK4VNFTP2SV7S4UU5EUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:08:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税战趋于缓和，波音飞机返回中国交货]]></title><description><![CDATA[飞行跟踪数据显示，一架新的波音737 MAX飞机周一重新降落在中国，这表明随着北京和华盛顿关税战的缓和，这家美国飞机制造商正在恢复向中国客户的交付。【原文：A new Boeing 737 MAX landed back in China on Monday, flight tracking data showed, a sign the U.S. planemaker was resuming deliveries to Chinese customers as Beijing and Washington ease their tariff war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-plane-lands-back-china-delivery-tariff-war-eases-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VK2KAUNVZJF5DUCNLEFPVZIXE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 04:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国 5 月出口放缓，通货紧缩因关税而加深]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国加征关税，中国5月份出口增长放缓至三个月来的最低点，同时工厂通货紧缩加深至两年来最严重的水平，这给世界第二大经济体带来了内外两方面的压力。【原文：China's May exports growth slowed to a three-month low as U.S. tariffs slammed shipments, while factory-gate deflation deepened to its worst level in two years, heaping pressure on the world's second-largest economy on both the domestic and external fronts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-may-exports-slow-deflation-deepens-tariffs-bite-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B457X3TUN5L3LFVPCV2TQ42GDM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 03:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[星巴克在中国降低部分饮品价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[星巴克周一在其微信社交媒体账户上发布了一篇文章，称将在中国把部分冰饮的价格平均下调 5 元（0.70 美元）。【原文：Starbucks will lower prices of some iced drinks by an average of 5 yuan ($0.70) in China, the company said in a post published on its Weixin social media account on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/starbucks-lower-prices-some-drinks-china-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5J6CDNAWKZP35JV65KH7TCAXVM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 03:47:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中美谈判前亚洲股市攀升，美元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚洲市场对好于预期的美国就业数据做出了反应，在伦敦举行的旨在修补中美贸易裂痕的会谈之前，股市跳涨，美元收窄了近期涨幅。【原文：Shares jumped and the dollar pared recent gains on Monday as Asian markets reacted to better-than-expected U.S. jobs data ahead of talks in London aimed at mending a trade rift between the United States and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-06-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C6E7RLRT5VPCHK5FNGQT4456UM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 02:22:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>