<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:08:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:08:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[调查显示，近一半在欧美国公司预计经济联系将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五公布的一项调查显示，近一半在欧洲运营的美国公司认为跨大西洋经济关系将恶化，尽管这与美国总统唐纳德-特朗普第二个任期之初相比已有明显改善。【原文：Almost half of U.S. companies operating in Europe believe transatlantic economic relations will worsen, although that is a marked improvement from the start of U.S. President Donald Trump's second term, according to a survey published on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/nearly-half-us-companies-europe-expect-declining-economic-ties-survey-shows-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUPHDUCCJBMG7KLL7ZMIWTJQSQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 04:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普新关税的相关信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有新职责将从 10 月 1 日起生效。【原文：All the new duties will take effect from October 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/what-know-about-trumps-tariffs-branded-drugs-furniture-other-goods-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YWDXXBK5QJKZTGNKE235XUKXTM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:46:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行将于 9 月 30 日维持利率不变，但可能在第三季度通胀之后降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社调查显示，澳大利亚储备银行下周将把现金利率维持在 3.60% 的水平，所有经济学家都这么认为，因为劳动力市场依然紧张，政策制定者正在等待通胀缓解的确切迹象。【原文：The Reserve Bank of Australia will keep its cash rate at 3.60% next week, all the economists in a Reuters poll said, as the labour market remains tight and policymakers wait to see firm signs that inflation is easing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/rba-hold-rates-september-30-cut-likely-after-q3-inflation-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMDKYWYY75OUPDFEXJJ37JYXTQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本将启动机制支持美国贸易协定下的 5,500 亿美元投资]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财政部周五表示，将在一家国有开发银行设立一个投资基金，以支持东京与华盛顿达成的关税协议中商定的 5,500 亿美元的一揽子投资计划。【原文：Japan's finance ministry said on Friday that it will set up an investment facility at a state-owned development bank to support a $550 billion investment package agreed in Tokyo's tariff deal with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-launch-facility-support-550-billion-investment-under-us-trade-deal-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQQ3AQGFGJMTHBLVCXGGIQ2KIA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁征收关税后亚洲制药商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普威胁从10月1日起对进口品牌药品征收100%的关税，除非这些药品的生产商在美国的生产工厂已经破土动工，在此之后，周五亚洲制药商的股票大多下跌。【原文：Shares of Asian drugmakers mostly fell on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened 100% tariffs on imports of branded pharmaceuticals from October 1, unless their producers had already broken ground on U.S. manufacturing plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/shares-asian-drugmakers-drop-after-trump-threatens-tariffs-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E6SS3J4IBVN4NMNSMDG6S3PURQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:52:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特斯库董事长福雷斯特加倍重视可再生能源，向特朗普发起挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚矿业公司 Fortescue 执行主席安德鲁-福雷斯特（Andrew Forrest）在接受采访时表示，人们对其脱碳相关产品兴趣浓厚，他对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普关于气候变化是世界上最大骗局的说法提出了质疑。【原文：Australian miner Fortescue is experiencing strong interest in its decarbonization-related offerings, Executive Chairman Andrew Forrest said in an interview, as he challenged U.S. President Donald Trump's claim that climate change is the greatest con job in the world.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/fortescue-chairman-forrest-doubles-down-renewables-challenge-trump-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4CJAW7SGVMFLGJKFUI3F26EGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元守住涨幅，关注支出数据为美联储提供线索]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国数据好于预期，抑制了美联储今年进一步宽松的预期，美元周五继续大幅上涨。【原文：The dollar held on to steep gains on Friday after better-than-forecast U.S. data dampened expectations for further easing by the Federal Reserve this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-holds-gains-attention-turns-spending-data-fed-clues-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I3CWXENZWVODHG4MUR77RIEMXM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 02:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯削减燃料出口，石油将创三个月来最大单周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于乌克兰对俄罗斯能源基础设施的袭击促使莫斯科限制燃料出口，并接近削减原油产量，油价周五上扬，有望创下自6月初以来的最大涨幅。【原文：Oil prices edged up on Friday, on track to rise at their steepest rate since early June as Ukraine's attacks on Russia's energy infrastructure push Moscow to restrict fuel exports and close to cutting crude output.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-set-biggest-weekly-gain-three-months-russia-cuts-fuel-exports-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMBTLZAMRZJI3FBDLNFFEXPTSU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:46:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 Gol 航空公司控制人结束与 Azul 的潜在合并谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gol 航空公司周四表示，其控股股东 Abra 集团已通知同行 Azul 公司，决定终止两家巴西航空公司之间潜在的业务合并谈判。【原文：Airline Gol said on Thursday that its controlling shareholder, Abra Group, has notified peer Azul of its decision to end talks for a potential business combination between the two Brazilian carriers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-airline-gols-controller-ends-talks-potential-merger-with-azul-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQ4JABFZHNMZLEU33B2CAQLUBE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征新关税，美联储减息押注解除，股市陷入困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）公布新一轮惩罚性关税之后，以及在经济数据强于预期之后交易商减少了对美国大幅降息的押注之后，周五亚洲股市开局不稳。【原文：Asia shares got off to a shaky start on Friday after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled a fresh round of punishing tariffs and as traders pared bets of sharp U.S. rate cuts following stronger-than-expected economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7HKY3T6HSNP4ZMH52N24BZUAFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:26:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perpetua Resources 正与嘉能可（Glencore）等商谈美国锑矿加工事宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perpetua Resources公司周四表示，该公司正在与嘉能可（Glencore）、创富集团（Trafigura）（TRAFGF.UL）和其他公司就在美国提炼锑的合作事宜进行谈判，这是为促进西方国家对中国封锁出口的一种重要矿产的供应所做努力的一部分。【原文：Perpetua Resources said on Thursday it is in talks with Glencore , Trafigura (TRAFGF.UL) and others about a partnership to refine antimony in the U.S., part of a push to boost Western supplies of a critical mineral whose exports China has blocked.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/perpetua-resources-talks-with-glencore-others-us-antimony-processing-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYWMA3HZFZOVBDKB4532HEFMDI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:08:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国监管机构调查公司发布加密货币公告前的股票走势]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四报道，美国监管机构已经检查了一些公司在宣布融资购买加密货币计划之前股价的剧烈波动，以寻找潜在的内幕交易和信息披露违规迹象。【原文：U.S. regulators have examined sharp movements in the stock prices of companies before they announced plans to raise money to buy cryptocurrency for signs of potential insider trading and disclosure violations, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-regulators-probe-stock-moves-before-companies-made-crypto-treasury-2025-09-26/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LLCILK2V3JIJ7H4JRTRNGFFV6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布自 10 月 1 日起对进口品牌或专利药品征收 100%的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将从10月1日起对进口品牌或专利药品征收100%的关税，除非制药公司在美国建厂。【原文：The United States will impose a 100% tariff on imports of branded or patented pharmaceutical products from October 1, unless a pharmaceutical company is building a manufacturing plant in the U.S., President Donald Trump said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-announces-100-tariff-imports-branded-or-patented-pharmaceuticals-october-1-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XAHE3YJNRRPV7BXALBCAKSZ3JE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:39:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[条款书显示，中国地平线机器人公司通过香港增发配股融资约 8.21 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周五看到的一份条款书显示，中国自动驾驶解决方案供应商地平线机器人公司（Horizon Robotics）通过香港增发配售筹集了约 8.21 亿美元。【原文：Chinese autonomous driving solutions provider Horizon Robotics has raised about $821 million through a Hong Kong top-up placement, according to a term sheet seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/chinas-horizon-robotics-raises-about-821-million-via-hong-kong-top-up-share-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JH2SGQ3L3ZPSRCL5U2S3RLUIME</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将从 10 月 1 日起对重型卡车进口征收 25% 的关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四表示，美国将从 10 月 1 日起对所有重型卡车的进口征收 25% 的关税。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Thursday that the United States will impose a 25% tariff on imports of all heavy trucks from October 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-says-us-will-impose-25-tariff-heavy-trucks-imports-october-1-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YUO4LJEBFJKSLHH2NUJMDYXU6M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府呼吁改革后，加拿大邮政工人举行全国罢工]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大邮政工人工会（Canadian Union of Postal Workers）表示，加拿大政府要求邮政公司进行大范围的改革，以加强其财务状况并实现现代化运营，随后加拿大邮政工人于周四举行了全国性罢工。【原文：Canada Post workers went on a nationwide strike on Thursday after the Canadian government called for the postal company to undergo a widespread transformation to bolster its finances and modernize operations, the Canadian Union of Postal Workers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/canada-post-workers-go-nationwide-strike-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUFWKGAVLFLWPJ2EHFU7UERHBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:55:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街最高监管机构称将审查白宫呼吁的裁员计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）负责人周四表示，他尚未对白宫要求联邦机构在政府可能关门期间进行大规模裁员的呼吁进行审查，但他相信该机构正在努力满足唐纳德-特朗普总统的优先要求。【原文：The head of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission said on Thursday he had yet to review a call from the White House for mass layoffs at federal agencies during a possible government shutdown but believed the agency was working to meet President Donald Trump's priorities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/top-wall-st-regulator-says-he-will-review-white-house-call-layoff-plans-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TKTILANYPJNIRCF4JIIFLYV6ZE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Information 报道，Meta 公司正在洽谈使用谷歌的双子座来改进广告定位功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Information 周四报道，Meta 的员工已经与 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌云公司（Google Cloud）就使用其双子座模型改善 Facebook 母公司广告业务的可能性进行了讨论。【原文：Meta staffers have had discussions with Alphabet's Google Cloud about the possibility of using its Gemini models to improve the Facebook parent's ad business, the Information reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-talks-use-googles-gemini-improve-ad-targeting-information-reports-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NGJ6TKN77RPSHCJ7UMRZ3GFCX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行出售 Banamex 股份后将寻求更多少数股权投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团高管周四表示，在启动潜在的首次公开募股之前，花旗集团将为其墨西哥零售部门 Banamex 寻找更多的少数投资者。【原文：Citigroup will look for more minority investors in its Mexican retail unit, Banamex, before launching a potential initial public offering, executives said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-turn-more-minority-investors-after-banamex-stake-sale-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNSNDWK3PFI7BAS5RBUDYWNQWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞任命前反垄断执法者德尔拉希姆为法律总监]]></title><description><![CDATA[派拉蒙天舞公司（Paramount Skydance）周四任命前美国反垄断高级官员马坎-德尔拉希姆（Makan Delrahim）为首席法务官，为竞购华纳兄弟发现公司（Warner Bros Discovery）做准备。【原文：Paramount Skydance on Thursday named Makan Delrahim, a former senior U.S. antitrust official, as its chief legal officer, amid preparations for a bid for Warner Bros Discovery .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-skydance-appoints-former-antitrust-enforcer-delrahim-legal-chief-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23RFXXFTU5IAVD5GCA6VTMUGHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大银行在纽约赢得驳回利差操纵诉讼的判决]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，一名联邦法官驳回了一系列反垄断诉讼中的 "所有剩余诉讼请求"，这些诉讼指控大型银行合谋操纵 Libor，而 Libor 是一种利率基准，曾支撑了数以万亿美元计的交易，损害了投资者的利益。【原文：A federal judge on Thursday dismissed "all remaining claims" in a slew of antitrust litigation accusing large banks of conspiring to rig Libor, an interest rate benchmark that once underpinned hundreds of trillions of dollars of transactions, at investors' expense.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/big-banks-win-dismissal-libor-rigging-litigation-new-york-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNY3VGO5YNMJPDT3KG2L4SWAHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敲响黑客攻击思科安全设备的警钟]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府网络防御机构就黑客利用思科安全设备中一个此前未知的漏洞一事向其他联邦机构发布了紧急指导。【原文：The U.S. government's cyber defense agency has issued urgent guidance to other federal agencies over hackers exploiting a previously unknown vulnerability in Cisco security devices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-sounds-alarm-over-hackers-targeting-cisco-security-devices-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PBARQ556CJIFJIAHMMFSVAKPYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:24:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官初步批准 Anthropic 与作者达成的 15 亿美元版权和解协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[据作者代表发布的一份新闻稿称，加利福尼亚州的一名联邦法官周四初步批准了一项具有里程碑意义的版权集体诉讼和解协议，该诉讼是由一群作者针对人工智能公司 Anthropic 在其人工智能训练中使用了他们的作品而提起的。【原文：A federal judge in California on Thursday preliminarily approved a landmark settlement of a copyright class action brought by a group of authors against artificial intelligence company Anthropic over the use of their work in its AI training, according to a press release from the authors' representatives.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-judge-approves-15-billion-anthropic-copyright-settlement-with-authors-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPBKB4OZPVOYVBUH2V73KOTJWU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:16:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：小声说......但这是顶部吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量。【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZT6KNPP7Z5KADHNBUHGKVYMDX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，尽管美国对中国船只征收港口费，但中国造船厂订单依然强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国战略与国际研究中心（Center for Strategic and International Studies）的一份最新报告显示，尽管美国针对这些船只征收港口费，旨在对抗中国的海上霸主地位，但全球航运公司仍在全力以赴地从中国造船厂订购商船。【原文：Global shipping companies are moving full steam ahead with commercial vessel orders from Chinese shipyards, despite the U.S. targeting those ships with port fees aimed at countering China's maritime dominance, a new report from the Center for Strategic and International Studies showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-shipyard-orders-strong-despite-us-port-fees-china-vessels-report-says-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CG2YRX4U7ZLZTKZRYMDEL6AL3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：瑞典鱼制造商梦得丽将把食品染料改成天然而非合成染料]]></title><description><![CDATA[生产色彩鲜艳的 Sour Patch Kids 和 Swedish Fish 糖果的食品制造商 Mondelez 公司在一封电子邮件中说，该公司正在积极努力为使用合成色素的产品改用天然染料，但没有给出过渡的时间框架。【原文：Food maker Mondelez, which manufactures brightly colored Sour Patch Kids and Swedish Fish candies, is actively working to switch to natural dyes for products that use synthetic colors, the company said in an email, without giving a time frame for the transition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/swedish-fish-maker-mondelez-will-switch-food-dyes-to-natural-not-synthetic-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YFV4POWNXBKHBP6WD2KPQ5VYJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普签署命令，宣布 TikTok 出售计划符合美国要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四签署了一项行政命令，宣布他将 TikTok 的美国业务出售给美国和全球投资者的计划将符合 2024 年法律的要求，该法律规定，除非中国所有者出售 TikTok，否则该短视频应用程序将被禁止使用。【原文：President Donald Trump signed an executive order on Thursday declaring that his plan to sell TikTok's U.S. operations to U.S. and global investors will meet the requirements in a 2024 law that says the short video app will be banned unless its Chinese owners sell it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-signs-order-declaring-tiktok-sale-plan-meets-us-requirements-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6XNBXX4PNNABB36VZW22NNWUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普改变对卢拉的看法可能要归功于巴西牛肉大亨]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士告诉路透社记者，巴西肉类包装巨头 JBS 的一位共同所有人在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周二在联合国演讲中出人意料地向巴西总统伸出橄榄枝约三周前私下会见了特朗普。【原文：A co-owner of Brazilian meatpacking giant JBS met privately with U.S. President Donald Trump about three weeks before Trump extended a surprise olive branch to Brazil's president in his United Nations speech on Tuesday, three people with knowledge of the encounter told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trumps-change-heart-lula-may-be-thanks-brazilian-beef-tycoon-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMCZ5TWJQ5K4BNNRN3R7JIAAZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:25:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于对廉价生活必需品的需求强劲，好市多季度收入超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[好市多批发公司（Costco Wholesale）周四公布的第四季度营收超出预期，原因是追求低价的美国人涌向这家会员制零售连锁店，抢购价格较低的生活必需品。【原文：Costco Wholesale beat fourth-quarter revenue estimates on Thursday, as Americans hunting for bargains flocked to the membership-only retail chain to snap up lower-priced essentials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/costco-beats-quarterly-revenue-estimates-strong-demand-cheaper-essentials-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5UZQSFLXQVN2BJNA6EKE6VYPZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:18:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊 AWS 首席执行官斥责员工产品推出缓慢]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社查阅的一份会议记录显示，亚马逊网络服务公司（Amazon Web Services）高层周四对员工进行了告诫，称他们在 12 月举行的首届 "重塑"（Reinvent）客户活动中，云计算服务提供商推出产品的速度太慢。【原文：Amazon Web Services' top executive admonished staff on Thursday for what he called slow product rollouts by the cloud computing provider at its premier Reinvent customer event in December, according to a transcript of a meeting reviewed by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/amazons-aws-ceo-chides-staff-slow-product-rollouts-2025-09-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UI25YKWDSJNJ5CLQKFR7K5PMYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>