<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:04:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:04:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，巴里克矿业公司将马里黄金联合企业从 2025 年产量预测中剔除]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴里克矿业公司（Barrick Mining）的四位消息人士告诉路透社，该公司已将其马里黄金联合企业从其 2025 年的总体产量预测中剔除，这加剧了该公司与旨在提高西非国家收入的新采矿立法之间长达两年的争议所造成的影响。【原文：Barrick Mining has removed its Mali gold complex from its overall output forecast for 2025, four sources told Reuters, adding to fallout from a two-year dispute over new mining legislation aimed at boosting the West African country's revenue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/barrick-mining-removes-mali-gold-complex-2025-output-forecast-sources-say-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F5PV3NBXXVN55LKFQSMD226Q6I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，阿波罗和 Irth Capital 提出了收购约翰老爹的要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位熟悉此事的人士周三表示，阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）和伊思资本管理公司（Irth Capital Management）已与约翰爸爸国际公司（Papa John's International）接触，希望达成一项交易，将这家美国比萨连锁店私有化。【原文：Apollo Global Management and Irth Capital Management have approached Papa John's International for a deal that would take the U.S. pizza chain private, two people familiar with the matter said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/apollo-irth-capital-made-an-offer-buy-papa-johns-sources-say-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IANPAZBZHNJQNAE4M7TAJ4FYZM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌任命内部人士卡武克库奥卢领导人工智能产品开发工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的首席执行官桑达尔-皮查伊（Sundar Pichai）给公司领导人的一份备忘录，随着人工智能进入主流应用的新阶段，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周三任命了一位内部人士领导未来的人工智能产品开发。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Wednesday appointed an insider to lead its future AI-powered product development, as AI enters a new phase of mainstream adoption, according to a memo from CEO Sundar Pichai to company leaders seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/google-names-insider-kavukcuoglu-lead-ai-powered-product-development-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A6ACONDQGVKITGY4UXMHCZNB7A</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者报告》敦促国会放弃电动汽车税提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个有影响力的消费者组织周三敦促共和党立法者放弃对电动汽车征收 250 美元年费以支付道路维修费用的计划。【原文：An influential consumer organization on Wednesday urged Republican lawmakers to drop a plan to impose a proposed $250 annual fee on electric cars to pay for road repairs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/consumer-reports-urges-congress-drop-electric-vehicle-tax-proposal-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FF76ITCG35PW7AWQMYZA6IQTAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受对华征收 145% 关税影响，美国 5 月海产品进口大幅下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据 Descartes Datamyne 的数据，在唐纳德-特朗普总统对来自中国的许多商品征收 145% 的短期关税后，5 月份美国最繁忙的几个海港的进口量急剧下降，导致贸易停滞不前。【原文：Imports at several of the busiest U.S. seaports dropped sharply in May, after President Donald Trump's short-lived 145% tariffs on many goods from China stalled trade, according to data from Descartes Datamyne.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-ocean-imports-plunged-may-145-tariffs-china-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VI5ANRS26ZP6VMVGVIC6NKYIXQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:10:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国月度预算赤字降至 3160 亿美元，因为关税增加了关税收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周三表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收新的高额进口关税，美国海关税收几乎翻了两番，达到创纪录的 230 亿美元，美国政府 5 月份的预算赤字为 3160 亿美元，比去年同期下降了 9% 或 310 亿美元。【原文：The U.S. government posted a $316 billion budget deficit for May, down 9%, or $31 billion, from a year earlier, as customs receipts nearly quadrupled to a record $23 billion due to President Donald Trump's steep new import tariffs, the Treasury Department said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-monthly-budget-deficit-falls-316-billion-tariffs-boost-customs-receipts-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TT5KYJN3IBN6ZHXAPXDPGFFA5E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[优步起诉佛罗里达律师事务所和医疗诊所在车祸中欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[打车公司优步（Uber）对迈阿密一家律师事务所和迈阿密一家医疗中心提起诉讼，指控他们策划了一起医疗和保险骗局，其中涉及伪造汽车碰撞事故。【原文：Ride-hailing company Uber filed a lawsuit against a Miami law firm and a Miami medical center accusing them of orchestrating a medical and insurance scam that involved staged car collisions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/uber-sues-florida-law-firm-medical-clinics-fraud-over-car-crashes-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R52362NHFBLJDMBW5RBWKARN7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:52:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在奥斯汀推出机器人出租车，测试马斯克对自动驾驶未来的愿景]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉本月将在其大本营德克萨斯州奥斯汀市推出自动驾驶 "robotaxis"，面临生存考验。【原文：Tesla faces an existential test this month as it aims to launch self-driving “robotaxis” in its home base of Austin, Texas, where public-safety officials are increasingly concerned about the state’s anti-regulation stance toward autonomous vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-robotaxi-rollout-austin-tests-musks-vision-self-driving-future-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEHGT6MOQZKAVPP2PKB7SEBRGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:34:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Voyager Technologies 估值 38 亿美元，纽交所首日股价上涨逾一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[旅行者科技公司（Voyager Technologies）的股票周三在纽约证券交易所首次亮相时上涨了 125%，这家国防和太空公司的估值达到 38 亿美元。【原文：Shares of Voyager Technologies rose 125% in their New York Stock Exchange debut on Wednesday, valuing the defense and space firm at $3.8 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/voyager-technologies-valued-38-billion-shares-more-than-double-nyse-debut-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UQYEKYKJAJLQFOMQUXOYSWSTOM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉因华纳兄弟分拆将其信用评级下调至垃圾级]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周早些时候，华纳兄弟发现公司宣布分拆，信用评级机构惠誉国际评级公司（Fitch Ratings）周三将该公司的评级下调至垃圾级，因为投资者正在权衡这一交易对其债务持有人可能产生的影响。【原文：Credit ratings agency Fitch Ratings on Wednesday downgraded Warner Bros Discovery to junk status following the company's announced split-up earlier this week, as investors weigh the deal's likely impact on holders of its debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/warner-bros-credit-rating-downgraded-junk-by-fitch-split-up-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJ43AWKORFJWZAG5TEBTWZMTMQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷市场交易商谨慎欢呼 "没有克里斯蒂娜的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷交易商周三欢呼雀跃，因为法院对民粹主义的前总统克里斯蒂娜-费尔南德斯-德基什内尔（Cristina Fernandez de Kirchner）下达了政治禁令。【原文：Argentine traders cheered on Wednesday a court's political ban on populist former President Cristina Fernandez de Kirchner, a powerful but divisive politician who often clashed with investors and creditors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/argentine-market-traders-cautiously-cheer-future-without-cristina-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFCACVS36NLH5KSKN62TFWUL24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔加拿大分公司将关闭汉密尔顿拉丝厂，裁员 153 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[钢铁制造商安赛乐米塔尔的加拿大长材部门周三表示，作为拉丝业务重组的一部分，该部门将裁员 153 人。【原文：Steelmaker ArcelorMittal's Canadian long products unit said on Wednesday that it was laying off 153 workers as part of a restructuring of its wire drawing activities.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/arcelormittals-canadian-unit-close-hamilton-wire-drawing-mill-lay-off-153-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6XF5OYCOZODXA5B3HCFRCEX74</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:54:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[铂金飙升，钯金因需求窄幅而落后]]></title><description><![CDATA[铂金和钯金价格本月双双反弹，分别创下四年多和七个月来的新高，但分析师表示，由于钯金的需求基础较窄，他们对钯金的前景仍持谨慎态度。【原文：Platinum and palladium prices have both rallied this month, notching a more than four-year and seven-month high respectively, but analysts say they remain more cautious about the outlook for palladium due to its narrower demand base.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/platinum-surges-palladium-lags-narrow-demand-profile-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UVFTEIUTTZNC3LERC2LALJAYSU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特称共和党税收法案将收回美国企业税收主权]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）表示，共和党正在审议的税收和支出法案将防止数千亿美元的企业税款流向外国政府。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said that the Republican tax and spending bill under consideration will prevent hundreds of billions of dollars of corporate tax payments from going to foreign governments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bessent-says-republican-tax-bill-will-reclaim-us-corporate-tax-sovereignty-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y3RN7NQJ3JJTZDDUNZ53YLDKEQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:17:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：中国对稀土出口许可证放宽了六个月的限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周三援引知情人士的话报道称，中国正在对美国汽车制造商和生产商的稀土出口许可证设置六个月的限制。【原文：China is putting a six-month limit on rare-earth export licenses for U.S. automakers and manufacturers, The Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-puts-six-month-limit-its-ease-rare-earth-export-licenses-wsj-reports-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNNKKYCUSVJM3FAXLQQEENDSDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行预计市场业务将实现第 13 个季度收入增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行首席执行官布莱恩-莫伊尼汉（Brian Moynihan）周三表示，美国银行预计其市场业务在第二季度将实现连续第13个季度的收入增长，投资银行业务收费将达到12亿美元。【原文：Bank of America expects its markets business could post a 13th consecutive quarter of revenue growth and investment banking fees could hit up to $1.2 billion in the second quarter, CEO Brian Moynihan said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bank-america-expects-markets-business-post-13th-quarter-revenue-growth-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZP4QPTSFUJJONOXX34NZ2PTKD4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提名的 FAA 候选者誓言对波音公司 "问责]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）总统提名的联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）负责人誓言要追究波音公司的责任，因为一系列的安全问题引发了人们对这家美国飞机制造商的质疑。【原文：President Donald Trump's nominee to head the Federal Aviation Administration vowed to hold Boeing accountable after a series of safety issues have raised questions about the U.S. planemaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/trump-faa-nominee-vows-hold-boeing-accountable-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2SOFS6PKRIAXMHA2HGIWU5VIQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官延长 Citgo 拍卖日程，将最终听证会推迟至八月]]></title><description><![CDATA[据周三提交的一份文件显示，特拉华州的一名美国法官延长了由法院组织的委内瑞拉炼油商 Citgo Petroleum 母公司股份拍卖的时间表，将销售过程的最后听证会推迟至 8 月 18 日。【原文：A U.S. judge in Delaware has extended the schedule for a court-organized auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned refiner Citgo Petroleum, moving the sales process's final hearing to August 18, according to a filing on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-judge-extends-citgo-auctions-schedule-moves-final-hearing-august-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FW4OZGMP4BKJ3ND363SJLBRVHE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼和环球影业起诉图片创作者 Midjourney 侵犯版权]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔特-迪斯尼公司和康卡斯特旗下的环球公司周三对 Midjourney 公司提起版权诉讼，称其流行的人工智能图像生成器是 "剽窃的无底洞"，因为它使用了这两家公司最知名的角色。【原文：Walt Disney and Comcast's Universal filed a copyright lawsuit against Midjourney on Wednesday, calling its popular AI-powered image generator a "bottomless pit of plagiarism" for its use of the studios' best-known characters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-universal-sue-image-creator-midjourney-copyright-infringement-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q33VOHW2LZMCHKREXB5KJOC3XU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美联储应将利率下调 "整整一个百分点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三重申了他的观点，即美联储应将利率下调一个百分点，并称最新的通胀数据 "非常好"。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday reiterated his view that the Federal Reserve should cut interest rates by one percentage point, saying the latest inflation figures were "great."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-fed-should-lower-rates-by-one-full-point-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HV55OCFENOVDI2ECBGBACTFSA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:07:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长贝森特呼吁中国成为贸易谈判中的 "可靠伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）周三呼吁中国信守其在上个月于日内瓦达成的美国初步贸易协议中所做的承诺，此前数小时他和其他中美官员就实施该协议的新框架达成了一致。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on Wednesday called on China to uphold its commitments under an initial U.S. trade agreement reached in Geneva last month, hours after he and other U.S. and Chinese officials agreed on a new framework to implement the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-treasurys-bessent-calls-china-be-reliable-partner-trade-negotiations-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOROEVQFDBOFZEHLUNHKQ2YMGQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[喜力将在墨西哥投资超过 27 亿美元，直至 2028 年]]></title><description><![CDATA[啤酒制造商喜力公司首席执行官周三表示，该公司将在墨西哥投资 27.5 亿美元用于不同的项目。【原文：Beer maker Heineken will invest $2.75 billion in different projects in Mexico, the company's CEO in the country said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/heineken-will-invest-over-27-bln-mexico-through-2028-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ULEUM226GBLFBIW2OJISXDJLEI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:04:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长希思表示墨西哥央行可能暂停降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长乔纳森-希思（Jonathan Heath）周三在接受当地报纸《经济学家报》（El Economista）采访时表示，面对通胀反弹，墨西哥央行可能会暂停下调基准利率。【原文：Mexico's central bank may pause cuts to its benchmark interest rate in the face of an inflationary rebound, deputy governor Jonathan Heath said in an interview with local newspaper El Economista published on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexicos-central-bank-may-pause-rate-cuts-deputy-governor-heath-says-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IISJXEZPSRJA5KTFGBT6JKSCKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对美联储降息的希望使美国国债收益率在供应激增前保持低位：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[债券策略师认为，美国国债收益率将进一步下降，他们对美联储在暂停降息半年多后恢复降息的预期依然不减，即使交易商将承销大量新的供应。【原文：U.S. Treasury yields are set to decline further according to bond strategists who are clinging to expectations the Federal Reserve resumes cutting interest rates after pausing for more than half a year even as dealers are set to underwrite a deluge of new supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/hopes-fed-rate-cuts-keep-us-treasury-yield-views-low-ahead-supply-deluge-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGSD76YEJBJVRG7JTWTHVHPZII</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:45:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔伦能源公司与亚马逊签署核电协议，为数据中心提供燃料]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国公用事业公司塔伦能源公司（Talen Energy）周三宣布扩大与亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）的核能合作，从其位于宾夕法尼亚州的苏斯奎汉纳（Susquehanna）电厂向亚马逊网络服务（AWS）数据中心提供多达 1920 兆瓦的电力。【原文：U.S. utility Talen Energy announced on Wednesday an expanded nuclear energy partnership with Amazon.com to supply up to 1,920 megawatts of electricity from its Susquehanna plant in Pennsylvania to Amazon Web Services (AWS) data centers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/talen-energy-amazon-sign-nuclear-power-deal-fuel-data-centers-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZNJJOTCRYZNFDO47ZIICYSD77Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 五月消费者价格温和上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于汽油价格依然低迷，5 月份美国消费者价格略有上涨，但由于关税提高了进口商品的成本，通胀可能在未来几个月内回升。【原文：U.S. consumer prices rose slightly in May as gasoline prices remained subdued, but inflation is likely to pick up in the months as tariffs boost the cost of imported goods.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/view-may-consumer-prices-rise-moderately-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMNTJOKFH5NYJAQEJBLCP6MGG4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:04:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德与美国生物技术公司 Deep Apple 签订价值 8.12 亿美元的减肥药许可协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦诺和诺德公司（Novo Nordisk）与生物技术公司 Deep Apple Therapeutics 达成了一项价值高达 8.12 亿美元的合作协议，共同开发治疗肥胖症等心脏代谢疾病的药物。【原文：Denmark's Novo Nordisk is partnering with biotech company Deep Apple Therapeutics in a deal worth up to $812 million to develop drugs for cardiometabolic diseases, including obesity, the California-based company said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-signs-812-million-weight-loss-drug-license-deal-with-us-biotech-deep-apple-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHPPRG6NRZJHTFTNAPYOO3XQ7M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者撤出美股，转向欧洲和新兴市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于对美国财政政策、债务增加以及贸易关税引发经济衰退风险的担忧日益加剧，全球投资者已将资金从美国股市转移到欧洲和新兴市场资产。【原文：Global investors have moved money from U.S. equities and into European and emerging markets assets, as concerns mount over U.S. fiscal policy, rising debt and the risk that trade tariffs will trigger a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-fundflows-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C62DCCMUVRN3XL3FCEGRZSRX4M</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团财务总监对瑞士资本规则表示失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团（UBS）财务总监托德-塔克纳（Todd Tuckner）周三对拟议中的瑞士新资本法规表示失望。【原文：UBS finance chief Todd Tuckner voiced his disappointment on Wednesday over proposed new Swiss capital regulations, which he said was the beginning of a possibly long process that the bank intends to contribute to.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-finance-chief-voices-disappointment-over-swiss-capital-rules-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCDMOOESIRKMNCLC3V7WUFNURY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:51:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易员加大对美联储 9 月开始降息的押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，上月通胀率低于预期加深了金融市场的信念，即美联储将在9月前开始削减利率，而不是等待更长的时间。【原文：Cooler-than-expected inflation last month deepened conviction in financial markets Wednesday that the Federal Reserve will start cutting interest-rate cuts by September rather than waiting longer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/traders-add-bets-september-start-fed-rate-cuts-2025-06-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K536YRRIZVPXJAGJUZITUAFBDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>