<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:07:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:07:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普宣布加征关税后德国汽车制造商股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁从 8 月 1 日起对欧盟进口产品征收 30% 的关税，但并未提及对汽车的特殊待遇，德国汽车制造商的股票周一下跌。【原文：Shares in Germany's carmakers fell on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump threatened a 30% tariff on EU imports from August 1, with no mentioning of a special treatment for autos, which remain subject to a 27.5% duty.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-german-carmakers-fall-after-trump-tariff-announcement-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUT47CKO3RPULHPGG3UEW7WSCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对欧盟和墨西哥征收新关税，欧洲股市下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最近威胁要对欧盟和墨西哥征收高额关税，令投资者惶恐不安，欧洲股市周一下跌，汽车行业领跌。【原文：European shares fell on Monday, led by automobiles, as the U.S. President Donald Trump's latest threat to impose steep tariffs on the European Union and Mexico kept investors on edge.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/european-shares-fall-trumps-new-tariff-threats-eu-mexico-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EWGLA75BGRIOTBOLUW3AUFXVOM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马斯克表示不支持特斯拉与 xAI 合并]]></title><description><![CDATA[亿万富翁埃隆-马斯克周一在 X 上发表文章称，他不支持特斯拉与他的人工智能初创公司 xAI 合并。【原文：Billionaire Elon Musk said in a Monday post on X he does not support a merger between Tesla and his artificial intelligence startup xAI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/musk-says-he-does-not-support-merger-between-tesla-xai-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYV7VLDNORPPDNVZW4ANEJHEJ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟委员称欧盟与美国即将达成良好贸易协定]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易委员马洛斯-塞夫科维奇（Maros Sefcovic）周一表示，欧盟和美国的贸易谈判正接近一个对双方都有利的结果。【原文：The European Union and United States are approaching a good outcome for both sides in their trade talks, EU trade commissioner Maros Sefcovic said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-us-approaching-good-trade-deal-eu-commissioner-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMPBH6P7CNODRL5TVSRSJBULBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度航空致命空难调查 "远未结束" 首席执行官在初步报告发布数日后表示]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度航空公司首席执行官坎贝尔-威尔逊（Campbell Wilson）周一在一份内部备忘录中说，印度航空公司对上个月在艾哈迈达巴德市失事的梦幻客机的调查 "远未结束"，并补充说，印度航空公司仍对进一步的调查持开放态度，并告诫不要 "过早下结论"。【原文：The investigation of the crashed Air India Dreamliner in Ahmedabad city last month is "far from over", the airline's Chief Executive Campbell Wilson said in an internal memo on Monday, adding that the airline remains open to further inquiries and cautioned against "premature conclusions".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fatal-air-india-crash-probe-far-over-says-ceo-days-after-prelim-report-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JKEJSG3LCNKF3IZOS5OPRUZEHA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国准备命令航空公司检查波音飞机的燃料开关]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国交通部对外媒体发言人周一表示，韩国交通部正准备命令国内所有运营波音喷气机的航空公司根据美国联邦航空管理局2018年的一项建议检查燃油开关。【原文：South Korea's transport ministry is preparing to order all airlines in the country that operate Boeing jets to examine fuel switches in accordance with a 2018 advisory from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration, the ministry's foreign media spokesperson said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/south-korea-preparing-order-airlines-check-fuel-switches-boeing-jets-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZD7XJSFFDBPHNDTHBEM6FL7M44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[葛兰素史克寻求 FDA 批准扩大 RSV 疫苗在成人中的使用范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国制药商葛兰素史克公司（GSK）周一表示，它已向美国食品和药物管理局提交了一份申请，要求将其呼吸道合胞病毒（RSV）疫苗的使用范围扩大到50岁以下的高危成人。【原文：British drugmaker GSK said on Monday it had submitted an application to the U.S. Food and Drug Administration to extend the use of its respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccine to adults under the age of 50 at a higher risk of the disease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/gsk-seeks-fda-nod-expanded-use-rsv-vaccine-adults-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MQUQ2VNK4FMDFAN2DOIFEOBQGE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:42:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行将标普 500 指数年底目标价上调至 6250 点]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大皇家银行资本市场（RBC Capital Markets）周日将 S&amp;P 500 指数的年终目标从 5730 点上调至 6250 点，这是今年以来第二次上调目标，理由是投资者情绪更加浓厚，对 2026 年经济前景的关注度也越来越高。【原文：RBC Capital Markets on Sunday raised its S&amp;P 500 index year-end target to 6,250 from 5,730, its second hike this year, citing stronger investor sentiment and growing focus on 2026 economic prospects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/rbc-lifts-sp-500-year-end-price-target-6250-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WOIWXTCXEVN3VLJHRGBZKLY7XE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新加坡四年来最大规模首次公开募股后，数据中心 NTT DC REIT 首秀不温不火]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡的 NTT DC REIT 是一家数据中心房地产投资信托公司，在新加坡四年来最大的首次公开募股中，该公司借助人工智能的热潮募集了 7.73 亿美元，但周一的首次公开募股却表现平平。【原文：Singapore's NTT DC REIT , a data centre real estate investment trust, had a lacklustre market debut on Monday after riding a wave of AI interest to raise $773 million in the city-state's biggest IPO in four years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/data-centre-ntt-dc-reit-opens-flat-debut-after-singapores-biggest-ipo-4-years-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SU2QFRFARJPPKEK6VXM4SRXVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:17:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国有条件批准 Synopsys 收购 Ansys]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据中国市场监管部门周一发布的一份声明，该部门有条件地批准了软件公司 Synopsys 收购 Ansys 的交易。【原文：China's market regulator has granted a conditional approval for software firm Synopsys to acquire Ansys , according to a statement released by the regulator on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-grants-conditional-approval-synopsys-acquire-ansys-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUDCYV5T4BKWLOHLFFM4HIK6QQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利外长称欧盟准备向美国征收 21 亿欧元关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利外交部长安东尼奥-塔亚尼（Antonio Tajani）周一在接受报纸采访时说，如果两国无法达成贸易协议，欧盟已经准备好了一份对美国商品征收价值210亿欧元（约合245.2亿美元）关税的清单。【原文：The European Union has already prepared a list of tariffs worth 21 billion euros ($24.52 billion) on U.S. goods if the two countries fail to reach a trade deal, Italy's Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani said in a newspaper interview on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-ready-hit-us-with-21-bln-euro-tariff-list-italy-foreign-minister-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEBP2R6S5FNORMBGPFPURWZ5DQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[扭亏为盈一年后，博柏利投资者看到了进步]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔希-舒尔曼（Josh Schulman）就任巴宝莉首席执行官一年后，受命扭转这一英国奢侈品牌的颓势，尽管销售额仍在下降，但投资者对复苏的早期迹象表示满意。【原文：A year after Josh Schulman became Burberry's CEO with a mandate to turn the British luxury brand around, investors say they're pleased with early signs of recovery even though sales are still falling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/year-into-turnaround-burberry-investors-see-progress-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPHFAEEPNFNI3KWFNK7K3MMKEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标利用关税抢占头条的艺术]]></title><description><![CDATA[韦恩-科尔对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Wayne Cole.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDOVTZY44JNYBPJUWOMQAEKRZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 04:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币首次突破 12 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，比特币首次突破 12 万美元关口，成为全球最大的加密货币的一个重要里程碑，因为投资者押注于本周该行业长期寻求的政策胜利。【原文：Bitcoin crossed the $120,000 level for the first time on Monday, marking a major milestone for the world's largest cryptocurrency as investors bet on long-sought policy wins for the industry this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bitcoin-crosses-120000-record-high-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJ4D6Q4LOBLHPINEEFAIFQ3JC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 03:54:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税大限将至，中国出口回暖]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国的出口在 6 月份恢复了一些势头，而进口则出现反弹，因为在 8 月份的最后期限即将到来之前，企业急于出货，以利用北京和华盛顿之间脆弱的关税休战。【原文：China's exports regained some momentum in June while imports rebounded, as firms rushed out shipments to capitalise on a fragile tariff truce between Beijing and Washington ahead of a looming August deadline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-exports-imports-pick-up-trump-tariff-deadline-looms-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A75BNJ4UMZKBVDOF6EHEL3NYN4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 03:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[越南 CMC 2.5 亿美元超大规模数据中心获批]]></title><description><![CDATA[越南科技公司 CMC Corp. 周一表示，胡志明市当局已批准该公司在胡志明市建设一个价值 2.5 亿美元的超大规模数据中心。【原文：Vietnam's tech firm CMC Corp. has got approval from the authorities of Ho Chi Minh City to build a $250-million hyperscale data centre there, it said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/vietnams-cmc-gets-approval-250-mln-hyperscale-data-centre-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LDM6OWLHFRPCZCAL6SNOJ6PJBA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 03:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国财政部长表示泰国考虑对更多美国进口产品实行零关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周一表示，泰国正在考虑对更多的美国进口产品实行零关税。【原文：Thailand is considering offering zero tariffs on more U.S. imports, the finance minister said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/thailand-considering-offering-zero-tariffs-more-us-imports-finance-minister-says-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G72QBLSDRBJLJOYDH6SU57KS2Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 02:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国称八月可能达成美国框架贸易协议，农产品市场准入问题已摆上桌面]]></title><description><![CDATA[据当地媒体报道，韩国最高贸易特使周一表示，韩国有可能在8月1日的最后期限之前与美国达成一项 "原则性 "贸易协议，并表示首尔可能会对允许更多农产品进入其农业市场持开放态度。【原文：South Korea's top trade envoy said on Monday it may be possible to strike an "in-principle" trade deal with the United States by an August 1 deadline and signalled Seoul may be open to allow greater access to its agriculture markets, local media reported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/south-korea-trade-envoy-may-be-able-strike-framework-deal-with-us-by-aug-1-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EXA6473MNJO55NGBKNQT7YCIRY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 02:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马来西亚称原产美国的人工智能芯片需要贸易许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[马来西亚贸易部周一表示，原产于美国的高性能人工智能芯片的出口、转运和过境将受到贸易许可证的限制，即日起生效。【原文：Malaysia's trade ministry said on Monday that the export, transshipment and transit of high-performance AI chips of U.S. origin will be subject to a trade permit, effective immediately.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/malaysia-says-trade-permit-required-ai-chips-us-origin-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">66XYZB5JYZIQFCBEKKVUFCRZLA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 02:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理在铁矿石矿工与中国钢铁制造商会面时称赞绿色钢铁]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴尼塞（Anthony Albanese）周一在上海表示，澳中两国应在绿色钢材问题上加强合作，同时他还呼吁世界最大的钢铁生产商解决金属产能过剩问题。【原文：Australia and China should cooperate more closely over green steel, Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said in Shanghai on Monday, even as he called on the world's largest steelmaker to address excess capacity for the metal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/australian-pm-albanese-pledges-work-with-china-excess-steel-capacity-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F7KF5HEDVKWHK26LWGOYHLF6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 01:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油价格上涨，投资者关注特朗普对俄罗斯的声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者担心美国对俄罗斯的进一步制裁可能会影响全球供应，油价周一微幅走高，延续了上周五超过2%的涨势，但沙特产量的增加和持续的关税不确定性限制了油价的涨幅。【原文：Oil prices nudged higher on Monday, adding to gains of more than 2% from Friday, as investors eyed further U.S. sanctions on Russia that may affect global supplies, but a ramp-up in Saudi output and ongoing tariff uncertainty limited gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-edges-up-investors-eye-trump-statement-russia-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DHTBD5RSLZIPVOT3HGN6MBQIUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国贸易政策令人困惑，华尔街随亚洲股市下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街期货下跌拖累亚洲股市周一走低，原因是美国关税战的最新一轮威胁令投资者惶恐不安，尽管人们希望这主要是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的虚张声势，但其影响有限。【原文：Losses in Wall Street futures dragged Asian stocks lower on Monday as the latest round of threats in the U.S. tariff wars kept investors on edge, though the fallout was limited by hopes this was mainly bluster by President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NLZ34NNA2VOV7FDT3IZYOH4LJI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普威胁对欧盟征收 30% 的关税后欧元走软]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧元周一跌至三周低点，而墨西哥比索也在唐纳德-特朗普总统威胁从 8 月 1 日起对来自美国两个最大贸易伙伴的进口商品征收 30% 的关税后承压。【原文：The euro fell to a three-week low on Monday while the Mexican peso also came under pressure after President Donald Trump threatened to impose a 30% tariff on imports from two of the largest U.S. trading partners beginning August 1.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/euro-eases-after-trump-threatens-30-tariffs-eu-2025-07-14/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NKQ5G4MZFBMANEKFNHMTSKSWEE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，财富基金热衷于主动管理--以及中国--以抵御波动]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Invesco）对管理着 27 万亿美元资产的主权基金和中央银行进行的一项调查显示，全球主权财富基金正在转向积极的基金管理和对中国的投资，而各国央行则在分散储备，以应对动荡的全球环境。【原文：The world's sovereign wealth funds are turning to active fund management and investments in China, while central banks are diversifying reserves to weather a volatile global environment, an Invesco survey of sovereign funds and central banks managing $27 trillion in assets showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/wealth-funds-warm-active-management-china-weather-volatility-report-shows-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RJY5ZHTS4VJQPFZ3PQHLLGW3FM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 23:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西门子和 SAP 呼吁欧盟修改人工智能法规 - FAZ]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子和 SAP 的首席执行官们敦促欧盟修改其人工智能立法，称现行规定扼杀了创新。【原文：Siemens and SAP CEOs have urged the European Union to revise its artificial intelligence legislation, saying the current rules stifle innovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/siemens-sap-call-eu-revise-its-ai-regulations-faz-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWBXMP4OTNN4PA7HDEYJRX2X4Y</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 21:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，在印航调查期间，美国联邦航空局和波音公司通知燃油开关锁是安全的，有文件为证]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份文件显示，美国联邦航空管理局和波音公司已私下发出通知，称波音飞机上的燃油开关锁是安全的。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration and Boeing have privately issued notifications that the fuel switch locks on Boeing planes are safe, a document seen by Reuters showed and four sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/amid-air-india-probe-us-faa-boeing-notify-fuel-switch-locks-are-safe-document-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZYIKMV7ZENJPFIL27OYR2C2EDA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国葡萄酒和奶酪制造商称美国关税将造成严重打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[古斯-特罗姆皮兹和阿迪-纳波利塔诺报道【原文：By Gus Trompiz and Ardee Napolitano】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/french-wine-cheese-makers-say-us-tariffs-would-hit-hard-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2ITL3V5PRPSNKRJVSV4PSB3R4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 13:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[冯德莱恩：欧盟将在八月前搁置美国的贸易反制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[她说，使用欧盟的《反胁迫文书》尚未提上议事日程。【原文：Use of the EU's Anti-Coercion Instrument was not yet on the table, she said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/eu-keep-us-trade-countermeasures-hold-until-august-says-von-der-leyen-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHYQMANBZBL6PABCOTMPIYZT7M</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 12:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达首席执行官将于 7 月 16 日在北京举行媒体见面会]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司的一位官员周日表示，该公司首席执行官黄仁勋将于7月16日在北京举行媒体见面会，这是他继4月份强调中国市场重要性之后第二次访问中国。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang will hold a media briefing in Beijing on July 16, an official from the company said on Sunday, marking his second visit to the country after a trip in April where he stressed the importance of the Chinese market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-ceo-hold-media-briefing-beijing-july-16-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D764ZT2M75NVTLO6VUHJW7QIXM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:12:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国资深政治家期待与特朗普就欧盟关税争端展开更多谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位德国高级政治家周日表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）威胁要对欧盟提高关税从而加剧贸易战之后，欧盟和华盛顿可以进一步谈判并推迟提高进口关税。【原文：A senior German politician said on Sunday the European Union and Washington could negotiate further and postpone higher import duties after U.S. President Donald Trump ramped up the trade war by threatening a hike in tariffs on the bloc.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/senior-german-politician-expects-more-talks-eu-tariff-dispute-with-trump-2025-07-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMWV2DDZZ5IBJFP7F73VVPKZ6Q</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:28:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>