<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:34:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:34:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[巴西部长介入 JBS 奴隶劳动调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的文件，巴西劳工部长路易斯-马里尼奥（Luiz Marinho）正在对一项调查进行不寻常的最终审查，该调查可能会将肉类包装商 JBS SA 的一个家禽部门列入黑名单，因为该部门的工人遭受了 "类似奴役的条件"。【原文：Brazilian Labor Minister Luiz Marinho is carrying out an unusual final review of an investigation that could blacklist a poultry unit of meatpacker JBS SA for subjecting workers to "slavery-like conditions," according to documents seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/brazilian-minister-intervenes-jbs-slave-labor-investigation-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5COGCYRW4ZKLBEDXNLNFIVW2SA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔与 Nvidia 的交易如何帮助英特尔实现下一代芯片制造]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，英伟达（Nvidia）与英特尔（Intel）的交易可能会使这家陷入困境的芯片制造商的下一代制造技术站稳脚跟，即使这家人工智能芯片领导者没有直接承诺使用该技术制造自己的芯片。【原文：Nvidia's deal with Intel could put the struggling chipmaker's next-generation manufacturing technology on a stronger footing, even without a direct commitment from the AI chip leader to use that technology to make its own chips, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-intels-nvidia-deal-could-help-intels-next-generation-chip-manufacturing-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6TZPBJHRZVPLFJGJCJUW7YAKVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士和备忘录称，软银愿景基金将裁员 20%，转向大胆的人工智能押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份备忘录和一位熟悉该计划的消息人士透露，软银集团将在全球范围内裁掉近 20% 的愿景基金团队，因为该公司将把资源转移到创始人孙正义在美国的大规模人工智能赌注上。【原文：SoftBank Group will lay off nearly 20% of its Vision Fund team globally as it shifts resources to founder Masayoshi Son’s large-scale artificial intelligence bets in the United States, according to a memo seen by Reuters and a source familiar with the plan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/softbank-vision-fund-lay-off-20-employees-shift-bold-ai-bets-source-memo-say-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4IEQWCVHFI5TBMYZUVGC2FH6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:38:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据CNBC报道，Nvidia斥资9亿多美元聘请Enfabrica公司首席执行官并获得技术许可]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 CNBC 周四报道，英伟达（Nvidia）斥资 9 亿多美元聘请了 Enfabrica 首席执行官 Rochan Sankar 和这家人工智能硬件初创公司的其他员工，并获得了该公司的技术许可。【原文：Nvidia has spent over $900 million to hire Enfabrica CEO Rochan Sankar and other staff at the artificial intelligence hardware startup and to license the company's technology, CNBC reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidia-spent-over-900-million-hire-enfabrica-ceo-license-technology-cnbc-reports-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OVXTBFF3ONNUROQU4IQTTNNTLM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱纳尔公布季度利润下降，因购房者承受压力过大]]></title><description><![CDATA[房屋建筑商伦纳（Lennar）周四报告称，由于通胀压力继续拖累住房需求，该公司第三季度利润下降了 46%，并预计第四季度房屋交付量将低于华尔街预期。【原文：Homebuilder Lennar reported a 46% decline in third-quarter profit and forecast fourth-quarter home deliveries below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, as inflationary pressures continued to weigh on housing demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/lennar-reports-lower-quarterly-profit-affordability-pressures-weigh-home-buyers-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SOFNIKT5TZOVNBJQUKXFKPMBRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，迪士尼高管将与基梅尔会面，评估脱口秀节目的未来]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引三位知情人士的话报道，迪斯尼公司高管将与停播的脱口秀主持人吉米-基梅尔（Jimmy Kimmel）会面，讨论其节目的未来。【原文：Walt Disney executives will meet with suspended talk-show host Jimmy Kimmel to discuss the future of his program, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing three people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/walt-disney-executives-meet-with-kimmel-assess-talk-show-future-bloomberg-news-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7SQBQ2EKZK4HOERXNFBTRVYHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[外国持有的美国国债在 7 月份升至历史新高，中国国债持有量下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周四公布的数据显示，在日本和英国的增持带动下，外国持有的美国国债在7月份升至历史峰值，连续第三个月创下历史新高。【原文：Foreign holdings of U.S. Treasuries rose to an all-time peak in July, data from the Treasury Department showed on Thursday, hitting record highs for a third straight month, led by gains in holdings from Japan and the United Kingdom.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/foreign-holdings-us-treasuries-surge-all-time-high-july-chinas-sink-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FS5UHWXPV5P3ZKTNJ26S5JZGS4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马运河开始遴选建设和运营液化石油气管道的公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马运河管理局周四表示，在与感兴趣的公司会面后，已开始竞争性程序，以选择将设计、建造和运营液化石油气（LPG）运输管道的公司。【原文：The Panama Canal has begun a competitive process to select the company that will design, build and operate a pipeline to transport liquefied petroleum gas (LPG), its authority said on Thursday, following meetings with interested companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/panama-canal-starts-process-select-firms-build-operate-lpg-pipeline-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXJGTFYPJNKULBOPPYV2CFI76E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着市场扩大，寰宇一家联盟考虑印度合作伙伴]]></title><description><![CDATA[寰宇一家 "联盟是一个拥有从美国航空公司到澳洲航空公司等 15 个成员的航空集团，其首席执行官表示，随着印度航空市场的持续增长，该联盟正在考虑建立一个印度航空合作伙伴。【原文：The oneworld Alliance, an airline group with 15 members ranging from American Airlines to Qantas Airways , is considering an Indian airline partner as the market continues to grow, its chief executive said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/oneworld-alliance-considers-indian-partner-market-expands-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6ZSZBEUR5OQ3LXAO2PNI3M3RY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:33:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capital One 与社交媒体创作者的诉讼达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[Capital One 与社交媒体创建者达成和解，这些创建者称，有数百万人使用一个免费的浏览器扩展来寻找折扣，但当购物者购买他们的产品和服务时，该扩展却窃取了他们的销售佣金。【原文：Capital One settled a lawsuit by social media creators who said a free browser extension used by millions of people to find discounts stole their sales commissions when shoppers bought their products and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/capital-one-settles-social-media-creators-lawsuit-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VUXW6HWBBJJ5TEVHILOK63IXDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰新任央行行长将面临信誉考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰财政部长预计将在未来几周内宣布新的央行行长人选，经济学家希望此举将标志着央行行长和主席意外离职的动荡时期的结束。【原文：New Zealand's finance minister is expected to announce a new central bank chief in the coming weeks, with economists hoping the move will signal the end of a tumultuous period in which both the bank's governor and chairman unexpectedly departed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-new-central-bank-governor-face-credibility-test-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CFQMKJF3LBMM5NIQXBUECFUCAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：美联储降息，全球股市暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解推动全球市场的各种力量【原文：Making sense of the forces driving global markets】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2NPR6GONGVJMXKIUV6TGJL6T7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft 因司机分类不当向新泽西州赔偿 1940 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[新泽西州官员周四表示，Lyft 已向新泽西州支付了 1940 万美元，因为审计发现这家共享出行公司将 10 万多名司机错误地归类为独立承包商。【原文：Lyft has paid $19.4 million to New Jersey after an audit found the ride-sharing company misclassified more than 100,000 drivers as independent contractors, state officials said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/lyft-paid-194-million-new-jersey-over-driver-misclassifications-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VTFQA6Q3MBI7DKCBFFNABZ5WFE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部官员称，特朗普的人工智能计划支持反垄断执法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部的一位官员周四在纽约表示，作为特朗普政府巩固美国人工智能主导地位计划的一部分，美国反垄断执法人员正在警惕人工智能领域的反竞争行为。【原文：U.S. antitrust enforcers are on guard against anticompetitive behavior in the artificial intelligence sector as part of the Trump administration's plan to cement U.S. AI dominance, a Department of Justice official said in New York on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/trumps-ai-plan-supports-antitrust-enforcement-doj-official-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5LU6YPPNRMI3NBQGYXJ65KZOI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:52:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，随着资金紧张加剧，CFPB 考虑解雇员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位知情人士透露，美国消费者金融保护局正在考虑裁员，因为该机构面临资金紧张问题。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is considering furloughing workers as the agency confronts a funding crunch, according to two people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/cfpb-considers-worker-furloughs-funding-crunch-deepens-sources-say-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NQJWDZFSUZJWLHFX4GABHXBIPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息后第二天，美国企业债券交易量猛增]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美联储在 9 月份会议上降息四分之一个基点的刺激，美国投资级市场的公司债券交易在本周早些时候的平静期后于周四有所回升。【原文：U.S. corporate bond deal-making in the investment-grade market picked up on Thursday following a quiet period earlier in the week, spurred by a quarter basis point rate cut from the Federal Reserve at its September meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-corporate-bond-dealmaking-jumps-day-after-fed-rate-cut-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7P3XWXPA7ZNMFIM6E2TOYPQC34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递季度利润增长，但美国关税削弱了 2026 年盈利预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦快递（FedEx）公布的季度利润有所增长，但预计2026年的每股收益将大大低于分析师的预期，因为该公司预计美国将决定终止对低价值直接面向消费者的货运的关税豁免。【原文：FedEx reported a higher quarterly profit but forecast 2026 earnings per share largely below analysts' estimates, as it anticipates a hit from the U.S. decision to end tariff exemptions on low value direct-to-consumer shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-forecasts-2026-earnings-below-estimates-amid-us-tariff-impact-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Q2OYJUJHXRI6PCQVKZRMMLQ444</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称中国似乎已批准 TikTok 协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四告诉福克斯新闻，本周早些时候，他宣布与中国达成协议，让短视频应用 TikTok 继续在美国运营，听起来中国似乎已经批准了与 TikTok 达成的协议。【原文：President Donald Trump told Fox News on Thursday that it sounded like China had approved a deal on TikTok, after announcing an agreement earlier this week with China that would keep the short-video app operating in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/trump-says-it-sounds-like-china-has-approved-tiktok-deal-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5NU2SWXEVINTAOYSQFRCDDMKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 19:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道埃克石油公司将超越 2025 年钻探目标，高管称可能实现最佳产量目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚国营能源公司 Ecopetrol 负责碳氢化合物业务的副总裁拉斐尔-古兹曼（Rafael Guzman）周四表示，该公司 2025 年钻探 10 口油井的目标将超额完成 20% 至 40%。【原文：Colombia's state-run energy company Ecopetrol is set to exceed its 2025 goal of drilling 10 oil wells by between 20% and 40%, the company's vice-president for hydrocarbons Rafael Guzman said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ecopetrol-beat-2025-drilling-goal-may-best-output-target-executive-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRPIMPT77BO2HJKQ3IJHTC35AY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 19:38:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道知情人士称诺和诺德裁减美国肥胖症教育团队，裁员开始在网上流传]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位接近诺和诺德公司的消息人士透露，该公司已经裁减了一个美国销售团队，该团队的工作重点是为医疗服务提供商提供肥胖症和糖尿病教育，路透社还查阅了该公司在LinkedIn上发布的信息。【原文：Wegovy maker Novo Nordisk has cut a U.S. sales team focused on obesity and diabetes education for healthcare providers, according to two sources close to the company and LinkedIn posts reviewed by Reuters, an early sign of the drugmaker's push to cut costs and regain ground on rival Eli Lilly .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/novo-nordisk-cuts-us-obesity-education-team-layoffs-begin-say-sources-online-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XTKCGOKRPJK2JD77HHHHF6TXBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 19:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌为 Chrome 浏览器添加双子座，避免反垄断破裂]]></title><description><![CDATA[谷歌将从本周四开始把 Gemini 整合到其 Chrome 浏览器中，供美国用户使用。就在几周前，联邦法官在一起反托拉斯案件中避免了谷歌被迫解体的命运。【原文：Google will integrate Gemini into its Chrome browser for users in the U.S. starting Thursday, just weeks after a federal judge spared the company from a forced breakup in an antitrust case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/google-adds-gemini-chrome-browser-after-avoiding-antitrust-breakup-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZXWBSUNLLFPL5FRCLWV7LDGSII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部称美银证券解决了刑事调查问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四表示，美国银行证券部解决了涉及前雇员涉嫌操纵市场计划的刑事调查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department said on Thursday that the Bank of America Securities resolved a criminal investigation involving alleged market manipulation schemes by former employees.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-justice-department-says-bank-america-securities-resolves-criminal-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGCXI3POFZKUBAAUW6RREJ2AII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:26:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡莱尔招聘两名高级管理人员，以促进直接借贷业务发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[私募股权公司凯雷（Carlyle）周四表示，该公司已为其直接借贷业务聘请了两名高级管理人员，以努力提高其在不断增长的市场中的份额。【原文：Private equity firm Carlyle has hired two senior executives for its direct-lending business as it tries to boost its share of a growing market, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/carlyle-makes-two-senior-hires-boost-direct-lending-business-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXT4SMM3IVNOVCKQDY7N3YPYWY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛任命本-斯奈德为首席美国股票策略师，科斯汀退休，备忘录称]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社周四看到的一份内部备忘录显示，高盛已任命本-斯奈德（Ben Snider）为其新任首席美国股票策略师，接替将于今年年底退休的老将大卫-科斯汀（David Kostin）。【原文：Goldman Sachs has named Ben Snider as its new chief U.S. equity strategist, succeeding veteran David Kostin, who is set to retire at the end of the year, according to an internal memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/goldman-names-ben-snider-chief-us-equity-strategist-kostin-retires-memo-says-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DME7N7CJSZLE5BWV26636QSOCI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特拉华州法院重新举行 Citgo 母公司拍卖听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[特拉华州法院为完成委内瑞拉所有的 Citgo 石油公司母公司股份拍卖而举行的为期四天的听证会在短暂暂停后于周四恢复，以便律师审查纽约另一案件的裁决，该裁决确认了以 Citgo 股权作抵押的委内瑞拉违约债券的有效性。【原文：A four-day court hearing in Delaware to complete an auction of shares in the parent of Venezuela-owned Citgo Petroleum resumed on Thursday after a brief suspension to allow lawyers to review a decision in a separate New York case confirming the validity of defaulted Venezuelan bonds collateralized with Citgo equity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/legalindustry/court-hearing-delaware-citgo-parent-auction-resumes-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KI4QWC5HRPKHL7ULQV7KRNXGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[顶级航运企业希望全面修订联合国船舶燃料排放协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[包括希腊主要航运公司在内的一批顶级航运公司周四表示，他们希望修改联合国10月份提交通过的一项旨在减少船用燃料排放的协议，这使美国反对后的协议草案更加复杂。【原文：A group of top shipping companies including leading Greek players said on Thursday they want changes to a United Nations deal tabled for adoption in October that seeks to cut marine fuel emissions, adding complications to the draft accord after U.S. opposition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/top-shipping-players-want-overhaul-un-ship-fuel-emissions-deal-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TMGO5I674FKZNNJSB7WGNCI2GI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全公司 Netskope 首度登陆纳斯达克，股价上涨，估值 87.9 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，Netskope 首次登陆纳斯达克，股价上涨超过 21%，使这家网络安全公司的市值达到 87.9 亿美元。【原文：Shares of Netskope rose over 21% in their debut on Nasdaq on Thursday, giving the cybersecurity firm a market capitalization of $8.79 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/cybersecurity-firm-netskope-valued-879-billion-shares-rise-nasdaq-debut-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FXT46GYJFVKNPAYH2MKRLCE4PA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:06:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普要求美国最高法院允许解雇美联储理事丽莎-库克]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府周四请求美国最高法院允许他继续解雇美联储理事丽莎-库克（Lisa Cook）--此举自 1913 年美联储成立以来从未有过先例--这场法律诉讼危及美联储的独立性。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration asked the U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday to let him move ahead with firing Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook - a move without precedent since the central bank's founding in 1913 - in a legal battle that imperils the Fed's independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-asks-us-supreme-court-allow-firing-fed-governor-lisa-cook-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2PGRHWM5RPGPOOE4T4DWUUWP4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:47:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会指控 Live Nation 和 Ticketmaster 与票务经纪人勾结]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会（U.S. Federal Trade Commission）周四表示，该机构正在起诉 Live Nation 及其票务部门 Ticketmaster，指控它们默许票务经纪人违反其政策，抢购数百万张演唱会门票，然后以高价卖给歌迷。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is suing Live Nation and its ticketing arm Ticketmaster for tacitly allowing ticket brokers to violate its policies and scoop up millions of concert tickets later sold to fans at a significant markup, the agency said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/ftc-accuses-live-nation-ticketmaster-colluding-with-ticket-brokers-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M6PTIFUT75KXFHRMX3E2C3OLIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院将于 11 月 5 日审理特朗普关税案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周四确定于 11 月 5 日就唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收全球关税的合法性进行辩论，这是对这位共和党总统最大胆的行政权力主张之一的一次重大考验，而行政权力一直是其经济和贸易议程的核心。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday set a date of November 5 for arguments it will hear concerning the legality of Donald Trump's sweeping global tariffs in a major test of one of the Republican president's boldest assertions of executive power that has been central to his economic and trade agenda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us-supreme-court-hear-trumps-tariffs-case-november-5-2025-09-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GZDYZSBAFJMTRLMLZT4WWROVHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>