<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:36:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:36:31 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的潜在回归加剧了新兴市场投资者的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统大选的激烈角逐令新兴市场的投资者感到不安，他们担心前总统唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫可能会在新兴市场大放异彩之际对其造成损害。【原文：A tight U.S. presidential election race has unnerved investors in emerging markets, who fear a return of former President Donald Trump to the White House could hurt emerging markets just as they were poised to shine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/potential-return-trump-fuels-concern-among-emerging-market-investors-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSV3A4AACZLONGHT3FPYLPVY2I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[总理哈里斯：苹果退税为爱尔兰基础设施建设带来机遇]]></title><description><![CDATA[爱尔兰总理西蒙-哈里斯（Simon Harris）周四表示，本周欧盟法院下令苹果公司向爱尔兰支付 130 亿欧元（约合 144 亿美元），这为政府提供了解决基础设施、房屋建设和资本项目等迫切需求的机会。【原文：An EU court order this week that Apple pay Ireland 13 billion euros ($14.4 billion) presents the government with opportunities to address pressing infrastructure, housebuilding and capital project needs, Prime Minister Simon Harris said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-back-taxes-hand-ireland-infrastructure-opportunities-pm-harris-says-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QLPVQSNNQNJ6HCVRDOHMVQ6YZU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行收购德国商业银行，并购前景看好，欧洲银行业崛起]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，欧洲银行股继续上扬，主要原因是联合信贷银行（UniCredit）在一天前收购了德国商业银行（Commerzbank）9%的股份。【原文：Shares in European banks continued their upward trend on Thursday, mostly driven by the read-across from UniCredit's sweep to buy a 9% stake in Germany's Commerzbank a day earlier.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/european-banks-rise-unicredits-move-commerzbank-lifts-ma-prospects-forefront-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C53VKDD6BVJKVN3WOCUDZYRQ5I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moderna 预计 2025 年销售额可达 35 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Moderna 周四表示，预计明年的销售额将在 25 亿美元到 35 亿美元之间，并预测新产品的推出将推动 2026 年到 2028 年的年均收入增长率达到 25%。【原文：Moderna on Thursday said it expects sales of between $2.5 billion and $3.5 billion next year, and forecast that new product launches would drive an average annual growth rate of 25% in revenue between 2026 and 2028.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/moderna-expects-up-35-billion-2025-sales-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CEXZFSHPXFKZDAUOMSKQ3F3LNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银资产管理因增长风险削减全球投资组合中的企业债券风险敞口]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银资产管理公司（UBS Asset Management）的一位高级基金经理表示，在市场反弹期间，该公司一直在抛售其全球投资组合中的公司债券，理由是担心经济放缓或美国大选迫在眉睫可能引发波动并抹杀收益。【原文：UBS Asset Management has been selling corporate bonds in its global portfolios during market rallies, a senior fund manager said, citing concerns that a slowing economy or the looming U.S. election could spark volatility and wipe out returns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ubs-asset-management-cuts-exposure-corporate-bonds-global-portfolios-growth-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2QXLQC5SNM6NOGZG255HBRSYY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:13:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在申请失业救济人数公布之前，期货小幅走高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，美国股指期货小幅上涨，在上一交易日扭转跌势收高，市场关注美联储下周可能降息前即将公布的经济数据。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose slightly on Thursday, after reversing a selloff to close higher in the previous session, with focus on upcoming economic data in the lead up to the Federal Reserve's likely interest rate cut next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-marginally-higher-ahead-jobless-claims-numbers-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNIXQHNZ7NOCFB5DSIYKMFOQAI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[专家称，特朗普的加征关税计划将使航运成本飙升，就像2018年一样]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运和零售业专家表示，美国总统竞选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）如果在11月再次入主白宫，其提高进口商品关税的计划将使货运费飙升并加速通货膨胀，就像他在2017-21年任期内所做的那样。【原文：U.S. presidential contender Donald Trump's plan to hike tariffs on imports if he is elected back to the White House in November would send cargo rates soaring and accelerate inflation, just like it did during his 2017-21 term, shipping and retail experts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trumps-plan-hike-tariffs-would-spike-shipping-costs-just-like-2018-experts-say-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWUQUXPM2BLGVOAH4PEEWZ7HAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大选临近，美国汽油价格将降至每加仑 3 美元以下]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师本周表示，美国驾车者最快将在下个月看到汽油价格在三年多来首次降至每加仑 3 美元以下，也就是在他们参加 11 月总统大选投票前不久。【原文：U.S. motorists should see gasoline prices fall below $3 a gallon for the first time in over three years as soon as next month, shortly before they go to vote in November's presidential election, analysts said this week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-gasoline-prices-set-fall-under-3gallon-election-nears-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TJINVBSF2VIMNDHV7N42ZPJCYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:05:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车与现代汽车探讨联合汽车开发项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司和现代汽车公司周四表示，双方已同意探索未来在关键战略领域的合作，包括潜在的联合汽车开发、供应链问题和清洁能源技术。【原文：General Motors and Hyundai Motor Co said on Thursday they have agreed to explore future collaboration across key strategic areas including potential joint vehicle development, supply chain issues and clean-energy technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-hyundai-motor-explore-joint-vehicle-development-projects-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5GXKTIEJFMYJKXDEAWRPTBY4I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工人投票决定合同，波音罢工威胁迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司美国西海岸工厂的工人将于周四就备受批评的新合同和可能的罢工进行投票，这给这家长期生产延误和债务不断增加的飞机制造商带来了巨大压力。【原文：Boeing's U.S. West Coast factory workers will vote on a much-criticized new contract and a possible strike on Thursday, piling pressure on the planemaker as it wrestles with chronic production delays and mounting debt.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-strike-threat-looms-workers-vote-contract-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BIAMHKXWEFIRBN3D7CUVZNKJHI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：第一刀不一定最深]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿曼达-库珀（Amanda Cooper）对美国和全球市场未来一天的展望。【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Amanda Cooper.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7WCHAG52FMH5NQF5CJ2COQ6XI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对约 3,118 辆 VinFast 汽车展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，已对约 3118 辆 VinFast 汽车展开调查，原因是有报告称车道保持辅助系统（Lane Keep Assist System）无法正常工作。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on Thursday said it has opened a probe into about 3,118 VinFast vehicles over reports that the Lane Keep Assist System was not functioning correctly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-opens-probe-into-around-3118-vinfast-vehicles-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KXXWDQLTTVLHBAWJCFCT476XE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:56:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，通用磨坊正在就向 Lactalis 和 Sodiaal 出售北美酸奶业务进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，通用磨坊公司正在洽谈将其在美国和加拿大的酸奶业务分别出售给法国乳制品公司Groupe Lactalis和Sodiaal，这两家公司旗下拥有Yoplait等品牌。【原文：General Mills is in talks to sell its U.S. and Canadian yogurt operations, which houses brands such as Yoplait, to French dairy firms Groupe Lactalis and Sodiaal, respectively, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/general-mills-talks-sell-north-america-yogurt-operations-lactalis-sodiaal-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5232ZX4ZZMSLCXE6LH6JRWVPU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国商业银行、意大利联合信贷银行股价涨幅扩大，因 Orcel 提出计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国商业银行和意大利联合信贷银行周四股价延续涨势，此前意大利银行首席执行官安德烈亚-奥塞尔（Andrea Orcel）提出了收购其德国竞争对手更多股份甚至将其兼并的计划，这加剧了市场对该地区进一步交易的猜测。【原文：Commerzbank and UniCredit shares extended gains on Thursday after the Italian bank's CEO Andrea Orcel laid out plans to buy more of its German rival or even take it over, fuelling speculation about further dealmaking in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/commerzbank-unicredit-shares-extend-gains-orcel-lays-out-plans-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ND3SIYKRWNJ3RLDRJS6QYBFAZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国奇瑞计划投资欧洲，打造欧慕达和Jaecoo品牌]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车制造商奇瑞汽车意大利市场负责人告诉路透社，奇瑞汽车准备斥资数十亿欧元，确保其欧慕达（Omoda）和杰酷（Jaecoo）品牌在三年内得到欧洲客户的青睐。【原文：Chinese carmaker Chery Auto is ready to spend billions of euros to ensure its Omoda and Jaecoo brands are embraced by European customers within three years, the head of the two brands for the Italian market told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-chery-plans-investment-drive-build-omoda-jaecoo-brands-europe-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WPZ77LXDSZK75FXM2NLERV2HFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:11:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗氏公司股价因肥胖药早期试验的副作用结果而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，罗氏公司股价下跌，原因是市场寄予厚望的一种早期肥胖症药物候选产品在最初的人体试验阶段出现了较高的暂时性副作用。【原文：Shares in Roche fell on Thursday after an early-stage obesity pill candidate that carries high market hopes was linked to a high rate of temporary side effects in its initial test phase on humans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/roche-shares-drop-side-effects-result-early-stage-obesity-pill-trial-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BWIPCRGRCJLJ7KO7573RR7IZUQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 07:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰企业因劳动力短缺而雇用更多妇女和青少年]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于与俄罗斯的战争消耗了大量劳动力，企业正试图通过雇用更多女性从事传统上由男性主导的工作，以及求助于青少年、学生和老年工人来弥补劳动力的严重不足。【原文：As the war with Russia drains the labour force, businesses are trying to cover critical shortages by hiring more women in traditionally male-dominated roles and turning to teenagers, students and older workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraine-businesses-hire-more-women-teens-labour-shortages-bite-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5FIC5FWK5PMJFQAFQPSSU3WSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PGIM 开设阿布扎比办事处，加入资金管理公司抢滩阿联酋首都的行列]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国保险公司保德信金融公司（Prudential Financial）的投资管理部门 PGIM 周四表示，该公司已在阿布扎比开设了一家办事处，加入了众多前来阿联酋首都开发日益增长的富裕客户群的资金管理公司的行列。【原文：PGIM, the investment management arm of U.S. insurer Prudential Financial , has opened an office in Abu Dhabi, it said on Thursday, joining a slew of money managers coming to the United Arab Emirates capital to tap a growing pool of wealthy clients.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/pgim-opens-abu-dhabi-office-joining-money-managers-rush-uae-capital-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BL6BSIEMRJ3RNE6JOKO6SLPEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:06:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[杜蕾斯在印度大力推广面向女性和农村消费者的安全套]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年来，全球最大的安全套生产商利洁时（Reckitt Benckiser）一直在设计产品和市场营销，以吸引印度男性购买其杜蕾斯（Durex）品牌。现在，该公司正在推行一项增长战略，将赌注押在女性和农村消费者身上。【原文：For years, the world's biggest condom maker Reckitt Benckiser designed products and marketing to lure Indian men to its Durex brand. Now, it is pushing a growth strategy by betting on women and rural consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/durex-makes-india-condom-push-women-rural-consumers-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VFVDZ5GOMBPXLDDSH4GGMMUSSA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 05:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默多克接班人之争将在内华达州法庭上演]]></title><description><![CDATA[一场关于鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）媒体帝国控制权的闭门法庭争夺战将于 9 月 16 日开庭，这场争夺战可能决定福克斯新闻和《华尔街日报》的未来。【原文：A closed-door court battle over control of Rupert Murdoch’s media empire begins Sept. 16, and could determine the future of Fox News and the Wall Street Journal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/murdoch-succession-battle-play-out-nevada-courtroom-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23ZKX4MKTZNEDJGM77HAQESC7Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 05:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：欧洲央行迫在眉睫，科技股引发反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDADEBO7MNJMBKP3NEXJNR3ICQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台新提高对新光的收购要约，这可能是台湾最大的金融交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾金融企业集团台新表示，将把收购同业新光的报价提高 25%，达到约 2224 亿新台币（70 亿美元），这将是台湾金融服务业有史以来最大的一笔并购交易。【原文：Taiwan financial conglomerate Taishin said it would raise its offer for peer Shin Kong by 25% to about T$222.4 billion ($7 billion), in a deal that would be Taiwan's biggest-ever financial services industry merger.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/taishin-raises-offer-shin-kong-what-could-be-taiwans-biggest-financial-deal-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZYNYTYGK5MZTFK2LP25RMD5PQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:23:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，美国假日销售将以 2018 年以来最慢的速度增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[德勤（Deloitte）周四的数据显示，由于持续的通货膨胀和储蓄枯竭使购物者在这个重要的购物期变得更加节俭，美国假日销售额预计将以六年来最慢的速度增长。【原文：U.S. holiday sales are expected to grow at their slowest pace in six years, data from Deloitte showed on Thursday as persistent inflation and dried up savings turn shoppers more frugal for the all-important shopping period.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-holiday-sales-grow-slowest-pace-since-2018-report-says-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PR6BK5ZZVI6BBDD6MN2XOQKEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人口普查显示，去年美国家庭租金负担不变，但因种族而异]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国人口普查局（Census Bureau）周四表示，去年美国租房者和房主的住房成本中位数都有所上升，虽然租房者用于住房的收入比例总体上没有变化，但不同种族的家庭承受成本负担的程度也不尽相同。【原文：The median cost of housing for both U.S. renters and homeowners rose last year and while the share of income renters put toward housing was unchanged overall the degree to which households were cost-burdened varied by race, the Census Bureau said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-household-rent-burden-unchanged-last-year-varied-by-race-census-says-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FA4DUJGO2FNCVK2E2ELARPY3BE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Couche-Tard 考虑提高对 Seven & i 的收购价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[彭博新闻社周四援引熟悉 Couche-Tard 内部谈判的未具名消息人士的话报道称，加拿大 Alimentation Couche-Tard 公司正在讨论将收购日本 Seven &amp; i Holdings 公司的出价提高多少。【原文：Canada's Alimentation Couche-Tard is discussing how much it could raise the offer price to buy Japan's Seven &amp; i Holdings , Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing unnamed sources familiar with Couche-Tard's internal talks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/couche-tard-considers-raising-offer-price-seven-i-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WC3536O6XJJIXBZWMMUVI5GM7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市受华尔街科技股提振上涨，美元受日元影响扩大涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周四反弹，追随华尔街科技股的涨势，而美元则在美国核心通胀率意外小幅上扬并使美联储下周大幅降息的希望破灭后保持涨势。【原文：Asian shares bounced on Thursday, tracking a tech-driven rally on Wall Street, while the dollar held onto gains after U.S. core inflation surprised slightly on the upside and dashed hopes of a large rate cut by the Federal Reserve next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4IWAJZ6BZROSXJXOUI5NE7PYXU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:08:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在费城 Roundup 案的审判中，陪审团裁定拜耳旗下的孟山都公司胜诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜耳旗下的孟山都公司周三表示，费城法院陪审团在 Young Roundup 产品责任审判中作出了有利于他们的判决。【原文：Bayer's Monsanto unit said on Wednesday that a Philadelphia Court jury reached a verdict in the Young Roundup product liability trial in their favor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/jury-rules-favor-bayers-monsanto-philadelphia-trial-over-roundup-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ZMW74Z4GNL6LLBS4LPZRXHECY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行鹰派决策者呼吁将利率至少上调至 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[鹰派决策者田村直树（Naoki Tamura）周四表示，日本央行必须在明年年底前将利率上调至至少1%，这坚定了该行坚持稳步收紧货币政策的决心。【原文：The Bank of Japan must raise interest rates to at least 1% by late next year, hawkish policymaker Naoki Tamura said on Thursday, reinforcing the bank's resolve to persist with steady monetary tightening.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bojs-tamura-calls-raising-rates-least-1-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2OHOXDWAVJIMLISTAFXGS7INXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:38:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经销商表示担忧后，Stellantis 为自己辩护]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车制造商 Stellantis 周三告诉其美国经销商，8 月份的销量比 7 月份增长了 21%，经销商库存连续两个月减少了约 10%。【原文：Automaker Stellantis told its U.S. dealers on Wednesday that its August sales were up 21% from July, and its dealer inventory was reduced for two consecutive months by approximately 10%.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-defends-itself-after-us-dealers-flag-concerns-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6IPFEPKDZMUVDZAWUWMYENKZM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚九大娱乐公司首席执行官迈克-斯尼斯比下台]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚广播公司 Nine Entertainment 周四表示，首席执行官迈克-斯尼斯比（Mike Sneesby）将于 9 月 30 日卸任，首席财务与战略官马特-斯坦顿（Matt Stanton）将临时接任。【原文：Australian broadcaster Nine Entertainment said on Thursday Chief Executive Officer Mike Sneesby would step down with effect from Sept. 30 and that chief finance and strategy officer Matt Stanton would take over on an interim basis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/australias-nine-entertainment-ceo-mike-sneesby-step-down-2024-09-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W66LKZ7LMFOGXKXZREHDD2V26A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>