<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:05:23 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普任命卢特尼克领导美国贸易和关税事务后，他与中国的关系引来抨击]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，共和党当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）任命投资银行家霍华德-卢特尼克（Howard Lutnick）领导那些已成为中美贸易战矛头所指的机构。【原文：Investment banker Howard Lutnick's exposure to China came into sharp relief on Wednesday, after Republican President-elect Donald Trump tapped him to lead the agencies that have become the tip of the spear in the U.S.-China trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/lutnicks-china-ties-draw-fire-after-trump-taps-him-lead-us-trade-tariffs-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V27YQ7SK2FOSNHN4E4HF5UPOHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部称谷歌必须剥离 Chrome 浏览器以结束搜索垄断]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官周三称，Alphabet 旗下的谷歌必须剥离其 Chrome 浏览器，并且在五年内不得重新进入浏览器市场，这是为结束谷歌搜索垄断而向法官提出的要求清单的一部分。【原文：Alphabet's Google must divest its Chrome browser and should not be allowed to re-enter the browser market for five years as part of a list of requests made to a judge to end Google's search monopoly, U.S. prosecutors argued on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-must-divest-chrome-end-search-monopoly-doj-says-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRVBZ4T25RIFPJYIDM47WFSUBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克的 Neuralink 公司获加拿大批准进行脑芯片试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的神经链接公司（Neuralink）周三表示，它已获准在加拿大开展首次临床试验，该设备旨在让瘫痪者只需通过思考就能使用数字设备。【原文：Elon Musk's Neuralink said on Wednesday it has received approval to launch its first clinical trial in Canada for a device designed to give paralysed individuals the ability to use digital devices simply by thinking.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/science/elon-musks-neuralink-receives-canadian-approval-brain-chip-trial-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B5WLIHBNZ5KTDCPJV6ICC4WQHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达的预测打压风险偏好，亚洲股市有所回落]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲股市周四下跌，此前人工智能宠儿英伟达（Nvidia）的收入预期令人失望，美元走强，比特币因预期美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）提出的政策而创下历史新高。【原文：Asian equities fell on Thursday after AI darling Nvidia disappointed investors with a subdued revenue forecast, while the dollar firmed and bitcoin hit a record high in anticipation of U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's proposed policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXEXC7PNZ5PMLCARFE62PVWAI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币首次突破 95,000 美元，因对特朗普加密货币计划持乐观态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，比特币向100,000美元迈进的步伐进一步加快，投资者押注美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对加密货币采取更友好的监管方式将为这一资产类别带来繁荣时代。【原文：Bitcoin's march toward $100,000 made further ground on Thursday as investors bet a friendlier U.S. regulatory approach to cryptocurrencies under President-elect Donald Trump will unleash a boom era for the asset class.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-breaks-95000-first-time-optimism-over-trump-crypto-plans-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FXZCMSBBFPK5GJ7XELESBV6BY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田研发负责人表示，本田希望利用固态电池将电动汽车的行驶里程增加一倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[本田汽车研究部门负责人周三表示，本田汽车的目标是到2020年代末，当电动汽车开始采用全固态电池（一种正在开发的新型动力源）时，将电动汽车的行驶里程增加一倍。【原文：Honda Motor aims to double the driving range of its electric cars by the late 2020s when they start to adopt all-solid-state batteries, a new type of power source under development, the head of its research unit said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-hopes-double-ev-driving-range-with-solid-state-batteries-rd-chief-says-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GMLBLFICBVPWPMXGBOG35UJY24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:45:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团的亿万富翁高塔姆-阿达尼在美国被控行贿；债券交易被撤销]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度企业集团的亿万富翁、世界最富有的人之一因涉嫌参与数十亿美元的贿赂和欺诈计划而在纽约被起诉。【原文：The billionaire chair of the Indian conglomerate and one of the world's richest people has been indicted in New York over his role in an alleged multibillion-dollar bribery and fraud scheme.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/indias-adani-green-energy-withdraws-planned-dollar-bond-sale-sources-say-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3CRSFNRV5JYXDXBQMIS2QX6NM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称 Kioxia 市值将达 50 亿美元，日本芯片制造商将获上市批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士称，根据首次公开募股的指示性价格，贝恩支持的 Kioxia 市值将达到约 7,500 亿日元（约合 48.4 亿美元），该芯片制造商将于周五获得东京交易所的上市批准。【原文：Bain-backed Kioxia will have a market value of about 750 billion yen ($4.84 billion) based on the indicative price for its initial public offering, with the chipmaker to receive listing approval from the Tokyo bourse on Friday, two sources said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/kioxia-market-value-set-5-bln-japan-chipmaker-receive-listing-approval-sources-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUK4NBBCLZLMTBP46MKPWLRWB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达的供应障碍损害了交付，但掩盖了蓬勃的需求]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）周三的营收预测令华尔街失望，引发了人工智能热潮是否正在减退的疑问。但根据英伟达高管、分析师和投资者的说法，答案是肯定的。【原文：Nvidia's revenue forecast on Wednesday disappointed Wall Street, raising questions over whether the artificial intelligence boom is waning. But the answer, according to Nvidia executives, analysts and investors, is a resounding no.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/nvidias-supply-snags-hurting-deliveries-mask-booming-demand-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XLSXPBTFQNMDJHU2DO5PFKU4IM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 02:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[地缘政治紧张局势引发供应担忧，油价坚挺]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于俄罗斯和乌克兰之间的战争持续不断，地缘政治紧张局势升级引发了对供应的担忧，周四油价走高。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday due to supply concerns triggered by escalating geopolitical tensions amid the ongoing war between Russia and Ukraine.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-firm-geopolitical-tensions-raise-supply-concerns-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQSU3B5J7FJWLKERT4OQGOXVAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿达尼美元债券在美国贿赂指控后暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿达尼公司的美元债券价格周四在亚洲早盘交易中大幅下跌，此前这家印度企业集团的亿万富翁董事长因涉嫌贿赂和欺诈在纽约被起诉。【原文：Dollar bond prices for Adani companies fell sharply in early Asia trade on Thursday after the Indian conglomerate's billionaire chairman was indicted in New York over allegations of bribery and fraud.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/adani-dollar-bonds-tumble-after-us-bribery-charges-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6BKE7Q2NQBIBZEILISCC7IO2ZI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场关注特朗普政策和美联储前景，美元走强]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元周四大体坚挺，因为交易员们在等待美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普提出的政策更加明朗化，并试图对美联储不太激进的降息前景进行猜测。【原文：The U.S. dollar stood broadly firm on Thursday as traders awaited more clarity on U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's proposed policies and sought to second-guess the prospects of less aggressive interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-pulls-ahead-markets-focus-trump-policies-fed-outlook-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VWV7DKFZHBLPPKSQBEPZG52YWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:27:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[现代汽车在快速增长的市场推出大型电动 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[现代汽车周三发布了其首款三排电动 SUV，进军大型家用车市场，全球汽车制造商都希望该市场有朝一日能成为利润增长点。【原文：Hyundai Motor unveiled its first three-row electric SUV on Wednesday, pushing into a market for big family cars that global automakers hope will one day be a profit powerhouse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hyundai-unveils-big-electric-suv-fast-growing-market-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HXVLABZYKVMXNFVEYBEBWHR7UM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:07:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[罗森沃塞尔将于 1 月 20 日卸任美国联邦通信委员会主席一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦通信委员会主席杰西卡-罗森沃塞尔（Jessica Rosenworcel）周三表示，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）就任总统后，她将于 1 月 20 日从监管美国电信公司的机构卸任。【原文：Federal Communications Commission Chair Jessica Rosenworcel said on Wednesday she will step down from the agency that oversees U.S. telecommunications companies on Jan. 20 when Donald Trump assumes the presidency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rosenworcel-step-down-us-federal-communications-commission-chair-jan-20-2024-11-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MWXZ3K4375L7ZIR3OFM23OAVVU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[网络安全需求稳定，Palo Alto 营收和利润均超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks 公司周三公布的第一季度营收和利润超出华尔街预期，原因是在数字威胁增加的情况下，该公司网络安全服务的支出保持健康。【原文：Palo Alto Networks beat Wall Street expectations for first-quarter revenue and profit on Wednesday, owing to healthy spending for its cybersecurity services amid a rise in digital threats.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/palo-alto-tops-revenue-profit-estimates-steady-cybersecurity-demand-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCEOVJGZDFLOHGTGVBE3NLXGRA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 23:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[火鸡成本降低，今年美国感恩节大餐将更便宜]]></title><description><![CDATA[通胀疲软的消费者今年应该会发现，经典感恩节大餐的费用会从他们的薪水中减少，这主要是因为美国人减少了购买感恩节大餐的主菜--火鸡。【原文：Inflation-weary consumers should see the cost of their classic Thanksgiving dinner gobble less of their paychecks this year, largely because Americans are buying less of the meal's centerpiece dish, turkey.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/lower-turkey-costs-set-table-cheaper-us-thanksgiving-feast-this-year-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ASAJTAYZBVLIZONPB5R6H6RX4E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 22:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国锌业收购战考验首尔应对 "韩国折扣 "的决心]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国锌业公司（Korea Zinc）的收购战给首尔增添了压力，迫使其通过立法改革，以确保在一个股票市场由家族企业主导的国家，为所有投资者提供更好的保护。【原文：A takeover battle over Korea Zinc is adding pressure on Seoul to pass legislative reforms to ensure better protections for all investors in a country with a stock market dominated by family-run conglomerates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/korea-zinc-takeover-battle-tests-seouls-resolve-tackling-korea-discount-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P4OSMNCQ7NLA5DLUALBQAL4KHA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 22:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[波音公司向密苏里州近 700 名员工发出裁员通知]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周三公布的一份联邦政府要求的文件，波音公司向密苏里州的 692 名工人发出了裁员通知，这是这家负债累累的美国飞机制造商计划裁员 1.7 万人（占其全球员工总数的 10%）的一部分。【原文：Boeing issued lay off notices to 692 workers in Missouri, home to the company's Defense, Space &amp; Security division, according to a federally-required filing posted on Wednesday, as part of the debt-heavy U.S. planemaker's plan to cut 17,000 jobs, or 10% of its global workforce.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-gives-lay-off-notices-nearly-700-missouri-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZVURWRM4JLSFDG6QPUXMLCST4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 22:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 对影响美国数千人的网络中断进行修复]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit 周三表示，它已经推出了一个软件漏洞的修复程序，该软件漏洞导致美国数万人无法访问该社交媒体平台。【原文：Reddit said on Wednesday it has rolled out a fix for a software bug that prevented tens of thousands of people from accessing the social media platform in the U.S.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reddit-deploys-fix-outage-affecting-thousands-us-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QFUAMDWJNJLTPFYXUJG442WQIM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:59:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价英伟达业绩超预期，但未能带来火花]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7XT3HBZMSVMYXAFBFZO5ECJQOI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:48:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能芯片领军企业英伟达预测第四季度营收高于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周三，英伟达（Nvidia）预测第四季度营收略高于预期，押注于其梦寐以求的人工智能芯片的强劲销售，但仍未能达到投资者的高预期，而投资者已将英伟达打造成全球最有价值的公司。【原文：Nvidia forecast fourth-quarter revenue slightly above estimates on Wednesday, betting on robust sales of its coveted AI chips, but still failed to meet lofty expectations of investors who have made it the world's most valuable firm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/ai-chip-leader-nvidia-forecasts-fourth-quarter-revenue-above-estimates-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A5OD3QWPGRPVRNKELFQN7VB2XY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雪花公司上调年度产品收入预期，宣布与 Anthropic 达成人工智能协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[雪花公司（Snowflake）周三上调了年度产品收入预期，押注于数据云和分析平台的强劲需求，并宣布与人工智能公司 Anthropic 建立合作伙伴关系。【原文：Snowflake on Wednesday raised its annual product revenue forecast, betting on robust demand for its data cloud and analytics platform, and announced a partnership with artificial intelligence firm Anthropic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/snowflake-raises-annual-product-revenue-forecast-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZHFT6BZABLXRPNFYMTURI26XE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席柯林斯认为美国央行未来将有更多降息举措]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿联邦储备银行行长苏珊-柯林斯（Susan Collins）周三重申，她认为美国央行未来还会有更多的降息举措，因为美国央行正努力使货币政策正常化，同时缓解通胀压力。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Boston President Susan Collins reiterated on Wednesday she believes the U.S. central bank has more interest rate cuts ahead as it seeks to normalize monetary policy while inflation pressures ease.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-collins-sees-more-rate-cuts-ahead-us-central-bank-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FJBZY4WGTBIFDJIQLNJKDECGEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度阿达尼集团主席在美国被起诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官周三表示，印度企业集团阿达尼集团（Adani Group）主席高塔姆-阿达尼（Gautam Adani）因涉嫌行贿数亿美元并向美国投资者隐瞒这一计划而在美国被起诉。【原文：The chair of Indian conglomerate Adani Group, Gautam Adani, has been indicted in the U.S. over an alleged scheme to pay hundreds of millions of dollars in bribes and conceal the scheme from American investors, prosecutors said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/chair-indias-adani-group-indicted-united-states-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BKFFW5UH3RIEXPZPLE2IP76PRY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 20:54:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国指控五人参与 "分散蜘蛛 "黑客计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国检察官周三公布了对 Scattered Spider 五名涉嫌成员的刑事指控，该网络犯罪团伙涉嫌入侵数十家美国公司，窃取机密信息和加密货币。【原文：U.S. prosecutors unveiled criminal charges on Wednesday against five alleged members of Scattered Spider, a cybercrime group suspected of hacking into dozens of U.S. companies to steal confidential information and cryptocurrency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/us-charges-five-scattered-spider-hacking-scheme-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C35WCFRTFBK2HABCLFYU3GBQVQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 20:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pinebridge 称，非衰退性降息周期应支持信贷业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[资产管理公司 PineBridge Investments 在一份报告中称，它看到了一个罕见的非衰退性降息周期的开始，这将支持杠杆融资等固定收益资产的表现。【原文：Asset manager PineBridge Investments said in a report that it is seeing the start of a rare non-recessionary interest rate-cutting cycle that should support performance of fixed income assets like leveraged finance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/non-recessionary-rate-cutting-cycle-should-support-credit-pinebridge-says-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGM7XDCFVZP4XLP6VXNAHGIBCM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[浑水公司称做空 Elf Beauty 股票后股价下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金首席执行官卡森-布洛克（Carson Block）周三在伦敦举行的 Sohn 会议上表示，浑水公司（Muddy Waters）持有化妆品公司精灵美妆（Elf Beauty）的空头头寸。【原文：Muddy Waters has taken a short position in cosmetics company Elf Beauty , the hedge fund's chief executive Carson Block said at the Sohn conference in London on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/elf-beauty-stock-slides-after-muddy-waters-says-it-has-shorted-its-shares-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G46PFCQSYVNURGVGL4FD3Q4ALM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:36:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼表示降息令人担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）周三对美国央行在通胀率持续高于美联储2%的目标时降息表示不满，这为她呼吁对进一步降息采取谨慎态度增添了几分色彩。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman on Wednesday expressed discomfort with the U.S. central bank cutting interest rates while inflation continues to run above the Fed's 2% goal, adding a bit more color to her call for a cautious approach to further rate reductions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bowman-says-rate-cuts-are-concerning-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZI4TBQ76KFNZDNVPRH3XKN2NSY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷 YPF 公司将于 2025 年第二季度为石油管道寻求 20 亿美元融资]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷国营石油公司 YPF 的一位消息人士周三称，该公司将在 2025 年第二季度寻求 20 亿美元的融资，以完成其 Vaca Muerta Sur 项目。【原文：Argentina's state-run oil company YPF will seek $2 billion in financing in the second quarter of 2025 to complete its Vaca Muerta Sur project, a company source said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/argentinas-ypf-seek-2-billion-financing-oil-pipeline-q2-2025-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REYJU2QIKBJ6FGTKWVEX3DWGGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:05:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新闻集团称投资者拒绝终止双重类别投票结构的提议]]></title><description><![CDATA[新闻集团（News Corp）周三表示，投资者拒绝了激进投资者 Starboard Value 提出的终止双重类别投票结构、打破默多克家族对出版商控制的建议。【原文：News Corp said on Wednesday that investors rejected a proposal by activist investor Starboard Value to break the Murdoch family's grip on the publisher by ending a dual class voting structure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-says-investors-reject-proposal-end-dual-class-voting-structure-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TOJZ46CT4ZPN5LJO6WQVZLH6MQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 18:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>