<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:09:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:09:35 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税分裂日本公司，丰田下调预期，索尼、本田上调预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的关税政策正在对日本公司造成巨大冲击，丰田汽车（Toyota Motor）等一些大型出口商下调了利润预期，而索尼（Sony）和本田（Honda）等公司则表示，关税影响将比他们担心的要小。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs are cleaving Japan Inc, as some big exporters like Toyota Motor slash their profit forecasts while Sony and Honda are among those saying the impact will be less than they had feared.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trump-tariffs-split-japan-inc-toyota-cuts-forecast-while-sony-honda-raise-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYNR2NQD7RPT5LI6JLOADWOKUI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚对特朗普威胁将美国药品关税提高至 250% 感到担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚卫生部长周四表示，澳大利亚非常关注美国总统唐纳德-特朗普最近威胁要在较长时期内将药品进口关税提高高达250%。【原文：Australia is very concerned about U.S. President Donald Trump's latest threat to raise tariffs on pharmaceutical imports by up to 250% over the longer term, its health minister said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australia-worried-by-trump-threat-raise-us-pharma-tariffs-250-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXJ2BX6W7ZJTLJU3UI3ZS4MWHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国关税拖累，消费疲软，日本下调经济增长预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本政府周四下调了本财年的经济增长预期，原因是美国关税导致资本支出放缓，持续的通胀拖累了私人消费，威胁到脆弱的经济复苏。【原文：Japan's government cut its growth forecast for this fiscal year on Thursday as U.S. tariffs slow capital expenditure and persistent inflation weighs on private consumption, threatening a fragile economic recovery.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-cuts-growth-forecast-us-tariffs-drag-weaker-consumption-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5YUCY3SWVJRNPIRCBJRD4LWCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印美关税僵局：新德里有哪些选择和风险？]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度很可能成为受美国总统唐纳德-特朗普贸易攻势打击最严重的国家之一，如果三周内不能达成协议，印度进口商品的关税将激增至 50%。【原文：India is likely to be among the countries worst hit by U.S. President Donald Trump's trade offensive, with tariffs on Indian imports set to surge to 50% if a deal is not struck in three weeks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-us-tariff-standoff-what-are-new-delhis-options-risks-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MONBF5KKY5IS3AZJ2IJ6VKHATI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港稳定币法案的客户身份规定引发业界关注]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内人士表示，香港新的稳定币法律规定了严格的客户身份识别规则，这可能会阻碍数字货币的应用，并影响香港在全球数字金融市场的竞争力。【原文：The strict customer identification rules mandated in Hong Kong’s new stablecoin law could hinder adoption of the digital currency and the city's competitiveness in global digital finance markets, sources from the industry said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hong-kong-stablecoin-bills-client-identity-rules-spark-industry-concern-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4QL5MEN57VKTNL5KD33MFVXHRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国企业在 2025 年上半年售出创纪录数量的货币期权]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年上半年，中国企业卖出的货币期权数量创下历史新高，因为国内企业，尤其是出口商，押注人民币汇率稳定，并利用衍生品赚取额外利润。【原文：Chinese companies sold a record amount of currency options in the first half of this year as domestic businesses, particularly exporters, bet on a steady yuan and used derivatives to make some extra money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-firms-sell-record-amount-currency-options-first-half-2025-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMFR47XRBZMYNE7F327O74X6QA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:32:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[矿业巨头压缩红利，着眼于为增长提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[到目前为止，由于矿产价格下滑，大型矿商需要为其大规模开发项目保留现金，同时努力控制成本，因此在本财报季中，大型矿商支付的股息是多年来最低的。【原文：So far this earnings season, large miners are paying out their lowest dividends in years, as mineral prices slip and they need to retain cash for their massive development projects, while trying to keep a lid on costs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/mining-giants-squeeze-dividends-with-an-eye-toward-funding-growth-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77LIJML5JVMZBNCJ2K74Y7M4ZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[软银集团第一季度净利润 28.7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本科技投资商软银集团（SoftBank Group）4-6 月份实现净利润 4218 亿日元（约合 28.7 亿美元）。【原文：Japanese technology investor SoftBank Group logged a net profit of 421.8 billion yen ($2.87 billion) over the April-June quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/softbank-group-posts-287-billion-net-profit-q1-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUT2KLB3OJK5BE2AWLCQVBLLEE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[持怀疑态度的投资者叫停中国的反价格战反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国政府打击价格战和工业生产过剩的运动刺激下，中国钢铁和水泥股在 7 月份大涨，基金经理杨廷武迅速收获了收益。【原文：Fund manager Yang Tingwu was quick to harvest his gains after a furious July rally in Chinese steel and cement stocks, spurred by Beijing's campaign against price wars and excess industrial production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/sceptical-investors-call-time-chinas-anti-price-war-rally-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HLBP2ROZARIFJEW3MIMDIVZJLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:41:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投资承诺缓解关税担忧，苹果股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司承诺在美国追加 1,000 亿美元投资，缓解了市场对华盛顿对半导体进口征收关税影响的担忧，此后苹果公司股价在法兰克福早盘交易中上涨 1.6%。【原文：Iphone maker Apple shares rose 1.6% in early Frankfurt trade after the company committed an additional $100 billion in U.S. investments, easing concerns over the impact of Washington's tariffs on semiconductor imports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/apple-shares-rise-us-investment-pledge-eases-tariff-concerns-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJPLIJWNRVOWDPY35HEY6GZAQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[假日酒店业主洲际酒店集团第二季度美国客房收入下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[假日酒店业主洲际酒店集团（InterContinental Hotels Group）周四报告称，由于经济不确定性影响了其最大市场的消费者支出，第二季度美国每间可用客房收入（RevPAR）出现下降。【原文：Holiday Inn owner InterContinental Hotels Group reported a fall in U.S. revenue per available room (RevPAR) in the second quarter on Thursday, as economic uncertainties dent consumer spending in its largest market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/holiday-inn-owner-ihgs-us-room-revenue-falls-second-quarter-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3RVY3RGU5JNH3GHDMZZWJJEXXY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[集装箱需求抵御贸易担忧，马士基上调利润展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运集团 A.P. 穆勒-马士基（A.P. Moller-Maersk）周四上调了全年利润展望，原因是尽管贸易战令人担忧，但全球海运集装箱货运需求仍表现出韧性。【原文：Shipping group A.P. Moller-Maersk on Thursday raised its full-year profit outlook as global demand for ocean container freight showed resilience despite concerns of trade wars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/maersk-boosts-profit-outlook-container-demand-defies-trade-fears-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOEMOESBIJN63P7E3VR6EJ4PSM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:13:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管欧佩克+大幅增产，为何石油市场依然紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+"产油国利用夏季的高需求启动了三年来的首次增产，但事实证明，这些目标难以实现，导致市场出人意料地紧张。【原文：OPEC+ oil producers have used high summer demand to launch their first output increases in three years, but those targets have proved difficult to hit, leaving the market surprisingly tight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/why-oil-market-is-tight-despite-big-opec-output-hikes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BZXYWIWSCVJYJHF3WZR5ZOTVOM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田表示将在日本新建汽车工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司（Toyota Motor）周四表示，将在日本中部以其名字命名的城市建造一座新的汽车工厂，并于 2030 年代初投入运营。【原文：Toyota Motor said on Thursday it would build a new vehicle factory in its namesake city in central Japan to start operations in the early 2030s.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-says-it-will-build-new-car-factory-japan-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NT2ATCFWWZNSVCQM66Z3BQF5SI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱茵金属第二季度销售额略低于预期，但确认了目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）周四公布的第二季度销售额略低于预期，部分原因是德国国防合同迟迟未能签订，但该公司确认了全年业绩预期。【原文：Rheinmetall on Thursday posted slightly worse-than-expected second-quarter sales due in part to a delay in German defence contracts being awarded but confirmed its full-year forecast.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/rheinmetall-slightly-misses-q2-sales-expectations-confirms-target-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7WYBFLO3YNKRFIVP4NS5HWUYAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田将全年营业利润预期下调 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车公司周四将全年营业利润预期下调了 16%，原因是日元升值和美国提高进口关税对其财务业绩造成了影响。【原文：Toyota Motor cut its full-year operating profit forecast by 16% on Thursday as an appreciating yen and higher U.S. import tariffs weighed on its financial results.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-cuts-full-year-operating-profit-estimate-by-16-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMY3BVF7WVKSJBUMMUUQ3AUOGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安联第二季度利润好于预期并确认目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国安联集团（Allianz）周四公布第二季度净利润增长 13%，好于预期，并确认了全年目标。【原文：Germany's Allianz on Thursday posted a better-than-expected 13% rise in second-quarter net profit and confirmed its target for the full year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/allianz-posts-better-than-expected-q2-profit-confirms-target-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RAYR374WLRPKZNM3T473KBJNNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:17:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国电信第二季度利润达到预期，并上调了指导目标]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国电信公司周四公布的第二季度核心利润符合分析师预期，称德国和美国的业绩持续增长，并上调了全年利润指导。【原文：Deutsche Telekom reported second quarter core profit in line with analyst expectations on Thursday, citing continued growth in both Germany and the U.S., and edged up its full-year profit guidance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/deutsche-telekom-meets-q2-profit-expectations-lifts-guidance-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LPNALWXUA5KADMC7D7BDZKTCR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元疲软拖累西门子第三季度业绩符合预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[西门子周四公布的最新季度工业利润符合预期，尽管美元走软对这家德国工程集团的业绩造成了影响。【原文：Siemens reported industrial profit in line with forecasts for its latest quarter on Thursday, although the weakening dollar weighed on the German engineering group's figures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/siemens-reports-q3-results-line-with-forecasts-weak-dollar-weighs-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">REJO3FCDQVKUHLUSXCLWZPACXQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道卢比奥命令美国外交官针对欧洲科技法开展游说活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社看到的一份内部外交电报显示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的政府已指示美国驻欧洲外交官开展游说活动，以反对欧盟的《数字服务法案》（Digital Services Act）。【原文：President Donald Trump's administration has instructed U.S. diplomats in Europe to launch a lobbying campaign to build an opposition to the European Union's Digital Services Act, which Washington says stifles free speech and imposes costs on U.S. tech companies, an internal diplomatic cable seen by Reuters showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/rubio-orders-us-diplomats-launch-lobbying-blitz-against-europes-tech-law-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SMSAKEULZKOVI5YHKIDNRURKU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价英国央行将降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[凯文-巴克兰对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Kevin Buckland】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DEOUMMEM2JL5DKURJMEBOY2TOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在澳大利亚的住房争夺战中，政治转变选择了新手而非新移民]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚的经济适用房计划已在悉尼富人区莫斯曼（Mosman）展开，新的规划法对该地区长期以来的发展阻力提出了挑战。【原文：Australia's affordable housing push has arrived in the wealthy Sydney suburb of Mosman, where new planning laws now challenge longstanding resistance to development in the leafy area known for mansions and sweeping harbour views.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-housing-war-political-shift-picks-newbies-over-nimbys-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGKYKKE3WVJK3NERBMDYAZVSLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受美国经济担忧和关税紧张局势影响，日本投资者抛售外国股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 8 月 2 日的一周内，由于对美国经济前景和一系列新的贸易关税持谨慎态度，主要市场出现回落，日本投资者大幅抛售外国股票。【原文：Japanese investors significantly sold foreign stocks in the week to August 2 as major markets retreated on caution over U.S. economic outlook and a new set of trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/japanese-investors-ditch-foreign-stocks-us-economic-concerns-tariff-tensions-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSG62G53BVJP3EVNGWW6ZU4MYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普提高关税税率打击美国主要贸易伙伴的商品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周四开始对数十个贸易伙伴征收10%至50%的较高关税，这是对他在不大规模破坏全球供应链、不提高通胀率和不遭到贸易伙伴强烈报复的情况下缩小美国贸易赤字的战略的考验。【原文：President Donald Trump's higher tariff rates of 10% to 50% on dozens of trading partners kicked in on Thursday, testing his strategy for shrinking U.S. trade deficits without massive disruptions to global supply chains, higher inflation and stiff retaliation from trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/trumps-higher-tariff-rates-hit-goods-major-us-trading-partners-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JOXEMOCTFO6VODYKP5BNDBMWM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商担心 "贴纸冲击"，在涨价问题上与品牌商发生冲突]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税带来的成本上升和消费者勒紧裤腰带的双重压力下，大型零售商正与妮维雅制造商拜尔斯道夫和啤酒制造商喜力等消费品牌的生产商发生冲突，因为他们希望避免可能损害销售的价格冲击。【原文：Caught between rising costs from tariffs and belt-tightening consumers, big retailers are clashing with the producers of consumer brands such as Nivea-maker Beiersdorf and brewer Heineken , as they look to avoid sticker shock that could hurt sales.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wary-sticker-shock-retailers-clash-with-brands-price-hikes-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E4MOW46G7NJ4FIAQKCNH2ZJJPI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国稀土出口在上月达到峰值后于 7 月下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的海关数据显示，中国的稀土出口在一个月前创下纪录后，7月份下滑了23%，尽管初步数据还不完整，无法就中国政府加快发货的承诺得出肯定的结论。【原文：Rare earth exports from China slumped 23% in July after hitting a record a month earlier, customs data showed on Thursday, although the preliminary data is too incomplete to draw firm conclusions about Beijing's commitment to speed up shipments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-rare-earth-exports-slid-july-after-hitting-peak-prior-month-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPMVVJNI7NNC3EWMGEUWVCJEBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国7月出口高于预期，急于在特朗普关税最后期限前完成任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 7 月份的出口超过了预期，因为制造商充分利用了北京和华盛顿之间脆弱的关税休战协议，在本月晚些时候迫在眉睫的最后期限到来之前发货。【原文：China's exports beat forecasts in July, as manufacturers made the most of a fragile tariff truce between Beijing and Washington to ship goods ahead of a looming deadline later this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-july-exports-top-forecasts-amid-rush-meet-trump-tariff-deadline-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UWW5P6WWAZLCZJAL7HDLXAJ474</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:33:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼将年度利润预期上调 4%，理由是贸易战影响较小]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼公司周四将全年营业利润预期上调 4%，至 1.33 万亿日元（约合 90.1 亿美元），理由是美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的贸易战影响减弱。【原文：Sony raised its full-year operating profit forecast on Thursday by 4% to 1.33 trillion yen ($9.01 billion), citing a diminished impact from U.S. President Donald Trump's trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sony-hikes-annual-profit-forecast-by-4-citing-smaller-trade-war-impact-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YBK5Q3ZO7RMJ5FSGBGDUPL4PUA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市攀升，美元受美联储宽松政策押注影响下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市上涨，日本股市创下历史新高，原因是华尔街科技股领涨、盈利向好以及对美国降息的预期不断增强，这些因素提振了市场情绪。【原文：Asian equities rose on Thursday, with Japanese shares hitting a record high, as tech-led gains on Wall Street, upbeat earnings and growing expectations for U.S. rate cuts boosted sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDCCOJVWHZMY3AVGPVML6U23MQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 AMP 半年盈利改善，但股价受利润下滑拖累]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚货币基金管理公司 AMP 公布了较高的半年收益，理由是其财富平台的净现金流强劲以及银行部门的利润率有所改善，但低于市场预期，导致其股价下跌。【原文：Australian money manager AMP posted higher half-year earnings, citing strong net cashflows in its wealth platform and margin improvement in its banking unit, but fell short of market expectations, which sent its shares lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/australias-amp-half-year-earnings-improve-shares-drag-profit-miss-2025-08-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5ZUWY6EOJPZDHDGBDPFNCTSGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>