<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:12:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:12:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[Roblox预测年度预订量将强劲增长，游戏平台势头持续增强；股价大幅上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[Roblox周四公布的2026财年预订额超出华尔街预期，预示着玩家消费和参与度将迎来又一轮强劲增长。这家电子游戏平台正积极寻求占据全球游戏市场10%的份额。【原文：Roblox forecast fiscal 2026 bookings above Wall Street expectations on Thursday, signaling another year of strong growth in player spending and engagement as the videogame platform aggressively looks to capture 10% of the global gaming market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/roblox-forecasts-strong-annual-bookings-gaming-platform-momentum-grows-shares-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DJJY3R77BBN5FMHZ32VLIC4AHE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:11:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit营收超预期，人工智能推动广告销售增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reddit周四公布的季度营收超出华尔街预期，其广告平台通过人工智能技术实现的升级功能，助力这家社交媒体平台吸引更多营销商，推动其股价在盘后交易中上涨10%。【原文：Reddit forecast first-quarter revenue above Wall Street estimates on Thursday, as artificial intelligence-powered enhancements to its ad platform help the social media platform draw more marketers, sending its shares up 10% in extended trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/reddit-forecasts-revenue-above-estimates-ai-fuels-ad-sales-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I34VRY5A7BO6XIFOB64NGCDIEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gen Digital上调年度营收预期，因安全软件需求强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[杀毒软件供应商Gen Digital周四连续第三个季度上调年度营收预期，表明其数字安全服务需求强劲。【原文：Antivirus software provider Gen Digital raised its annual revenue forecast for a third consecutive quarter on Thursday, signaling strong demand for its digital security services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/gen-digital-raises-annual-revenue-forecast-strong-security-software-demand-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YSGN7VSQ5RIFHG5WZ64TOG7LB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊预计今年资本支出将达2000亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊周四与其他科技巨头一道，预测2026年将进行大规模资本支出，这是迄今为止最新迹象，表明科技公司短期内不会放缓其巨额人工智能投资步伐。【原文：Amazon.com on Thursday joined its Big Tech peers in projecting massive capital expenditures in 2026, the freshest sign yet that tech companies will not be hitting the brakes on their hefty AI investments anytime soon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-projects-200-billion-capital-spending-this-year-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYXFPUXIYBMBTEFXH2IPGSIJIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 21:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国检察官表示，检察官办公室不会起诉在刑事调查中配合调查的企业。]]></title><description><![CDATA[曼哈顿联邦检察官周四表示，联邦检察官计划加大对在刑事调查中配合调查的企业激励力度，包括承诺不予起诉。【原文：Federal prosecutors plan to increase incentives for companies that cooperate during criminal investigations, including promises not to prosecute them, the U.S. Attorney in Manhattan said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-attorney-says-it-will-not-prosecute-companies-that-cooperate-criminal-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6L5RTXU36FLMJJ3TLVZF7R2H7A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:49:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管政府补贴大幅增加，美国农场收入仍将在2026年出现下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农业部周四预测，尽管政府补贴接近历史最高水平，预计将占生产者利润总额的近29%，但今年美国农场净收入仍将下降0.7%，这表明美国农民面临的压力日益加剧。【原文：In a sign of growing stress for U.S. farmers, the Agriculture Department forecast on Thursday that U.S. net farm income would fall 0.7% this year, despite near-record government payments that are expected to account for nearly 29% of producers’ bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-farm-income-set-fall-2026-despite-surge-government-payments-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HHUFQ47ADJLNHPDSZZYSK63D7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:38:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[可口可乐将在美国和加拿大停产冷冻产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[可口可乐公司周四宣布，将停止在美国和加拿大市场销售冷冻产品，包括美汁源冷冻系列，以迎合不断变化的消费者口味。【原文：Coca-Cola said on Thursday it is discontinuing its frozen products, including its Minute Maid frozen line, in the U.S. and Canada markets as it tries to appease shifting consumer taste.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/coca-cola-discontinue-frozen-products-us-canada-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J4EWW7CMZJM7HEVDMNW2ODB6CA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构将审查联邦航空管理局空中交通管制培训的高失败率]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国交通部监察长办公室周四表示，将针对空中交通管制学员的高淘汰率展开调查。当前美国长期面临管制员短缺问题，导致空中交通管理压力持续增大。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department Office of Inspector General said on Thursday it will open a probe into high failure rates among air traffic control trainees amid a long-standing shortage of controllers to manage U.S. air traffic.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-watchdog-review-high-failure-rate-faa-air-traffic-control-training-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TRJAV7FHXFJ4LD7Y6U5XDXPZFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:47:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福杰特能源在纽交所上市首日市值逼近80亿美元，人工智能基础设施需求持续增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[福杰特能源周四在纽约证券交易所上市首日市值逼近80亿美元，尽管市场存在局部过热担忧，但投资者对服务于人工智能热潮的企业仍保持着强劲需求。【原文：Forgent Power was valued at nearly $8 billion in its New York Stock Exchange debut on Thursday, as investor appetite for companies catering to the AI boom remains healthy despite pockets of worries the market may have overheated.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/forgent-power-valued-nearly-8-billion-muted-nyse-debut-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35E7M6ZP6FOENNMXVIG3HQXLVQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美中两国选择不签署关于人工智能在军事领域使用的联合声明]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，参加军事人工智能峰会的约三分之一国家就如何规范该技术在战争中的部署达成宣言，但军事强国中美选择缺席。【原文：Around a third of countries attending a military AI summit agreed on Thursday to a a declaration on how to govern deployment of the technology in warfare, but military heavyweights China and the U.S. opted out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-china-opt-out-joint-declaration-ai-use-military-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6AKFXL6YIFM55IWY62SRYDXRYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[零售商加倍投入广告支出，通过提价摆脱关税阴霾]]></title><description><![CDATA[从增加广告支出、与温网合作到提价，雅诗兰黛和拉夫劳伦等美国零售商正竭尽全力抢占市场份额。随着市场日益呈现收入分化趋势，这些企业正试图摆脱关税压力。【原文：From increased ad spend, Wimbledon tie-ups to price hikes, U.S. retailers like Estee Lauder and Ralph Lauren are pulling out all stops to corner a slice of a market increasingly split along income lines as they try to shake off tariff pressure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/retailers-double-down-ad-spend-price-hikes-shake-off-tariff-blues-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BE6CZ4EYOBLLJKIKWHR33IMBDI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币暴跌冲击投机性囤币企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[加密货币市场的动荡正拖累那些在资产负债表上持有比特币及其他数字资产的企业股价，引发了业界对该领域可能面临更广泛压力的担忧。【原文：Turbulence in the cryptocurrency market is dragging down shares of companies that hold bitcoin and other digital assets on their balance sheets, sparking concerns over potential broader strains in the sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/bitcoin-slump-shakes-companies-that-jumped-crypto-hoarding-bandwagon-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MXR5VDSVD5LKPEPOPMWYZK6WJ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，沙特航空正与波音和空客就其迄今为止最大规模的喷气式飞机订单进行谈判。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周四报道，知情人士透露，沙特阿拉伯旗舰航空公司沙特航空正与波音和空客进行初步谈判，拟采购至少150架窄体和宽体客机。【原文：Saudi Arabia's flagship carrier Saudia is in early talks with Boeing and Airbus to buy at least 150 narrowbody and widebody jets, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/saudia-talks-with-boeing-airbus-its-largest-jet-order-date-bloomberg-news-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63RYPV3CNFOB5LTEADTJ3LCUFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克资深人士珀尔穆特领导的Eikon Therapeutics在纳斯达克上市首日估值达8.6亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[由默克公司资深人士罗杰·珀尔穆特领导的药物开发商艾康治疗公司，其股票周四在纳斯达克首次公开发行时开盘价较发行价下跌5.3%，公司估值约为8.603亿美元。【原文：Drug developer Eikon Therapeutics , headed by Merck veteran Roger Perlmutter, was valued at about $860.3 million after its shares opened 5.3% below their offer price in their Nasdaq debut on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/eikon-therapeutics-valued-860-million-nasdaq-debut-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIXL3K44INKQDHKMLWJ5FQMCUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anthropic发布AI升级版，市场重挫软件股]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能初创公司Anthropic周四推出其宣称的改进版人工智能模型，此前数日该公司产品取得的进展曾引发传统软件股抛售潮。【原文：Technology startup Anthropic on Thursday launched what it called an improved artificial intelligence model, days after its product advances helped kick-start a selloff of traditional software stocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/anthropic-releases-ai-upgrade-market-punishes-software-stocks-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CIRNWTWGA5KGLLREHNVCIC2ITA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鲍勃折扣家具公司估值达22亿美元，纽约证券交易所首日上市股价持平]]></title><description><![CDATA[由私募股权公司贝恩资本支持的鲍勃折扣家具公司，在周四首次公开募股首日开盘持平后，最终获得22.2亿美元估值。本周新股发行密集，投资者对新股保持审慎态度。【原文：Bob's Discount Furniture , backed by private equity firm Bain Capital, secured a valuation of $2.22 billion, after its shares opened flat in their debut on Thursday, as investors stayed selective about new offerings in a packed week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bobs-discount-furniture-valued-222-billion-shares-open-flat-nyse-debut-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVLHWXM45RPU7JM5HDFRPTAJMI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国军用船厂亨廷顿英格尔斯预计本季度将出现负自由现金流]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国军用船厂亨廷顿英格尔斯周四表示，尽管季度利润超出预期，但仍预计本季度自由现金流将为负值，导致其股价午盘下跌11%。【原文：U.S. military shipbuilder Huntington Ingalls said on Thursday that it had expected free cash flow for the current quarter to be negative, despite beating quarterly profit estimates, sending its shares down 11% at midday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-military-shipbuilder-huntington-ingalls-expects-negative-free-cash-flow-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OG2XE6LOQ5MUVF6QD6OBM4PBSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金抢进波动剧烈的1月市场以获取回报]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金1月份录得正回报，这得益于美国在委内瑞拉采取军事行动引发的市场波动、围绕美联储独立性的质疑，以及寒流导致天然气期货价格飙升所造成的连锁反应。【原文：Hedge funds posted positive returns in January thanks to ripples of market volatility stemming from U.S. military action in Venezuela, questions around the independence of the Federal Reserve and a cold snap that sent natural gas futures flying.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/hedge-funds-jump-into-volatile-january-reap-returns-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CZHWT3ZRVZPC3NRBOKHS3M7GO4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国众议院委员会向Coupang发出传票，作为歧视调查的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[众议院司法委员会周四向韩国电商巨头Coupang发出传票，作为其针对该公司涉嫌歧视美国企业调查的一部分，要求其提交与韩国政府之间的通信记录。【原文：The House Judiciary Committee on Thursday issued a subpoena to Coupang as part of its ongoing probe into alleged discrimination against U.S. companies, seeking communications between the e-commerce firm and the South Korean government.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-house-panel-issue-subpoena-coupang-part-discrimination-probe-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCHXES7DABP47JEBCAIAKI7RGM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[嘉能可与力拓核心资产对比分析]]></title><description><![CDATA[力拓周四第三次放弃了与竞争对手嘉能可达成一项大型采矿交易的计划。【原文：Rio Tinto walked away from a mega-mining deal with rival Glencore for the third time on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/how-glencore-rio-tintos-core-assets-stack-up-2026-01-09/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3OUFVH6AWFJLTBXF76FMNR5NNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大央行表示经济重组将耗时数年]]></title><description><![CDATA[作者：大卫·伦格伦【原文：By David Ljunggren】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/bank-canada-says-restructuring-economy-will-take-years-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPNKTB2Y4RLZNJYIC2ZC5MO7B4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[古巴将实施配给计划，美国正采取行动阻断燃料供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[古巴总统米格尔·迪亚斯-卡内尔周四表示，随着美国采取行动阻止向这个加勒比岛国供应石油，古巴政府将在下周推出一项应对燃油短缺的计划。【原文：Cuban President Miguel Diaz-Canel said on Thursday his government would roll out a plan in the next week to deal with fuel shortages as the U.S. moves to block the supply of oil to the Caribbean island nation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/cuba-roll-out-rationing-plan-us-moves-block-fuel-supply-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GJRELES635K4FFDJY63LWTFW5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:20:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利普斯66公司将裁员277人，洛杉矶炼油厂逐步停产]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯66公司计划裁员277人，因其位于洛杉矶地区、日处理量13.9万桶的炼油厂在关闭前逐步停产。加州就业监管机构的文件显示了这一情况。【原文：Phillips 66 is set to lay off 277 employees as operations at the 139,000-barrel-per-day Los Angeles-area refinery wind down ahead of closure, filings to California's employment regulator show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/phillips-66-cut-jobs-los-angeles-refinery-shuts-bloomberg-news-reports-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FD4SXR7H4BOGLHESLED22N42TU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴拿马总统表示港口合同不会授予单一运营商]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马总统何塞·劳尔·穆利诺周四表示，将不再向单一企业授予运营权，此前香港和记黄埔有限公司运营的两座港口已由其持有并运营近三十年。【原文：Panamanian President Jose Raul Mulino said on Thursday that the concession of contracts to operate two ports held and operated for nearly three decades by Hong Kong's CK Hutchison Holdings will "never again" be issued to a single company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/panamas-president-says-port-contracts-will-not-be-issued-single-operator-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUYPEMNPVZJVZD5QQBXP2SXGOA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[威瑞森消费者业务部门负责人离职，公司正全力推进转型计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国无线运营商威瑞森公司消费者业务部门负责人索米亚纳拉扬·桑帕斯即将离职，该公司正在新任首席执行官丹·舒尔曼的领导下实施转型计划。【原文：Verizon consumer division chief Sowmyanarayan Sampath is stepping down as the U.S. wireless carrier mounts a turnaround effort under its new CEO Dan Schulman.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/verizon-consumer-division-head-departing-company-mounts-turnaround-effort-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6CX5E5ZPR5PFFLXHAOE2XDVVGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国12月职位空缺降至逾五年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月职位空缺降至逾五年最低水平，此前因2025年末劳动力市场状况趋缓，上月数据亦被下调。【原文：U.S. job openings dropped to the lowest level in more than five years in December and data for the prior month was revised lower amid a softening in labor market conditions at the end of 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-job-openings-drop-more-than-five-year-low-december-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KW2ANSKW6NORDEEG7TYKL6WORY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺和诺德将就Wegovy配制问题对Hims & Hers采取法律行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[诺和诺德周四表示，将对Hims & Hers公司采取法律行动。此前这家在线远程医疗公司宣布，将开始提供该丹麦集团Wegovy药片的复方仿制药，每月售价49美元。【原文：Novo Nordisk said on Thursday it would take legal action against Hims & Hers after the online telehealth company said it will begin offering compounded copies of the Danish group's Wegovy pill at an introductory price of $49 per month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/novo-nordisk-take-legal-action-against-hims-hers-wegovy-compounding-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A4FK3HJVLVMKNO45WJF2VISAII</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peloton因需求疲软第三季度营收表现疲软，股价暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[Peloton Interactive周四预测第三季度营收低于华尔街预期，指出其健身设备需求疲软，股价应声暴跌约25%，跌至近一年半以来的最低点。【原文：Peloton Interactive forecast third-quarter revenue below Wall Street estimates on Thursday, pointing to weak demand for its fitness equipment, with shares plunging about 25% to their lowest level in about a year and a half.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/peloton-flags-soft-third-quarter-revenue-subdued-demand-shares-slump-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WMYM6RH47RKLJHSKIYSFVXN53Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员要求美国政府披露联邦航空管理局局长是否出售了其持有的航空公司股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[三名美国民主党参议员周四向交通部询问，联邦航空管理局局长是否已出售其持有的共和航空股份，以及他是否将因未在规定的剥离期限前出售股份而被迫放弃相关收益。【原文：Three Democratic U.S. senators on Thursday asked the Transportation Department if the head of the Federal Aviation Administration has sold his shares in Republic Airways and whether he will be forced to give up any gains for not selling the stake before a required divestment date.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/senators-ask-us-disclose-if-faa-administrator-sold-stake-airline-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YMHNSJVXXZIDVB26RAHQGDXSBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特表示，是否因货币政策选择起诉沃什取决于特朗普]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特周四拒绝承诺，若特朗普政府提名的美联储主席人选凯文·沃什推行与总统立场相左的货币政策，政府将不会起诉他。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent declined on Thursday to commit the Trump administration to not suing Kevin Warsh, its nominee to be Federal Reserve Chair, if he follows a monetary path opposed by the president.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/bessent-says-up-trump-whether-warsh-might-be-sued-monetary-policy-choices-2026-02-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KOAKAYAL6NLOFJDNKYOWOCKEIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>