<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:39:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:39:02 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟高级官员表示，欧盟成员国将于4月9日就针对美国关税的反制措施进行表决]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位欧盟高级官员周四表示，欧盟成员国将于4月9日（周三）就美国征收钢铝关税的反制措施进行投票。【原文：European Union member states are set to vote on Wednesday April 9 on countermeasures to the United States' steel and aluminum tariffs, a senior EU official, said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-members-vote-april-9-countermeasures-us-tariffs-says-senior-eu-official-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYPK3GHDEVOTLLMDGB4SEXJSDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙 Acerinox 公司称关税原则上是积极的，但要警惕过剩产品涌入欧盟]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙钢铁制造商 Acerinox 周四表示，美国的关税 "原则上 "会对该公司产生积极影响，因为西班牙是其主要市场，也是其主要钢厂所在地。【原文：Spanish steel maker Acerinox said on Thursday that the U.S. tariffs would have "in principle" positive effects on the company as the country is its main market and where its main steel mills are located.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/spains-acerinox-says-tariffs-positive-principle-wary-surplus-flooding-eu-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U5G2QT6BDNMFLICV6QU7QFZB5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:28:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊机器人出租车部门更新软件后，NHTSA 终止了对 258 辆 Zoox 汽车的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周四表示，在亚马逊自动驾驶汽车部门召回 258 辆 Zoox 汽车并更新其软件后，该局已结束对这些汽车制动问题的调查。【原文：The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Thursday it has closed its probe into 258 Zoox vehicles over a braking issue, after the Amazon self-driving car unit recalled them and updated their software.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nhtsa-closes-probe-into-258-zoox-vehicles-after-amazons-robotaxi-unit-updates-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWVDUJTWNFO3FNDQHCF3RCX6YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:21:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙将推出安全网保护企业和消费者免受美国关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙经济部长卡洛斯-奎尔波（Carlos Cuerpo）表示，西班牙首相佩德罗-桑切斯将于周四晚些时候宣布一揽子措施，以减轻美国新关税对企业和消费者的影响。【原文：Spanish Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez is due to announce a package of measures later on Thursday to cushion the impact of new U.S. tariffs on companies and consumers, Economy Minister Carlos Cuerpo said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/spain-roll-out-safety-net-protect-companies-consumers-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NZ72BECNJKQ5E637YIJPMCS7U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:16:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱尔兰称，报复美国数字服务并非欧盟立场]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易部长西蒙-哈里斯（Simon Harris）周四表示，在潜在的互惠贸易措施中将美国的数字服务作为目标并非欧盟的立场，这将对爱尔兰造成极大的损害，并敦促双方进行谈判。【原文：Targeting U.S. digital services in potential reciprocal trade measures is not the European Union's position and would be very damaging for Ireland, trade minister Simon Harris said on Thursday, urging negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/retaliating-against-us-digital-services-not-eu-position-ireland-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBZEWX224BO4DJ2VRTZ4RGSN2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德意志银行称存在美元信任危机风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[德意志银行（Deutsche Bank）周四就美元信心危机的风险发出警告，称资本流动配置的重大变化可能会取代货币基本面，货币走势也会变得无序。【原文：Deutsche Bank warned on Thursday of the risk of a crisis of confidence in the U.S. dollar, saying major shifts in capital flow allocations could take over from currency fundamentals and currency moves become disorderly.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/deutsche-bank-says-risk-dollar-confidence-crisis-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYBEIT6PYJM3TDJGSNBX2AVBQ4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:07:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新贸易现实来袭，投资者寻求不受关税影响的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[在关税到来之际，投资者正在寻找抵御经济阵痛的方法，寻找能够抵御经济衰退和通胀上升的资产，或者寻找对国际贸易依赖程度较低的公司。【原文：Investors are looking at ways to ward off economic pain now tariffs are here, seeking assets that can ride out a recession and higher inflation or companies that rely less on international trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/wealth/global-markets-tariffs-investors-analysis-pix-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTENXPANJRPPPLZ5TBUXTO4J6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芬兰称全欧洲应就关税问题与美国接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[芬兰总统亚历山大-斯图布（Alexander Stubb）周四表示，整个欧洲都应就贸易关税问题与美国进行接触。【原文：Finland's President Alexander Stubb said on Thursday that all of Europe should engage with the United States on the issue of trade tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/finland-says-all-europe-should-engage-with-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISJV6AN655M65CUUEMG4GPZKAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，"欧佩克+"成员国部长将按计划进一步提高石油产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧佩克+组织的两位消息人士周四称，欧佩克+组织的八位最高级别部长会议可能会维持要求从四月份起逐步增加石油产量的石油产出政策不变。【原文：A meeting of eight top ministers of OPEC+ will likely keep oil output policy that calls for gradual oil output hikes from April unchanged, two OPEC+ sources said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-ministers-seen-sticking-further-oil-output-hikes-planned-sources-say-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFEKHETACFMIXEY2DVTVJBTUUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国关税也将适用于几个月前订购的法拉利汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[这家意大利豪华汽车制造商的发言人周四表示，唐纳德-特朗普总统的新关税也将适用于几个月前订购但仍未运抵美国的法拉利汽车。【原文：President Donald Trump's new tariffs will also apply to Ferrari cars ordered months ago but still not delivered to the United States, a spokesperson for the Italian luxury automaker said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-tariffs-also-apply-ferrari-cars-ordered-months-ago-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QNCZIGNNNRK67LC2LAW37LFSV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[财政部长：泰国经济增长将受美国关税影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰国财政部长周四表示，由于美国征收关税，泰国的经济增长可能会减少一个百分点。
财政部长披差-春哈瓦吉拉（Pichai Chunhavajira）告诉记者，为了努力维持出口，政府将进口更多的美国商品，取消部分美国产品的关税，并解决美国商品的非关税壁垒和税收问题。【原文：Thailand's economic growth could be reduced by 1 percentage point due to the imposition of U.S. tariffs, the finance minister said on Thursday.
To try to maintain exports, the government will import more U.S. goods, remove tariffs on some U.S. products as well as address non-tariff barriers and taxes on U.S. goods, Finance Minister Pichai Chunhavajira told reporters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/thailand-growth-be-hit-us-tariffs-finance-minister-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFOWHHMNARJOFJEU37WK2JCSVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税引发利润预警潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去几个月里，美国企业对关税问题议论纷纷，但很少有企业在盈利展望中考虑到关税问题。随着美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的多线贸易战全面展开，投资者和分析师预计，未来几周将有大量企业发布盈利预警，这可能会对股市造成冲击。【原文：U.S. businesses have talked a lot about tariffs in the past few months, but very few modeled for them in their earnings outlooks. With President Donald Trump's multi-front trade war now in full effect, investors and analysts expect a barrage of corporate profit warnings in the coming weeks that could jolt the stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-set-stage-wave-profit-warnings-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JOQ5BJNHTVIRPG42QVT7KSONGI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:54:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊告诉欧盟法院法国图书快递费是保护主义行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊批评法国两年前征收的图书快递费，周四告诉欧洲最高法院，这项措施具有歧视性、保护主义性质，违反了欧盟法律。【原文：Amazon criticised a book delivery fee imposed by France two years ago, telling Europe's top court on Thursday the measure was discriminatory, protectionist and a breach of European Union law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-tells-eu-court-french-book-delivery-fee-is-protectionist-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MCZ5SFUNZRORRMJHTZ2DGNBZ3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱银行认为今年美国经济衰退的风险 "很高]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）周四表示，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）全面征收新关税后，美国经济今年陷入衰退的 "风险很高"。【原文：There is a 'high risk' of the U.S. economy falling into a recession this year after President Donald Trump's sweeping new tariffs, Barclays said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/barclays-sees-high-risk-us-recession-this-year-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NUBMVHFKVJNAHI36CF5N45JECM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:45:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的全面关税令市场震荡，美国加密货币股市下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于全球贸易紧张局势加剧，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）最新一轮的全面关税打击了投资者的信心，引发了风险较高资产的抛售，美国加密货币股票在周四的盘前交易中下跌。【原文：U.S. crypto stocks declined in premarket trading on Thursday after President Donald Trump's latest round of sweeping tariffs rattled investor confidence due to rising global trade tensions, sparking a sell-off in riskier assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-crypto-stocks-slide-trumps-sweeping-tariffs-jolt-markets-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JPEHQ2FRNJIMLF7ISYKMGSKCXA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税超出预期，中国股市和人民币大跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对中国及其主要贸易伙伴征收一系列全面的互惠关税后，中国人民币跌至七周来的最低水平，股市暴跌。【原文：China's yuan dropped to its lowest level in seven weeks and stock markets slumped on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump unveiled a sweeping set of reciprocal tariffs that were particularly heavy on China and its main trading partners.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-stocks-yuan-tumble-after-bigger-than-expected-trump-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NVCBYGPVVVLIDHDK5W7KKTXHCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基称特朗普关税对全球经济和贸易不利]]></title><description><![CDATA[船运公司马士基周四表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普周三宣布的关税措施对全球经济和贸易稳定来说是个坏消息。【原文：Shipping company Maersk said on Thursday that the tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday amount to bad news for the global economy and trade stability.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-tariffs-bad-global-economy-trade-maersk-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NR5N7HBYRFORLLAXZW6TSSQ3EY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特因安全带问题召回超过 10.5 万辆 SUV]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，因安全带问题召回约 105,322 辆 SUV。【原文：The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday that it is recalling about 105,322 SUVs over concerns related to their seat belts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-recalls-over-105000-suvs-seat-belt-concern-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6X26J5TQNKCLAM67ZVWXQFYDE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:21:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国经济部长表示，特朗普将在欧洲压力下屈服]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国经济部长罗伯特-哈贝克（Robert Habeck）周四表示，在不断升级的贸易战中，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普将在德国和欧洲的压力下屈服。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump will buckle under pressure from Germany and Europe in an escalating trade war, German Economy Minister Robert Habeck said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-will-buckle-under-pressure-europe-says-german-economy-minister-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PTARWH54HNNE7BJVCT2Y4LMP6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普挑起贸易战，全球遭受关税冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周四对盟国和竞争对手全面征收美国进口关税的举动引发了报复威胁，加剧了全球贸易战，有可能刺激通胀并引发对经济衰退的担忧。【原文：President Donald Trump's move to impose sweeping tariffs on U.S. imports on allies and rivals alike sparked threats of retaliation on Thursday, intensifying a global trade war that threatens to stoke inflation and raising fears of recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/trump-stokes-trade-war-world-reels-tariff-shock-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UU6J63Q2L5LDRKPEZ3QO7C6QE4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:59:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚牛肉农场主称特朗普关税将推高美国汉堡包价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[在澳大利亚郁郁葱葱的南部高地的牛群拍卖会上，一位拍卖师站在龙门架上，在近 2000 头等待购买的奶牛的喧闹声中大声喊道。【原文：At a cattle auction in Australia's lush Southern Highlands, an auctioneer shouts from a gantry over the din of nearly 2,000 cows waiting to be bought.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/australian-beef-farmers-say-trump-tariffs-boost-price-us-hamburgers-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDX72SUC4ZJORNHX36XOMADNFI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:44:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税打压股市，投资者纷纷躲避]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）大幅征收贸易关税，引发了对全球经济衰退的普遍担忧，周四全球股市和油价暴跌，投资者纷纷转向相对安全的债券、黄金和日元。【原文：World stock markets and oil prices tumbled and investors dashed to the relative safety of bonds, gold and the yen on Thursday, as President Donald Trump’s drastic U.S. trade tariffs stirred widespread fears of a global recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-pix-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GSXVUUI4RLGLER7VB7C4D5OJU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关税加剧经济衰退担忧，华尔街期货一蹶不振]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）对其贸易伙伴全面征收关税，加剧了人们对全面贸易战可能将全球经济推入衰退的担忧，美国股指期货周四下挫。【原文：U.S. stock index futures sank on Thursday after President Donald Trump's sweeping tariffs against its trading partners heightened fears of an all-out trade war that could push the global economy into a recession.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-futures-tailspin-tariffs-fuel-recession-fears-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33GUIOJEPJNS7ERUBAGNFKNBY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税削弱了美元的避险光泽]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元是世界上动荡时期最安全的资金存放地之一，但随着关税的不确定性及其对美国经济增长影响的担忧加剧，美元目前已被投资者避而远之。【原文：The dollar, one of the world's safest places to park money in times of turmoil, has been shunned by investors as an option for now as uncertainty over tariffs and concern over their impact on U.S. growth intensify.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/trumps-tariffs-dull-dollars-safe-haven-sheen-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C43MSOYCBROTPIBE2LX574J6YQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国加征关税引发市场下跌，交易商寻求避险澳元主食消费品]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收对等关税引发全球市场动荡后，投资者转向更安全的投资，澳大利亚主要消费品公司股票周四在杂货商科尔斯（Coles）和伍尔沃斯（Woolworths）的推动下上涨。【原文：Shares of Australia's consumer staple companies rose on Thursday, driven by grocers Coles and Woolworths , as investors moved to safer bets after U.S. President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariffs sparked global market turmoil.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/traders-seek-refuge-aussie-consumer-staples-us-tariffs-spark-market-fall-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RZWKXH3AUVPQFNOB4CWXR5377M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球饮料制造商三得利总裁表示，为避免关税，其目标是在当地销售饮料]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本饮料制造商三得利公司新任总裁周四表示，该公司正在寻求改变其烈酒在全球的销售地点，以应对潜在的贸易战。【原文：Japanese drinks maker Suntory is looking to shift where it markets its spirits across the globe as it girds for a potential trade war, its new president said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/global-drinks-maker-suntory-aims-sell-local-avoid-tariffs-president-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NIQCCHHL6BMIJFJMNCA2H2V4RE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:57:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普的关税将推高酒吧账单并削减工作岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[行业机构周四表示，由于美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）征收对等关税，从尼格罗尼鸡尾酒到苏格兰威士忌，成本将上升，销售将下降，工作岗位将减少，饮料品牌将从美国酒吧菜单上消失。【原文：From Negroni cocktails to Scotch whisky, costs will rise, sales will fall, jobs will be cut, and drinks brands will disappear from U.S. bar menus as a result of President Donald Trump's reciprocal tariffs, industry bodies said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/trumps-tariffs-set-drive-up-bar-bills-cut-jobs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ULWCZVI5FIRFLQ76DW5HVYOMM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:54:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kering 收购意大利眼镜制造商 Visard 和 Mistral 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[古驰（Gucci）的所有者开云集团（Kering）周四表示，其高端眼镜部门已签署协议，收购意大利制造商Visard的全部股份和另一家意大利公司Mistral的少数股份。【原文：Gucci owner Kering said on Thursday its high-end eyewear division had signed an agreement to acquire the entire share capital of Italian manufacturer Visard and a minority stake in another Italian company Mistral.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/kering-buys-stakes-italian-eyewear-manufacturers-visard-mistral-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XIPV2MDRURIE3NC6Q3MGTZYIC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织称，瑞士科技面临特朗普关税的沉重打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士行业协会 Swissmem 周四表示，瑞士科技公司正面临美国对瑞士征收贸易关税带来的严重挫折。【原文：Swiss tech companies are facing a serious setback from trade tariffs imposed by the United States on Switzerland, industry association Swissmem said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/swiss-tech-faces-severe-blow-trump-tariffs-industry-group-says-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GXWAA7UFAJIY3HADYJFT4Z55TY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国征收新关税，奢侈品和瑞士制表商股价受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国总统唐纳德-特朗普宣布对包括来自欧盟和瑞士的商品在内的商品征收新关税后，周四欧洲奢侈品公司股价下跌。【原文：Shares in European luxury companies dropped on Thursday after U.S. President Donald Trump announced new tariffs, including on goods from the European Union and Switzerland.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/luxury-swiss-watchmaker-shares-take-hit-new-us-tariffs-2025-04-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHNTCIH4MRKUDDFEHKWAYRLA74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>