<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:15:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:15:16 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司以145亿美元收购Penumbra公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[波士顿科学公司周四宣布，将以约145亿美元的交易额收购Penumbra公司。【原文：Boston Scientific said on Thursday it will buy Penumbra in a deal valued at about $14.5 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/boston-scientific-buy-penumbra-deal-valued-145-billion-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNO3C4ND5BPN7FSBOSK623FL2A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:07:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能视频初创公司Higgsfield最新融资后估值达13亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能视频生成初创公司Higgsfield向路透社透露，已完成8000万美元新一轮融资，公司估值突破13亿美元。随着市场对这项新技术的需求激增，投资者正争相布局该领域。【原文：AI video generation startup Higgsfield raised $80 million in new funding, valuing the company at over $1.3 billion, it told Reuters, as investors rush to develop the sector amid booming demand for the new technology.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ai-video-startup-higgsfield-hits-13-billion-valuation-with-latest-funding-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NANMPGVN2FIQDMRVXZQQCQLTNU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国议员提出法案，拟建立价值25亿美元的关键矿产储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国两党议员周四提出一项法案，计划建立价值25亿美元的关键矿产储备，此举旨在稳定市场价格并鼓励国内采矿和精炼业发展。【原文：A bipartisan group of U.S. lawmakers on Thursday introduced a bill to create a $2.5 billion stockpile of critical minerals, a move aimed at stabilizing market prices and encouraging domestic mining and refining.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-lawmakers-introduce-bill-create-25-billion-critical-minerals-stockpile-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KO3JBJ5JNRN7BKXW7BQSOKPR2Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西央行因"严重违规"清算REAG]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西央行周四下令清算经纪公司REAG（现称CBSF），该决定载于行长加布里埃尔·加利波利签署的文件中。此举是中型银行Banco Master倒闭引发的最新连锁反应。【原文：Brazil's central bank ordered on Thursday the liquidation of brokerage REAG, currently known as CBSF, according to a document signed by Governor Gabriel Galipolo, in the latest fallout from the collapse of mid-sized lender Banco Master.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/brazil-central-bank-liquidates-reag-serious-rule-violations-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64DLB4E3J5IHRDLKGOUN3IZTG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度警告苹果公司，在该公司拖延时间后，将推进反垄断诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度已向苹果公司发出最终警告，称将对这家美国科技巨头启动反垄断调查。一份机密文件显示，苹果公司拖延回应调查官员长达一年多，并阻碍了调查进程。【原文：India has issued a final warning to Apple that it will proceed in an antitrust case against the U.S. tech giant as the company has delayed responses to officials for over a year and undermined the investigation, a confidential order shows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/india-warns-apple-it-will-proceed-with-antitrust-case-after-company-plays-time-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T53P5A7ERNIJTBH6CGJXC6IHTA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[令人眼花缭乱的旋转]]></title><description><![CDATA[当今美国及全球市场中真正重要的因素【原文：What matters in U.S. and global markets today】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-view-usa-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OLG7UD7S4FNODDB6AKF6B6SWKY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚社交媒体禁令首月封禁470万青少年账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚互联网监管机构表示，在该国全球首创的16岁以下用户禁令生效仅一个月后，社交媒体公司已集体注销了近500万个澳大利亚青少年账户，这表明该措施产生了迅速而广泛的影响。【原文：Social media companies have collectively deactivated nearly five million accounts belonging to Australian teenagers just a month after a world-first ban on under‑16s took effect, the country's internet regulator said, a sign the measure has had a swift and sweeping impact.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-social-media-ban-hits-47-million-teen-accounts-first-month-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNCOGKV64FO5RDCBTFAY44CJYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotify将在部分市场将月度订阅价格上调至12.99美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify周四宣布，将把美国、爱沙尼亚和拉脱维亚市场的现有用户每月高级订阅服务价格上调1美元，至12.99美元。【原文：Spotify said ‌on Thursday it would raise the price of its ‌monthly premium subscription service ​by $1 to $12.99 for existing subscribers in ‍the United States, Estonia and Latvia markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spotify-raise-premium-subscription-price-1299-month-select-markets-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BSNMK2NX4BPRLBSZZFT2KLFFX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:13:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席调查引发美国债券投资者关注收益率上升，威胁住房可负担性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国债券投资者正为长期收益率上升做好准备，因针对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔的刑事调查加剧了通胀上升预期，此举可能最终加剧民众对购房负担能力的担忧。【原文：U.S. bond investors are bracing for higher long-term yields as a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has fueled expectations of elevated inflation, a move that could end up amplifying affordability concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-bond-investors-eye-higher-yields-fed-chair-probe-threatening-affordability-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIIGCVKCTNJE7DIR4FQGUHSI4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德资产规模在第四季度市场反弹中创下14万亿美元纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[贝莱德周四公布的第四季度利润超出华尔街预期，市场反弹推动其手续费收入增长，管理资产规模攀升至创纪录的14.04万亿美元。【原文：BlackRock beat Wall Street estimates for fourth-quarter profit on Thursday as a rally in markets lifted fee income and pushed its assets under management to a record $14.04 trillion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/blackrock-fourth-quarter-profit-rises-etf-inflows-index-fund-demand-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A2W757AFIBMZ7NBQWURCQ27ZTQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:06:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国农业经济出现扩大裂痕，成本上升，就业岗位消失]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国农业带，如今的时局令人沮丧。农民们正面临又一个价格低迷、成本高昂的季节，他们不得不艰难抉择——究竟该如何经营，甚至是否该继续经营下去。就在种植户们急需资金周转之际，银行却切断了部分人的贷款渠道。随着肉类加工厂关闭和农机制造商缩减规模，成千上万的工人正面临失业。【原文：Across the U.S. farm belt, these have become depressing times. Farmers are facing another season of low prices, high costs and difficult decisions about how — or whether — to keep operating. Banks are cutting off some growers just as they urgently need cash. Thousands of workers are losing jobs as meatpacking plants close and farm ​equipment makers scale back.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-farm-economy-shows-widening-cracks-costs-rise-jobs-vanish-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5JZC5PAOLFIZRIGY5HRSD2S7MU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道：美国FDA因安全性和有效性问题，在新推出的优惠券计划中推迟两项药物审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局已推迟对两款药物的审查，这两款药物原被选入特朗普政府的新快速审批计划。路透社获得的内部文件显示，该机构科学家对这两款药物的安全性和有效性提出质疑，其中包括一名患者在服用其中一种药物期间死亡的情况。【原文：The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has delayed reviews of two drugs chosen for the Trump administration's new fast-track program after agency scientists flagged safety and efficacy concerns, including the death of a patient while taking one of the medicines, internal documents seen by Reuters show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/us-fda-delays-two-drug-reviews-new-voucher-program-after-safety-efficacy-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4EPIXLPM25LJFJ5DYVNO6CHGHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股市领涨板块呈现扩大迹象，科技股之外领域开始发力]]></title><description><![CDATA[在多年见证科技股引领美国牛市之后，投资者正押注此轮涨势将扩展至工业、医疗保健及小盘股领域，这些板块有望迎头赶上并确立市场主导地位。【原文：After years of watching technology stocks drive the U.S. bull market, investors are betting the rally will broaden to industrial, healthcare and small-cap companies, with a chance they can catch up and assert market leadership.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stocks-leadership-showing-signs-broadening-beyond-tech-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NRYB7FDZMFPXLBRXGFPMATHW3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台积电带动半导体板块反弹，华尔街期货走高；金融企业财报即将发布]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四美国股指期货上涨，台积电亮眼财报推动半导体股走高，金融巨头财报发布前市场情绪升温。【原文：U.S. stock index futures rose on Thursday after TSMC's blowout quarterly results fueled a rally in semiconductor shares ahead of earnings from financial heavyweights.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wall-st-futures-rise-tsmc-sparks-semiconductor-rally-financial-earnings-deck-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYNZ3XTXIJJVXMDLDCL7OHR5S4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国媒体监管机构称Snapchat加强了非法内容风险检查]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国通信管理局（Ofcom）周四表示，社交媒体平台Snapchat在去年该媒体监管机构提出担忧后，已显著改善其非法内容风险评估机制。【原文：Britain's Ofcom said on Thursday social media platform Snapchat has significantly improved its illegal content risk assessment following concerns raised by the media regulator last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/uk-media-regulator-says-snapchat-improves-illegal-content-risk-checks-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOJEX4LLVVLG5DGYJYSMZYAZTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官埃莫蒂强调希望由内部人士接任]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂希望继任者能从银行内部选拔，他在周四发表于瑞士《每日导报》的专访中如是表示。【原文：UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti hopes his successor will be a candidate from within the bank, he told Swiss newspaper Tages-Anzeiger in an interview published on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-ceo-ermotti-underlines-his-desire-internal-successor-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EYYAR2UCFJOBBPYCDIDFR5YCLE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:24:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基将恢复苏伊士运河航线以服务MECL航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦航运巨头马士基周四宣布，其连接中东、印度与美国东海岸的MECL航线将恢复经红海和苏伊士运河的航行。【原文：Shipping group Maersk will resume sailings via the Red Sea and the Suez Canal for its MECL service, connecting the Middle East and India with the U.S. east coast, the Danish company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/maersk-resume-suez-canal-sailings-mecl-service-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BUNG454L4FI5FMSE3RYVXM3ZEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲律宾因儿童安全问题寻求封禁Grok应用]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲律宾信息通信技术部长周四表示，该国正着手阻止埃隆·马斯克的人工智能聊天机器人Grok进入市场，因其存在生成性化图像的风险，包括可能危及儿童安全的内容。【原文：The Philippines is moving to block Elon Musk's AI chatbot Grok amid concerns about its ability to generate sexualised images, including content that could pose child safety risks, the secretary of information and communications technology said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/philippines-seeks-block-access-grok-child-safety-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VEUQNXYV5VOAJCZ6RND67OIIMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[2025年加拿大房屋销售因关税冲击下滑1.9%]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大房地产协会周四公布的数据显示，去年加拿大房屋销售量出现年度下滑，12月销售量和房价均出现下跌。【原文：Canadian home sales posted an annual decline last year as sales and prices fell in December, ​data from the Canadian Real Estate Association showed on ‌Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadian-home-sales-fall-19-2025-tariff-shock-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76CRI4Q4Y5NVXJBBS4EHFOF62I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASML市值突破5000亿美元，台积电财报点燃半导体板块涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[ASML股价周四飙升至历史新高，推动其市值突破5000亿美元大关，巩固了其作为欧洲市值最高企业的领先地位。【原文：Shares in ASML surged to a new all-time high on Thursday, pushing its market capitalisation past the $500 billion milestone and cementing its lead as Europe’s most valuable company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/asml-tops-500-billion-market-cap-tsmc-results-ignite-semis-rally-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T4VOKN44MROBHECZ4PUAOAXIBA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国监管机构表示将继续调查X平台深度伪造内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国媒体监管机构通信管理局（Ofcom）周四表示，尽管欢迎该公司近期政策调整，但仍将继续对埃隆·马斯克旗下X平台的Grok人工智能聊天机器人涉及性亲密深度伪造图像一事展开正式调查。【原文：British media regulator Ofcom said on Thursday its formal investigation into Elon Musk's X over its Grok AI chatbot's sexually intimate deepfake images would continue, even as it welcomed the company's recent policy change.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/uk-regulator-says-its-x-deepfake-probe-will-continue-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUBEGNAEIFIABHKTRW7WIVPBHA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维基百科所有者与微软、Meta达成人工智能内容训练合作协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[维基百科周四宣布与微软、Meta和亚马逊等多家科技巨头建立合作伙伴关系，标志着这家非营利组织在将科技公司对内容的依赖转化为商业价值方面迈出了重要一步。【原文：Wikipedia on Thursday unveiled partnerships with several Big Tech companies including Microsoft , Meta and Amazon , marking a major step up in the non-profit's ability to monetize tech firms' reliance on its content.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/wikipedia-owner-signs-microsoft-meta-ai-content-training-deals-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCIESMMCZJPSLKZT4LYBBOR56U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:34:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据消息人士透露，和记黄埔寻求旗下零售业务以300亿美元估值进行第二季度首次公开募股。]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，香港跨国企业和记黄埔有限公司正寻求为旗下零售业务屈臣氏集团筹备香港及伦敦上市事宜，估值约300亿美元，最早可能于第二季度启动。【原文：Hong Kong conglomerate CK Hutchison Holdings Ltd is seeking a valuation of around $30 billion for retail unit A.S. Watson Group's listings in Hong Kong and London as soon as the second quarter, two people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ck-hutchison-seeks-30-billion-valuation-retail-units-q2-ipo-sources-say-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAY4UY4DFBNAHDEQWG3I6AFT3U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:16:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱立信将在瑞典裁员1600人]]></title><description><![CDATA[电信设备集团爱立信周四宣布，计划在瑞典裁员约1600人。【原文：Telecoms equipment group Ericsson plans to lay off some 1,600 employees in Sweden, the company said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/ericsson-shed-1600-jobs-sweden-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBOUSCZKONJDLKXEVDW4J7OPOE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国产业部长表示将持续关注美国芯片关税政策以最大限度降低影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国产业通商资源部部长金正宽周四表示，政府将持续关注美国对特定人工智能半导体芯片加征关税的进展，以最大限度减轻对本土产业的影响。该部声明称。【原文：South Korean Industry Minister Kim Jung-kwan said on Thursday that the government will keep monitoring developments on U.S. tariffs on certain AI semiconductor chips to minimise the impact on local industries, according to a ministry statement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/south-korea-keep-monitoring-us-chip-tariffs-minimise-impact-industry-minister-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AXZMML6JUBN7RPDH5YEOHMFQYI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[裕信银行否认有意收购蒙特帕斯基银行股份的传闻]]></title><description><![CDATA[裕信银行周四驳斥了有关其有意收购西恩纳蒙特帕斯基银行股权的传闻，称这些传闻"纯属猜测且毫无根据"。【原文：UniCredit on Thursday dismissed as "speculative in nature and unjustified" rumours of it being interested in buying a stake in Banca Monte dei Paschi di Siena .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-dismisses-rumours-about-mps-stake-says-it-studies-all-ma-options-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D62NFCYPDZMIVIBHEL6D7TVGCQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:36:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper将于第二季度初完成对JDE Peet's的收购]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keurig Dr Pepper与荷兰投资公司Kodiak BidCo于周四对咖啡茶饮集团JDE Peet's发起全现金收购要约，预计将于第二季度初完成交易。【原文：Keurig Dr Pepper and Dutch vehicle Kodiak BidCo launched on Thursday an all-cash takeover bid for coffee and tea group JDE Peet's , which they expect to complete early in the second quarter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/keurig-dr-pepper-launches-all-cash-takeover-bid-jde-peets-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UXIWK6C3NBPE3PKA47CHRCXZBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国称贝森特言论凸显外汇稳定对美韩合作的重要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国高级官员周四表示，美国财政部长斯科特·贝森特近期关于韩元汇率的言论，凸显了外汇稳定对首尔与华盛顿双边经济合作的重要性。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent's recent comments on the Korean won underscore the importance of foreign exchange stability for bilateral economic cooperation between Seoul and Washington, a senior South Korean official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bessents-comments-show-importance-fx-stability-us-south-korea-cooperation-seoul-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UEZVOKQWKVLOFL6GX4JBCV6RLI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:21:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊推出基于欧洲的新云服务以解决用户担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊旗下AWS云服务周四推出全新云服务，该服务完全部署于欧洲。此举旨在解决用户对主要美国供应商数据安全性的担忧，为欧洲大陆提供独立的替代方案。【原文：Amazon's AWS launched a new cloud service located entirely in Europe on Thursday, addressing user concerns about the data security delivered by mainly U.S.-based providers by offering the continent's own independent alternative.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-launches-new-europe-based-cloud-service-address-user-concerns-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N2CPM2AU7VM5DEVL6KFLYV7OQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士竞争监管机构对微软许可费展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士竞争委员会周四表示，已对微软在该国的许可费问题启动初步调查。【原文：Switzerland's competition commission said on Thursday it launched a preliminary investigation into Microsoft's licensing fees in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/swiss-competition-authority-opens-probe-into-microsoft-licensing-fees-2026-01-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YIBFWXCSIFMQZHZSQWQJBNLQUE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>