<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:46:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:46:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[捷蓝航空全年收入预期低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[捷蓝航空公司（JetBlue Airways）预计，由于美国大选在即，国内旅游需求放缓，2024 年的收入降幅将超过预期，导致其股价在周二收盘前下跌 4.5%。【原文：JetBlue Airways forecast a bigger-than-expected fall in 2024 revenue amid a moderation in domestic travel demand ahead of the upcoming U.S. elections, sending its shares down 4.5% before the bell on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/jetblues-full-year-revenue-forecast-misses-estimates-shares-fall-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CALPIIIQJROYXB4D2JZV5BEWAE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[康宁公司因光纤需求强劲而预测季度业绩乐观]]></title><description><![CDATA[大猩猩玻璃制造商康宁公司周二公布的第四季度利润预期超出预期，原因是网络数据消耗量（包括用于生成式人工智能模型训练的数据消耗量）不断增加，对其光纤产品的需求也持续增加。【原文：Gorilla Glass maker Corning fourth-quarter profit forecast beat estimates on Tuesday, as rising consumption of data over networks, including for generative AI model training, continues to increase demand for its optical fiber products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/corning-forecasts-upbeat-quarterly-results-robust-demand-optical-fiber-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KVR7GRUFI5MJJAZTY3QIED4A3A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:53:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[D.R. Horton 2025 年收入和房屋交付量低于预期，股价下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，D.R. Horton 预测 2025 年的收入和房屋交付量均低于预期，原因是抵押贷款利率的波动使一些购房者保持观望，而该建筑商保留了折扣以刺激需求。【原文：D.R. Horton forecast 2025 revenue and home deliveries below estimates on Thursday, as mortgage rate volatility kept some home buyers on the sidelines and the builder retained discounts to whip up demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/dr-horton-sees-2025-revenue-home-deliveries-below-estimates-shares-fall-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRBAKO3XA5I7JIPC6M2G3JTZJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿布扎比的 CYVN Holdings 就收购迈凯轮汽车业务达成非约束性协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[两家海湾公司周二表示，总部位于阿布扎比的投资公司 CYVN Holdings 已达成一项非约束性协议，将从巴林主权财富基金 Mumtalakat 手中收购汽车制造商迈凯轮汽车业务 100% 的股份。【原文：Abu Dhabi-based investment vehicle CYVN Holdings has entered a non-binding agreement to buy 100% of carmaker McLaren's automotive business from Mumtalakat, the sovereign wealth fund of Bahrain, the two Gulf firms said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/abu-dhabis-cyvn-holdings-enters-non-binding-deal-buy-mclarens-automotive-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RHXJP3QXHBMANJOFO76EIHMQRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[莱多斯公司因国防需求强劲而上调年度预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国防承包商莱多斯控股公司（Leidos Holdings）周二上调了年度利润和收入预期，认为在地缘政治局势日益紧张的情况下，全球武器需求将保持强劲。【原文：U.S. defense contractor Leidos Holdings raised its annual profit and revenue forecasts on Tuesday, banking on strong worldwide weapons demand amid growing geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/leidos-lifts-annual-forecasts-robust-defense-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UV4EOBSIINIYTOEVEEHZI4AAFY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融产品需求增加，MSCI 第三季度利润强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[指数提供商摩根斯坦利资本国际公司（MSCI）周二发布报告称，由于对其产品和服务的需求强劲，公司第三季度利润有所增长。【原文：Index provider MSCI on Tuesday reported a rise in its third-quarter profit helped by robust demand for its products and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/msci-reports-strong-q3-profit-amid-increased-demand-financial-products-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GSWK57BMORKRLCOX6FUDJTRGKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于燃料需求疲软，炼油商菲利普斯 66 公布第三季度利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 周二公布的季度利润下降，原因是燃料需求低迷导致利润率下滑。【原文：Phillips 66 posted a fall in quarterly profit on Tuesday, hurt by a slump in margins due to lackluster fuel demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/refiner-phillips-66-reports-lower-third-quarter-profit-weak-fuel-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NBVFIXPYTBJOPBEJ5V3PEMSUDQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[需求低迷，麦当劳全球销售额降幅超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[麦当劳周二公布的季度全球可比销售额降幅超过预期，主要市场的客流量疲软对其造成了影响，尽管麦当劳在数年涨价后加大了促销力度以吸引顾客。【原文：McDonald's on Tuesday posted a steeper-than-expected drop in quarterly global comparable sales, hurt by weaker traffic across its key markets even as it intensified promotions to woo back customers after several years of price hikes.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-global-sales-fall-more-than-expected-muted-demand-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DTVVJDGYOJJZ7JMIN5BCGV46EM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PayPal 预计第四季度营收低于预期，利润增长乏力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，PayPal 预测第四季度营收低于预期，原因是这家数字支付公司将重点从积极扩张转向利润率更高的业务，导致其股价在开盘前下跌 6.6%。【原文：PayPal forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates on Tuesday as the digital payments company shifts its focus to higher-margin businesses from aggressive expansion, sending its shares down 6.6% before the market open.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/paypal-forecasts-q4-revenue-below-estimates-profit-push-puts-growth-behind-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2G2LTSN5NVKMHM3F465HS3X7AE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特股价下跌 6%，原因是供应障碍和成本影响了利润预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司周二股价下跌 6%，此前该公司调低了全年利润预期，将原因归咎于产能过剩引发的全球价格战导致的供应商中断和保修成本。【原文：Ford Motor shares fell 6% on Tuesday after the automaker tempered its full-year profit forecast, blaming supplier disruptions and warranty costs amid a global price war fueled by overcapacity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-shares-fall-6-supply-snags-costs-hurt-profit-forecast-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TESJOK63EJMYFERYA5YQCY3BWQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 11:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞上调利润预期，第三季度业绩超预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞公司周二上调了全年盈利预期，此前其 COVID-19 疗法的销售好于预期，帮助其第三季度盈利超过了华尔街的预期。【原文：Pfizer raised its full-year profit forecast after better-than-expected sales of its COVID-19 treatment helped it beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter earnings on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pfizer-raises-profit-forecast-after-beating-third-quarter-estimates-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BMCCRSDTQVOCJGP7SRINXNKYY4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[皇家加勒比因邮轮需求强劲和价格上涨而上调年度盈利预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[皇家加勒比公司周二第四次上调了今年的年度利润预期，这主要得益于该游轮运营商多次上调船票价格，以及对私人目的地和凉爽景点游轮的需求增加。【原文：Royal Caribbean on Tuesday raised its annual profit forecast for a fourth time this year, boosted by the cruise operator's multiple ticket price hikes and higher demand for cruises to private destinations and cooler spots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/royal-caribbean-lifts-annual-profit-forecast-strong-cruise-demand-price-hikes-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4LEJWBDRIRPBFAJTYBO5DXTD5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[不断恶化的写字楼贷款给美国地区性银行的 CRE 投资组合带来压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师表示，随着远程工作的持续盛行，美国地区性银行仍在努力应对其办公楼贷款账面上的压力，但降息可能会缓解其他商业房地产（CRE）领域的压力，从而提供一些缓解措施。【原文：U.S. regional banks continue to grapple with pressures in their office loan books as remote work stays prevalent, but rate cuts may provide some relief by easing the strain on other commercial real estate (CRE) segments, analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/deteriorating-office-loans-stress-us-regional-banks-cre-portfolios-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CPHXWUKCYBPK5EAUQLG7SEDMEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:46:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于扭亏为盈计划初见成效，面包车所有者 VF Corp 的业绩飙升 22]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vans 制造商 VF Corp 在连续两个季度亏损后扭亏为盈，股价在周二的盘前交易中大涨 22%，促使投资者押注这家陷入困境的服装和鞋类制造商将以快于预期的速度扭亏为盈。【原文：Shares of Vans maker VF Corp surged 22% in premarket trading on Tuesday after turning a profit following two quarters of losses, prompting investors to bet on a faster-than-expected turnaround at the struggling apparel and footwear maker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/vans-owner-vf-corp-soars-22-turnaround-plan-starts-pay-off-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOJKM7E3IJJDTCN5WEM4CQIOKE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:33:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[倍耐力首席执行官称公司目前未计划关闭任何工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利轮胎制造商倍耐力公司首席执行官 Andrea Casaluci 在米兰举行的一次商业会议上表示，为应对汽车行业的危机，倍耐力公司不打算关闭任何工厂。【原文：Italian tyremaker Pirelli is not planning to close any of its factories as a response to the crisis of the automotive industry, CEO Andrea Casaluci said at a business conference in Milan.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/pirelli-ceo-says-company-is-not-currently-planning-any-factory-closures-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SDZOOLRVSZJBJLXMNKZHWDSFFE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：大选躁动的国债与巨型股的收益相得益彰]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DNZYGVXIDNJJDBSR6C6ICANL2I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究发现：到 2035 年，德国汽车业转型可能导致 18.6 万个工作岗位流失]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汽车工业协会（VDA）委托进行的一项研究周二公布，到 2035 年，德国汽车工业的转型可能导致 18.6 万个工作岗位流失，其中约四分之一已经流失。【原文：The transformation of the German car industry could lead to 186,000 jobs losses by 2035, of which roughly a quarter have already occurred, a study commissioned by the VDA auto industry association released on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/german-car-industry-transformation-could-cost-186000-jobs-by-2035-study-finds-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S25VGBKTDBMEDLAEHPHOV7FOJI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:21:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国利率期权为共和党扫荡定价，波动率飙升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在下周美国总统大选之前，利率期权投资者正在进行一些交易，如果利率保持高位，这些交易将获得回报，这表明市场正在为共和党的大选定价。【原文：Ahead of the U.S. presidential election next week, investors in interest rate options are putting on trades that will pay off if rates remain elevated, suggesting that the market is pricing in a sweep by the Republican party.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-interest-rate-options-price-republican-sweep-jump-volatility-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NJM7Z2D2C5MKJACD6JLXEZRRPE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[小米首席执行官在发布电动汽车前吹嘘纽博格林赛道纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，就在该公司举行活动揭晓其量产车型的几小时前，其制造商小米公司表示，中国的一款电动汽车原型在德国艰苦的纽伯格林赛道上创下了单圈时间纪录。【原文：A prototype Chinese electric vehicle has set a record lap time at Germany's grueling Nurburgring track, its maker Xiaomi said on Tuesday just hours before a company event expected to reveal the production model of the car.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/xiaomi-chief-touts-nurburgring-record-ahead-ev-launch-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SBRM66FGAFMEHF4AFQZL7QGKNQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国市场对 iPhone 的需求使苹果公司的收入创两年来最大增幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司预计将于本周四公布其两年来最大的季度收入增长，在该公司年度发布周期即将结束时，iPhone 的需求将好于近几年，尤其是在中国。【原文：Apple is expected to report its biggest quarterly revenue jump in two years on Thursday, with iPhone demand faring better than recent years toward the end of the company's annual release cycle, especially in China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-set-biggest-revenue-jump-two-years-iphone-demand-china-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUVVZKHRJ5LLNM2ZS7BLBZSQAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储降息重振小企业乐观情绪和借贷计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年夏天，布莱恩-布朗（Brian Brown）在太浩湖附近的景观美化业务逐渐枯竭。【原文：This past summer, leads for Brian Brown's landscaping business near Lake Tahoe were drying up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-rate-cut-revives-small-business-optimism-plans-borrow-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RC2FC7AIMJJJDNIR6TJBWPEPXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片制造商艰难反弹，英特尔季度营收将大幅下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[英特尔预计将于本周四公布其五个季度以来最大的季度收入降幅，这可能预示着这家曾经的标志性美国芯片制造商的数据中心和个人电脑市场份额将受到更多侵蚀。【原文：Intel is expected to report its biggest quarterly revenue drop in five quarters on Thursday, potentially signaling more erosion of data center and personal computer market share for the once iconic American chipmaker.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-set-big-drop-quarterly-revenue-chipmaker-struggles-bounce-back-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IPJBJMQUONMYXMXFWY7RZU4QAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道巴拿马运河运输量下降 65% 后寻求液化天然气卷土重来]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴拿马运河管理局（Panama Canal Authority）告诉路透社，随着亚洲市场需求的增长，以及新的预订系统允许托运人锁定船位，巴拿马运河旨在重新获得运载美国液化天然气前往亚洲的船舶流量，此前该运河第二重要航段的运输量下降了 65%。【原文：The Panama Canal aims to regain vessel traffic carrying U.S. liquefied natural gas to Asia as demand in that market rises and a new reservation system allows shippers to lock in slots, following a 65% decline in the transit of its second-most important segment, the Panama Canal Authority told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/panama-canal-seeks-lng-comeback-after-65-decline-traffic-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HPBACXHS5JIDLF4K4PMCSPOJQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[邮轮运营商从自己的私人岛屿中获益]]></title><description><![CDATA[主要的邮轮运营商正在引导他们的邮轮--以及数百万美元的投资--进入他们自己的私人目的地，那里有游览项目、海滩、酒吧和餐馆。【原文：Major cruise operators are steering their ships - and millions of dollars in investments - into their own private destinations packed with excursions, beaches, bars and restaurants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/cruise-operators-reap-benefits-their-own-private-islands-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5WCUP2GRBNH3CYJGV2S3NNBSU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:05:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国投票前一周，耶伦重提经济强劲的论点]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）试图重新阐述拜登政府的经济记录，她认为美国人的经济状况比乔-拜登总统上任时更好。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen is seeking to reclaim the narrative on the Biden administration's economic record on Tuesday, arguing that Americans are better off than they were when President Joe Biden took office.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/week-before-us-vote-yellen-revives-arguments-strong-economy-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZVSTU4CNF5PAVN42BQRQITVMSI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 10:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在财报大潮中，期货市场踯躅不前；福特汽车下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，美国股指期货变化不大，因为投资者准备迎接一系列公司业绩，尤其是 Alphabet 的业绩，以衡量科技行业的强弱。【原文：U.S. stock index futures were little changed on Tuesday as investors prepared for a bevy of corporate results, most notably from Alphabet to gauge the strength of the technology sector.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-tread-water-amid-earnings-deluge-ford-falls-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORUS43V2BZOHBFA7VGOYHVONIQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:59:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿迪达斯与说唱歌手叶达成庭外和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿迪达斯周二表示，阿迪达斯已与说唱歌手叶达成庭外和解，结束双方之间的所有法律诉讼，并补充说，协议中没有任何金钱交易。【原文：Adidas has reached an out-of-court settlement with rapper Ye to end all legal proceedings between them, the sportswear brand said on Tuesday, adding that no money changed hands in the agreement.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/adidas-reaches-settlement-with-rapper-ye-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZG3CX4I77BIPJDCWJXFEBO75JY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:56:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登宣布为美国港口投资 30 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周二宣布，将从《通货膨胀削减法案》（Inflation Reduction Act）中拨款 30 亿美元，用于改善美国的港口基础设施。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden on Tuesday announced a $3 billion investment from his Inflation Reduction Act to improve the country's port infrastructure.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-announces-3-bln-investment-us-ports-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4J5VD6ZJJNEZFUOYZYMWHCD5M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:11:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金斥资 2.17 亿美元购买美国办公楼 98% 的股份]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威主权财富基金周二表示，已与美国房地产投资公司DivcoWest合资，以2.17亿美元的价格购买了旧金山湾区门洛帕克一处办公楼物业97.7%的股份。【原文：Norway's sovereign wealth fund said on Tuesday it has bought a 97.7% stake in an office property in Menlo Park in the San Francisco bay area for $217 million, in a joint venture with U.S. real estate investment firm DivcoWest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/norways-sovereign-wealth-fund-buys-98-us-office-building-217-mln-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V5PDSTXJQBKW3FDLDYYFMN7PI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:09:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国非营利组织斥资 2.5 亿美元购买电动卡车，租赁给加利福尼亚港口]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国非营利组织气候联合公司周二宣布了一项计划，将在三年内斥资高达 2.5 亿美元购买多达 500 辆电动半挂卡车，该计划被称为迄今为止美国最大的一笔零排放卡车订单。【原文：U.S. nonprofit Climate United on Tuesday announced a plan to spend up to $250 million to buy as many as 500 electric semi trucks over three years in what it called the biggest single order of those zero-emissions trucks in the country so far.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-nonprofit-spend-250-mln-electric-trucks-lease-california-ports-2024-10-29/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CYOUYZ25JBIFJFRTYCTAEUI44M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>