<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:07:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:07:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛旗下 Flipkart 的在线卖家就反垄断调查起诉印度监察机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的法庭文件，在沃尔玛旗下的 Flipkart 上运营的三家在线卖家起诉了印度反垄断监督机构，因为该机构在调查中发现他们、Flipkart 和竞争对手亚马逊违反了竞争法。【原文：Three online sellers operating on Walmart -owned Flipkart have sued the Indian antitrust watchdog over an investigation which found they, Flipkart and rival Amazon breached competition laws, according to court filings seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/online-sellers-walmarts-flipkart-sue-india-watchdog-over-antitrust-probe-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHSZRTQPTZLMNFJLYQRHVFAWNQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯钢铁部门主管为 "艰难 "裁员做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[蒂森克虏伯集团钢铁部门的新任负责人告诉德国一家报纸，该集团的 27,000 名钢铁工人必须为大幅裁员做好准备。【原文：Thyssenkrupp's 27,000 steel workers must brace for deep cuts, the new head of the conglomerate's steel division told a German newspaper, setting the stage for significant layoffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/thyssenkrupp-steel-head-prepares-staff-tough-cuts-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O4RRCX4WC5NX5JPS6TRBLM3A4A</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 10:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[关注：如果您的人工智能看起来更聪明，那要归功于更聪明的人类培训师]]></title><description><![CDATA[早年，要让 ChatGPT 或其竞争对手 Cohere 等人工智能模型做出类似人类的反应，需要大量低成本员工帮助模型分辨基本事实，比如一张图片是汽车还是胡萝卜。【原文：In the early years, getting AI models like ChatGPT or its rival Cohere to spit out human-like responses required vast teams of low-cost workers helping models distinguish basic facts such as if an image was of a car or a carrot.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/if-your-ai-seems-smarter-its-thanks-smarter-human-trainers-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRFQUTY7X5O5TFJMEEWY44CS3I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 10:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[工会称波音工资谈判破裂，结束罢工毫无进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际机械师和航空航天工人协会（IAM）周五晚些时候表示，其与波音公司的薪资协议谈判已经破裂，目前没有安排进一步的谈判日期。【原文：The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) said late on Friday that its pay deal talks with Boeing had broken off and that there were no further dates scheduled for negotiations at this time.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/boeing-wage-talks-break-off-without-progress-end-strike-union-says-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ORIUMHP4EVJY7JLI6QVBYFOK2I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 04:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：道明银行可能在洗钱调查中认罪]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，道明银行（TD Bank）即将可能承认一项刑事指控，即其美国零售银行未能遏制与中国犯罪集团和非法芬太尼销售有关的洗钱活动。【原文：TD Bank is close to a possible guilty plea to criminal charges that its U.S. retail bank failed to curb money laundering tied to Chinese crime groups and illicit fentanyl sales, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/td-bank-nears-possible-guilty-plea-money-laundering-probe-wsj-reports-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FEU7MV2DD5L7HKVLQHLEIE3L74</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 04:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》称苹果退出加入 OpenAI 投资回合谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五称，苹果公司已退出参与 OpenAI 一轮融资的谈判，预计该轮融资将筹集约 65 亿美元。【原文：Apple has left negotiations to participate in an OpenAI funding round expected to raise about $6.5 billion, the Wall Street Journal said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/apple-drops-out-talks-join-openai-investment-round-wsj-says-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G3LJBR6YRFLTFC6LXLUBRGJJZM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 01:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UAW 敦促斯泰兰特工人批准罢工，指责汽车制造商违反合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）主席肖恩-费恩（Shawn Fain）周五在致该联合会美国分会的一封信中说，美国汽车工人联合会要求斯泰兰特公司的工人授权举行罢工，指责这家法国意大利汽车制造商违背了合同承诺。【原文：The United Auto Workers union asked the workers at Stellantis to authorize a strike, accusing the French-Italian car maker of breaking its contract promises, UAW President Shawn Fain said in a letter to the union's U.S. chapters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-urges-stellantis-workers-authorize-strike-accuses-car-maker-breaching-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HAMZ7AC7IBI7FH4LY34HDPND2I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenAI 明年营收将达 116 亿美元，为 Thrive 提供了在 2025 年再次投资的机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五表示，Thrive Capital 在 OpenAI 目前的 65 亿美元募资轮中投资了超过 10 亿美元，而且还得到了其他投资者没有得到的甜头：如果这家人工智能公司达到营收目标，Thrive Capital 有可能在明年以同样的估值再投资 10 亿美元。【原文：Thrive Capital is investing more than $1 billion of OpenAI's current $6.5 billion fundraising round, and it has a sweetener no other investors are getting: the potential to invest another $1 billion next year at the same valuation if the AI firm hits a revenue goal, people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/openai-sees-116-billion-revenue-next-year-offers-thrive-chance-invest-again-2025-2024-09-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FSACLST6ZILFJC2C2SBEDX6SE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:14:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球主动管理型 ETF 资产规模突破 1 万亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据提供商 ETFGI 的数据显示，在更宽松的监管和产品创新浪潮的推动下，全球主动管理交易所交易基金（ETF）的资产在 8 月底达到了创纪录的 1 万亿美元。【原文：Assets in actively managed exchange-traded funds (ETFs) worldwide hit a record $1 trillion at the end of August, according to data provider ETFGI, boosted by easier regulations and a wave of product innovation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/assets-actively-managed-etfs-top-1-trillion-worldwide-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AYJ3WWGTZBNLJF4MWELN47ZAFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 23:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西最高法院裁定 X 必须支付未付罚款才能恢复服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西最高法院周五表示，根据一份法庭文件，社交平台 X 需要支付略高于 500 万美元的罚款，才能恢复其在巴西的服务。【原文：Brazilian Supreme Court said on Friday that social platform X needs to pay just over $5 million in pending fines in order to resume its service in the country, according to a court document.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/brazils-top-court-rules-x-must-pay-pending-fines-resume-service-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMDKODTJVRJXVK3PXJENMGFN4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Binance 创始人赵明从美国拘留所获释]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社援引监狱管理局发言人的话报道，Binance 创始人赵长鹏周五从加利福尼亚州的一家惩教机构获释。【原文：Binance founder Changpeng Zhao was released from a correctional facility in California on Friday, Bloomberg News reported, citing a spokesperson for the Bureau of Prisons.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/binance-founder-zhao-released-us-custody-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KO6BQFYHJRMUDKVFRDUYPPSF4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官就家属反对波音认罪协议举行听证会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦地区法官里德-奥康纳（Reed O'Connor）周五表示，他将于 10 月 11 日举行听证会，审议两起波音 737 MAX 飞机坠毁事故中遇难者亲属对该飞机制造商承认共谋欺诈犯罪协议的反对意见。【原文：U.S. District Judge Reed O'Connor said Friday he will hold a hearing on Oct. 11 to consider objections from relatives of those killed in two Boeing 737 MAX crashes to the planemaker's agreement to plead guilty to criminal fraud conspiracy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-judge-hold-hearing-family-objections-boeing-plea-deal-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2QIZFA6GVNEBLHAQ2WK2U5QYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国医疗保险计划称 2025 年 D 部分和优势部分保费将下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国医疗保险与医疗补助服务中心（Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services）周五表示，预计2025年医疗保险处方药计划和私人医疗保险计划的平均保费和福利将保持稳定，保费略有下降。【原文：Average premiums and benefits for Medicare's prescription drug program and private Medicare plans are projected to remain stable in 2025 with premiums slightly declining, the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-medicare-says-part-d-advantage-premiums-will-fall-2025-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FIL4TUV63JIWRIWHKJPT4TQB7Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:49:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 就业数据考验美国股市软着陆希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[投资者对美国经济软着陆的希望将在下周经受考验，因为在一系列令人失望的就业报告发布后，政府将公布备受关注的劳动力市场数据。【原文：Investor hopes for a soft landing for the U.S. economy will be put to the test next week, as the government releases closely watched labor market data following a series of disappointing jobs reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-jobs-data-test-us-stock-markets-soft-landing-hopes-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TB2GMXHGEZP2RJWX2CC2PYGTAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，2030 年巴西混合动力和电动汽车销量将超过其他市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西汽车制造商协会 Anfavea 周五发布的一份研究报告显示，预计到 2030 年，巴西新型全电动或混合动力汽车的销量将超过内燃机汽车。【原文：The sales of new fully electric or hybrid cars in Brazil are expected to surpass sales of vehicles run on combustion engines in 2030, a study released on Friday by automakers association Anfavea showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/hybrid-electric-car-sales-outpace-rest-market-brazil-2030-study-shows-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KRQAAKZD5JJAXPEYNDTLIK7J4I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:15:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登称未改变对新日铁交易的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）周五表示，尽管新日本制铁公司（Nippon Steel）以 149 亿美元的价格竞购美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel）的计划已被延长国家安全审查，但他并没有改变主意。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden on Friday said he had not changed his mind about Nippon Steel's $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel despite the extension of a national security review of the proposed tie-up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/biden-says-he-hasnt-changed-his-mind-nippon-steel-deal-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y5WJXMHQMNNBVO3ACGXW64PC3Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:50:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在港口可能发生罢工之前，美墨铁路延误打击了农业部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[农业团体周五表示，铁路积压正在干扰美国和墨西哥之间的出口贸易，并在秋收之际阻断了农产品供应链。【原文：Rail backlogs are disrupting export trade between the United States and Mexico and snarling agricultural supply chains as the fall harvest is under way, agriculture groups said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-mexico-rail-delays-hit-farm-sector-ahead-possible-ports-strike-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ZQC57U5OZKO7CHAKFQTJG7XX4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:49:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆萨莱姆称美联储应 "逐步 "降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[圣路易斯联邦储备银行行长阿尔贝托-穆萨莱姆周五表示，美国央行应该 "循序渐进 "地降低利率，在此之前，他将上周降息半个百分点称为 "强烈而明确的信息"，他表示支持降息。【原文：St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank President Alberto Musalem on Friday said the U.S. central bank should cut interest rates "gradually" after what he called the "strong and clear message" of a half-point interest-rate cut last week, which he said he supported.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-should-cut-interest-rates-gradually-musalem-says-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGWMZSGJKRN5PCF73NCB6QTNCI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国对加拿大航空公司飞越伊拉克领空罚款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部周五表示，已对加拿大航空公司处以 25 万美元的罚款，原因是该公司 2022 年和 2023 年在被禁止的伊拉克领空运营航班。【原文：The U.S. Department of Transportation said Friday it had fined Air Canada $250,000 for operating flights in 2022 and 2023 in prohibited Iraqi airspace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-fines-air-canada-over-flights-over-prohibited-iraqi-airspace-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PNZAGD2CEBIYTHRE5H5BZHZOV4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[备忘录称，花旗银行就员工和承包商的不当行为向部分员工发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周五看到的一份备忘录，花旗集团就欺诈和不道德行为向一些员工发出警告，并表示正在考虑加强对承包商所做工作的审查，以确保公司的账单准确无误。【原文：Citigroup warned some employees about fraud and unethical behavior and said it is considering tighter scrutiny on work done by contractors to ensure the company is billed accurately, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citi-warns-some-employees-about-misconduct-by-staff-contractors-memo-says-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XDZOK2OEOBMDDNGJAK2NKCLR6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:29:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会指控芒果市场公司发售未经注册的加密代币]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会周五指控加密货币交易平台芒果市场（Mango Markets）未经注册销售其数字资产代币，监管机构将其认定为证券。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday charged cryptocurrency trading platform Mango Markets with unregistered sales of its digital asset token, which the regulator identified as a security.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-sec-charges-mango-markets-with-offering-unregistered-crypto-token-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPTBBISJWVJ6ZL65YK5KNWOAOA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 19:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩根士丹利的私募股权投资部门正在探索出售暖通空调公司 Sila]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士周五表示，摩根士丹利的中间市场收购部门正在探讨出售西拉服务公司（Sila Services），包括债务在内，这家住宅服务公司的估值可能在 15 亿美元左右。【原文：Morgan Stanley's middle-market buyout arm is exploring a sale of Sila Services that could value the residential services company at about $1.5 billion, including debt, people familiar with the matter said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/morgan-stanleys-private-equity-arm-explores-sale-hvac-firm-sila-sources-say-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDTMJP2IDFLXDNBZ2BV4NVSWH4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 18:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称若赢得大选将起诉谷歌]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国前总统、共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普周五表示，如果他在 11 月 5 日的大选中获胜，他将寻求起诉谷歌，声称该公司只显示关于他的 "坏故事"。【原文：Former U.S. President Donald Trump, who is the Republican presidential candidate, said on Friday he will seek the prosecution of Google if he wins the Nov. 5 election, claiming that the company only displays "bad stories" about him.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-he-will-seek-googles-prosecution-if-he-wins-election-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G72IGPIB3ZOPLD3CXXL3KJW73Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 18:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷米莱航空公司计划通过法令实现国有航空公司私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿根廷总统发言人曼努埃尔-阿多尼（Manuel Adorni）表示，阿根廷总统哈维尔-米莱（Javier Milei）打算在下周签署一项法令，对阿根廷航空公司（Aerolineas Argentinas）进行私有化。【原文：Argentina's President Javier Milei intends to sign a decree next week aimed at the privatization of flag carrier Aerolineas Argentinas, said presidential spokesman Manuel Adorni.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/argentinas-milei-plans-privatize-state-airline-by-decree-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3TAA5A4TBNV7GVBJ7HATLTQEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，联合信贷银行将把经过再培训的员工从中央办公室转移到网络中]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位消息人士周五透露，意大利联合信贷银行（UniCredit）计划投入大量资金对 600 名员工进行再培训，随着首席执行官 Andrea Orcel 缩减中央办事处的规模并加强销售队伍的力量，这些员工将大部分转移到该银行的分行网络。【原文：UniCredit plans to invest significantly in the retraining of 600 staff who will then be largely moved to the Italian bank's branch network as CEO Andrea Orcel slims down central offices and powers the sales force, two sources said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-shift-retrained-staff-central-offices-network-sources-say-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DR5ZQW7HFNMQJKRJUAD5HVQ33A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[白宫敦促工会和雇主就新的港口合同进行谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位白宫官员说，拜登政府正敦促工会和雇主在周二港口可能发生罢工之前，真诚、迅速地进行谈判，以达成新的合同协议。【原文：The Biden administration is urging the union and employers to negotiate in good faith and quickly to reach a new contract deal ahead of a potential strike at ports on Tuesday, a White House official said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/white-house-urges-union-employers-negotiate-new-ports-contract-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQG452V5WFLQXDUFN6U7XPMZBM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车因宏观经济不利因素下调 2024 年展望]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车周五下调了其年度展望，理由是其乘用车部门的业绩低于预期，以及宏观经济环境恶化。【原文：Volkswagen on Friday cut its annual outlook, citing a weaker-than-expected performance of its passenger car division as well as a deteriorating macroeconomic environment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-cuts-2024-outlook-macroeconomic-headwinds-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M5GZ7SWLBBJS5OUWIMN76AO3GM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登提议的中国汽车技术禁令可能使美国汽车销量减少多达 2.5 万辆]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部周五表示，禁止在美国汽车中使用中国互联汽车和中国关键软件及汽车硬件的新规定可能会使美国汽车销量每年减少多达25,841辆，并使价格上涨。【原文：The Commerce Department said Friday that new rules proposed to ban Chinese connected vehicles and key Chinese software and vehicle hardware in American cars could cut U.S. auto sales by up to 25,841 vehicles per year and raise prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/proposed-biden-chinese-car-tech-ban-could-cut-up-25000-us-auto-sales-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MJUVFWITJNOHBQAFTGNJLU4ZA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果必须面对涉及其应用程序的范围缩小的隐私诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官缩小了指控苹果公司通过 App Store、Apple Music 和 Apple TV 等专有应用程序收集 iPhone、iPad 和 Apple Watch 用户个人数据从而侵犯其隐私权的诉讼范围。【原文：A federal judge narrowed a lawsuit accusing Apple of violating the privacy of iPhone, iPad and Apple Watch users by collecting their personal data through proprietary apps such as the App Store, Apple Music and Apple TV.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/apple-must-face-narrowed-privacy-lawsuit-over-its-apps-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KCVPLXK7JLQBN25O4AUN2AAY4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会称，Chewy 公司高管就宠物保险合作进行内幕交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）周五表示，Chewy 公司一名前高管将支付 35275 美元，以了结 2021 年以来的内幕交易指控。【原文：A former Chewy executive will pay $35,275 to settle U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission insider trading charges dating from 2021, the regulator said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/chewy-executive-conducted-insider-trading-over-pet-insurance-partnership-sec-2024-09-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OSZLG7LNKVM6VO4B4WD57UXTWY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>