<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:06:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:06:28 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国 12 月建筑支出超出预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[受独户住宅建设的推动，12 月份美国建筑支出增幅超过预期，但高抵押贷款利率可能会抑制新住宅建设的进一步增长。【原文：U.S. construction spending increased more than expected in December, boosted by single-family homebuilding, but high mortgage rates could curb further gains in new residential construction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-construction-spending-beats-expectations-december-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">725L5EFDJ5MF5HZCPEXZPVAEGM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安大略省在最新一次加拿大关税抗议中取消了 Starlink 合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大安大略省周一宣布取消与埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的星链公司（Starlink）签订的价值 1 亿加元（约合 6812 万美元）的合同，这是对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）宣布加征关税的最新报复性举措。【原文：The Canadian province of Ontario on Monday announced it was cancelling a C$100 million ($68.12 million) contract with Elon Musk's Starlink, the latest retaliatory move against tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ontario-cancels-starlink-contract-latest-canadian-tariffs-protest-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MRV34E4FEJKQ3FEJF63YWULOPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税推动华尔街下跌，美元上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于担心美国总统唐纳德-特朗普对加拿大、墨西哥和中国征收关税只是全球贸易战的开端，会抑制经济增长，导致全球股市大跌，华尔街周一开盘走低。【原文：Wall Street opened lower on Monday following a worldwide selloff driven by concern that U.S. President Donald Trump's tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China are just the opening salvo in a global trade war that would curb economic growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">F3ZA3VVVUVIFLOYHVWYC77HHHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥向投资者作出保证，坚称可承受金融冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥财政部长罗赫略-拉米雷斯-德拉奥（Rogelio Ramirez de la O）周一表示，在美国宣布对墨西哥商品征收25%的关税后，墨西哥有足够的资源吸收金融冲击并应对全球挑战。【原文：Mexico has enough resources to absorb financial shocks and navigate global challenges after the United States announced 25% tariffs on its goods, Finance Minister Rogelio Ramirez de la O said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-offers-assurances-investors-insists-it-can-absorb-financial-shocks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SKLNDRKDN5PXXADTZGR4OSIZF4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:12:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1 月份美国制造业反弹；投入品支付价格指数大幅上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于订单强劲，美国制造业在 1 月份出现了两年多来的首次增长，但衡量工厂支付原材料价格的一项指标却稳中有升，而且在唐纳德-特朗普总统于上周末对来自加拿大和墨西哥的商品加征关税之后，价格可能会进一步上涨。【原文：U.S. manufacturing grew for the first time in more than two years in January amid strong orders, but a measure of prices paid by factories for raw materials rose solidly, and more increases are likely after President Donald Trump imposed tariffs on goods from Canada and Mexico at the weekend.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-manufacturing-rebounds-january-inputs-prices-paid-measure-surges-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6U7KBK7FORI2HGTYNHKLZLN3SA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:05:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在瑞典和挪威市场份额下降，马斯克阴影笼罩]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一的汽车登记数据显示，特斯拉一月份在瑞典和挪威的市场份额有所下降，这家美国电动汽车制造商在亿万富翁首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）高调涉足政坛后面临着人气考验。【原文：Tesla lost market share in Sweden and Norway in January, car registration data showed on Monday as the U.S. electric vehicle maker faces a test of popularity following billionaire CEO Elon Musk's high-profile foray into politics.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-loses-market-share-sweden-norway-musk-looms-large-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AO55U35DYZJVPPK52R2DGA3GFM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼影业从哥伦比亚广播公司收回《幸运之轮》和《危情时刻》的发行权]]></title><description><![CDATA[索尼影业公司周一在致哥伦比亚广播公司的一封信中表示，由于哥伦比亚广播公司制片厂未能履行合同条款，索尼影业公司已承担起热门电视节目《幸运之轮》和《危情时速》的全球发行职能。【原文：Sony Pictures has assumed global distribution functions for hit TV shows "Wheel of Fortune" and "Jeopardy!" citing failure by CBS Studios to live up to contract terms, the company said in a letter to CBS on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/sony-pictures-takes-back-distribution-rights-wheel-fortune-jeopardy-cbs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SYPHVA2VJNKVO6TCDGF6HZITQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特一月份美国销量下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特公司周一表示，由于内燃（ICE）汽车需求下降，该公司一月份在美国的销量下降了 6.3%。【原文：Ford's January sales in the U.S. fell 6.3% owing to lower demand for its internal combustion (ICE) vehicles, the company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-us-sales-dip-january-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SHKGOZWG7JIP7KXHE6BRYMWMCE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易战风险削弱信心，加拿大 1 月份工厂采购经理指数下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美国贸易关税迫在眉睫，加拿大制造业活动在 1 月份的增长速度有所放缓，这降低了人们对前景的信心，尽管客户为抢在美国征税之前采取行动，导致出口订单出现了 17 个月以来的首次增长。【原文：Canadian manufacturing activity increased at a slower pace in January as looming U.S. trade tariffs reduced confidence in the outlook, even as moves by clients to get ahead of the taxes led to the first increase in export orders in 17 months.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadian-factory-pmi-dips-january-trade-war-risk-dents-confidence-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AY3LHA7QENKJHM5HBQOHSA5SD4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在全球需求的推动下，Cboe 计划将股票交易时间延长至 24 小时]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cboe 全球市场公司（Cboe Global Markets）周一宣布，计划将美国股票交易扩展至每周五天、每天 24 小时的形式，以满足全球对美国股票市场的需求。【原文：Cboe Global Markets on Monday announced plans to expand U.S. equities trading to a 24-hour, five-days-a-week format to meet the global demand for the country's stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cboe-plans-extend-equities-trading-24-hours-amid-global-demand-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HRRGVHBARPCFKJY6QNV2G3CPE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RTX 前首席执行官格雷戈里-海耶斯卸任董事长一职]]></title><description><![CDATA[RTX 前首席执行官格雷戈里-海耶斯（Gregory Hayes）周一表示，将辞去执行董事长和董事会成员的职务。【原文：Former RTX CEO Gregory Hayes will step down as executive chairman and member of the board, the aerospace and defense major said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/former-rtx-ceo-gregory-hayes-step-down-chairman-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGIH7ZEJD5OTRJSNEUNS2PN52A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:37:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[哥伦比亚 Ecopetrol 公司与西方石油公司在二叠纪盆地续建合资企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚能源公司 Ecopetrol 周一表示，它已与西方石油公司达成协议，续签其在美国得克萨斯州二叠纪盆地的石油合资企业。【原文：Colombian energy company Ecopetrol said on Monday it has reached an agreement to renew its oil joint venture with Occidental Petroleum in the U.S. Permian basin in Texas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/colombias-ecopetrol-renews-joint-venture-with-occidental-petroleum-permian-basin-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ISWNIR63UBNHNPUPHZ7HSRXTE4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达阵交易Robinhood 推出超级碗预测合约]]></title><description><![CDATA[Robinhood 周一表示，该公司将推出赛事合同，让美国用户就超级碗的比赛结果下注，试图利用美国最具标志性的体育赛事之一的博彩狂热。【原文：Robinhood is rolling out event contracts to let U.S. users wager on the outcome of the Super Bowl clash, it said on Monday, seeking to tap into the betting mania around one of the most iconic sporting events in the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trading-touchdowns-robinhood-launches-super-bowl-prediction-contracts-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWFTR5WHGFMRDJTU4C53C4EDFI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在特朗普冻结美国援助之际，诺和诺德基金会表示没有支持全球卫生事业的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位官员告诉路透社，诺和诺德基金会不打算介入因美国冻结对外援助而陷入困境的全球卫生部门，并将继续专注于其核心的非传染性疾病议程。【原文：The Novo Nordisk Foundation does not plan to step in to prop up a global health sector reeling from a freeze on U.S.-funded foreign aid, and will continue to focus on its core non-communicable disease agenda, an official told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/no-plan-prop-up-global-health-novo-nordisk-foundation-says-trump-freezes-us-aid-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HKUQACXZNKADOO2A2CVF3YETY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 12:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国恒大电动汽车部门称在流动性危机中努力吸引投资者]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国恒大新能源汽车公司（China Evergrande New Energy Vehicle）周一表示，在严重的流动性危机下，该公司正努力吸引战略投资者，这阻碍了其运营，并推迟了 2024 年的必要审计。【原文：China Evergrande New Energy Vehicle said on Monday it is struggling to attract strategic investors amid a severe liquidity crisis, which has hampered its operations and delayed essential audits for 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-evergrandes-ev-unit-says-struggling-attract-investors-amid-liquidity-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZOJMH5AVNLPRF4LOM6T2BK4CM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 12:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司因牛肉和鸡肉需求强劲而上调年度销售预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）周一上调了年度销售预期，因为市场对其牛肉和鸡肉产品的强劲需求帮助该肉类包装公司第一季度业绩超出预期，使其股价在盘前交易中上涨了 4%。【原文：Tyson Foods raised its annual sales forecast on Monday as robust demand for its beef and chicken products helped the meat packer beat estimates for first-quarter results, sending its shares up 4% in premarket trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/tyson-foods-raises-annual-sales-forecast-beef-chicken-demand-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DQTN6E76BNIUTFKZJZU2CQOJHU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 12:37:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国金属买家可能转向中东和智利，因为关税会造成影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[据业内人士透露，美国公司将向中东和印度寻求更多的铝，并向智利和秘鲁寻求铜，以规避美国总统唐纳德-特朗普征收的全面关税。【原文：U.S. companies will look to the Middle East and India for more aluminium and to Chile and Peru for copper as they seek to circumvent sweeping tariffs imposed by U.S. President Donald Trump, according to industry sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-metal-buyers-likely-turn-mideast-chile-tariffs-bite-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DRLH5K5IEZIYFGVPQJCWTBSFLQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 12:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[随着大科技公司转向定制芯片，AMD 的人工智能赌注面临投资者审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[AMD 周二公布第四季度业绩时，投资者将仔细研究这家芯片设计公司的人工智能战略，因为大科技公司向定制硅的转变让人怀疑它在人工智能基础设施竞赛中的地位。【原文：AMD investors will closely examine the chip designer's artificial intelligence strategy when it reports fourth-quarter results on Tuesday as Big Tech's shift to custom silicon raises doubts about its place in the AI infrastructure race.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/amds-ai-bets-face-investor-scrutiny-big-tech-switches-custom-chips-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IEWAIWTGMRPOZG2PNF7TXAMPLU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 12:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称欧佩克+可能坚持石油增产计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）敦促欧佩克（OPEC）降低价格，但欧佩克+组织的代表告诉路透社记者，欧佩克+组织可能会在周一举行的最高部长小组会议上坚持目前的计划，即从四月份开始逐步提高产量。【原文：OPEC+ is likely to adhere to current plans to raise output gradually from April when a panel of top ministers meets on Monday, delegates from the producer group told Reuters, despite U.S. President Donald Trump urging OPEC to lower prices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-likely-stick-oil-output-hike-plan-sources-say-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJ66AWDVWFKZHPK6W5ORV4KAXA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:46:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普关税对高盛标普 500 指数盈利预测的影响高达 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛的经济学家估计，如果美国总统唐纳德-特朗普在第二个任期上任后宣布的最新贸易关税措施得以持续，那么美国企业的底线可能会被大幅削减。【原文：Goldman Sachs economists estimate that if the latest trade tariffs announced by U.S. President Donald Trump after assuming office in his second term are sustained, they could take a significant chunk out of Corporate America's bottom line.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-flags-up-3-hit-its-sp-500-earnings-forecasts-trumps-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DGT4N2KMARP7LJXR5UQ5NNEZ6E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛集团称，全球对冲基金抛售了除房地产股以外的所有股票]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在美国总统特朗普宣布加征关税导致全球市场暴跌之前，高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）表示，对冲基金上周抛弃了全球股市，并增加了对股市下跌的押注。【原文：Hedge funds last week jettisoned global stocks and added bets they would decline, said Goldman Sachs , just before U.S. President Trump announced tariffs that sent global markets tumbling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-hedge-funds-dump-everything-real-estate-stocks-says-goldman-sachs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W3PNC7QBPRLOVBDYN6C2OHUIHY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:36:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 市场因 "关税人 "而不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲、中东和非洲地区金融和市场突发新闻记者 Alun John 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天。【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets by Alun John, EMEA breaking news correspondent, finance and markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EOAHLONSFBPKVKT2FF3ECRPG2A</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌要求美国上诉法院推翻应用商店判决]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下谷歌和 "堡垒之夜 "游戏制造商 Epic Games 的律师将于周一在加利福尼亚州的一家美国上诉法院对簿公堂，因为谷歌试图推翻陪审团的裁决和法官迫使其改造应用商店的命令。【原文：Lawyers for Alphabet's Google and "Fortnite" maker Epic Games are set to square off before a U.S. appeals court in California on Monday, as Google tries to undo a jury verdict and a judge's order forcing it to revamp its app store.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/google-ask-us-appeals-court-overturn-app-store-verdict-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5H4QWI44DNLIJM4Z6Q6GNWCRPU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:09:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道特朗普的纪念币交易费用近 1 亿美元，小交易商却亏了钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据三家区块链分析公司的估算，唐纳德-特朗普总统的加密钱币背后的实体在不到两周的时间里积累了近 1 亿美元的交易费用，这是一个让数以万计的小交易商亏损的风险投资所带来的巨额暴利。【原文：Entities behind President Donald Trump’s crypto coin have accumulated close to $100 million in trading fees in less than two weeks, according to estimates from three blockchain analysis firms, a large windfall from a venture that has seen tens of thousands of small traders lose money.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/trumps-meme-coin-made-nearly-100-million-trading-fees-small-traders-lost-money-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPECPFDLLRMFZEMSR47S3YIUME</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:06:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国冬季COVID浪潮较小，辉瑞公司扭亏压力增大]]></title><description><![CDATA[有迹象表明，今年冬天美国的 COVID-19 病例比往年要少得多，这可能会给辉瑞公司带来更大的压力，迫使其从非 COVID 治疗中寻找增长点。【原文：Health experts are seeing signs of a much smaller wave of U.S. COVID-19 cases this winter than in previous years, which could put additional pressure on Pfizer to find growth from its non-COVID treatments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/smaller-us-winter-covid-wave-adds-pressure-pfizer-turnaround-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SLN7CGQ6JNOH7EBT5UG23JSQU4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税后，贸易战担忧搅动美国汽车巨头和大型科技公司股价]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普下令对墨西哥、加拿大和中国全面征收关税，引发了对全球贸易战可能打击经济增长的担忧，汽车制造商和大型科技股在股市大面积回落中首当其冲。【原文：Shares of automakers and megacap tech stocks bore the brunt of a wider equity pullback on Monday after U.S. President Donald Trump ordered sweeping tariffs against Mexico, Canada and China, sparking fears of a global trade war that could hit growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/trade-war-fears-roil-shares-us-auto-majors-big-tech-after-trump-tariffs-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E543HGQREBMABBQI26UCKTXJ44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:38:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空首席执行官表示，汉莎航空将从 2025 年开始利用 ITA 盈利]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国汉莎航空公司首席执行官卡斯滕-斯波尔（Carsten Spohr）周一表示，德国汉莎航空公司将从今年开始从对 ITA Airways 的投资中获利。【原文：Germany's Lufthansa will start making money from its investment in ITA Airways from this year, the chief executive of the German carrier, Carsten Spohr, said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/lufthansa-will-start-making-money-with-ita-2025-ceo-says-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EW5IF2NZUNJHDNCB55EPBTEZEQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：阿根廷农场枯萎的树叶预示着大豆和玉米收成将受到更大打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[农民达里奥-萨比尼（Dario Sabini）站在田间高大干枯的玉米植株间，检查着比往常小一些的玉米棒子，然后拿起发黄的叶子在手指间揉搓，这个季节的玉米应该是绿色的。【原文：Standing in his fields among tall, dry corn plants, farmer Dario Sabini inspects the smaller-than-usual corn cobs before taking the yellowing leaves of the crop that should be green at this time of the season, to crinkle them between his fingers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/wilted-leaves-argentinas-farms-signal-bigger-hit-soy-corn-harvest-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">64HNVLTD45J5HETBOUW2EU6AXI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国应如何应对特朗普？问深科技]]></title><description><![CDATA[从尖锐的政治问题到深刻的个人问题，中国网民描述了向 DeepSeek 人工智能应用程序提出的问题，包括中国政府应该如何应对美国总统唐纳德-特朗普的进口关税。【原文：From the sharply political to the deeply personal, Chinese internet users have described questions asked of the DeepSeek artificial intelligence app, including what Beijing should do in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's import tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/how-should-china-respond-trump-ask-deepseek-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KWR5ZLZ2NFONDMZ2ZSFGHUIV2E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普加征关税引发贸易战风险，期货价格暴跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普总统对墨西哥、加拿大和中国征收高额关税后，全球市场担心全面贸易战及其对全球经济的影响，美国股指期货周一暴跌。【原文：U.S. stock index futures tumbled on Monday as fears of a full-blown trade war and its impact on the global economy jolted markets around the world after President Donald Trump levied steep tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-tumble-trumps-tariffs-stoke-trade-war-risks-2025-02-03/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYZDVNGI2RJRBCT35ICFC7HLTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 09:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>