<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:12:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:12:57 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据《金融时报》报道，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂计划于2027年4月卸任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《金融时报》周二报道，瑞银集团首席执行官塞尔吉奥·埃尔莫蒂计划于2027年4月卸任。【原文：UBS Group CEO Sergio Ermotti is planning to step down in April 2027, the Financial Times reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/ubs-ceo-sergio-ermotti-plans-step-down-april-2027-ft-reports-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EETKJNAFBBOLRNVBL2J4LS5AAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国消费者价格指数在政府停摆造成的扭曲影响下有所回落，但近期可能已出现反弹。]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国12月消费者价格涨幅可能扩大，因部分与政府停摆相关的扭曲因素已消除——这些因素曾人为压低11月通胀水平。这将强化市场预期，即美联储本月将维持利率不变。【原文：U.S. consumer prices likely accelerated in December as some of the distortions related to the government shutdown that had artificially lowered inflation in November unwound, which would ​cement expectations of the Federal Reserve leaving interest rates unchanged this month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-consumer-prices-likely-snapped-back-after-being-restrained-by-government-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">362MZEHY4VJXTJ3YNVKWSO77Z4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾称已与美国就关税谈判达成"广泛共识"]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾与美国在关税谈判中已达成"广泛共识"，双方正商讨举行最终会议的时间表。台北当局周二表示，知情人士称相关公告可能在本月底前发布。【原文：Taiwan and the U.S. have reached a "broad consensus" on their tariff talks and are discussing a timetable for holding a concluding meeting, Taipei said on Tuesday, as a source familiar with the matter said an announcement could come by the end of the month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-says-it-has-reached-broad-consensus-with-us-tariff-talks-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3FBHTXGRTNOTDLUUA757PGX4XQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:56:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际足联携手Stats Perform获取博彩数据及世界杯直播权]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际足联宣布，已选定体育人工智能公司Stats Perform作为其首个官方博彩数据及博彩流媒体版权分销商，该合作涵盖2026年世界杯所有赛事的直播流媒体服务。【原文：FIFA has selected sports AI firm Stats Perform as their first official betting data and betting streaming rights distributor, which includes live streams for all matches at the 2026 World Cup, world soccer's governing body said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/fifa-taps-stats-perform-betting-data-live-streaming-rights-ahead-world-cup-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VLEB727BYJMQLEDUTO5WJU4DFQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 03:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管遭到特朗普斥责，埃克森美孚仍有意访问委内瑞拉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位熟悉埃克森美孚公司战略的消息人士周一告诉路透社，该公司仍有意访问委内瑞拉，并准备派遣评估团队前往该国。此前一天，美国总统特朗普表示可能禁止这家石油公司进入委内瑞拉。【原文：Exxon Mobil remains interested in visiting Venezuela and is prepared to send an assessment team there, a source familiar with the company's strategy told Reuters on Monday, a day after U.S. President Donald Trump said he might keep the oil company out of the country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/exxon-mobil-still-interested-venezuela-visit-despite-trump-rebuke-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W5ZDPQQXZBID7MDTAAGCIMMVLE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达表示其H200芯片无需预付费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达发言人周二向路透社发表声明称，该公司不要求客户预付H200芯片的货款。【原文：Nvidia does not require upfront payment for H200 chips, a spokesperson for the U.S. chipmaker said in a statement to Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/nvidia-says-no-upfront-payment-needed-its-h200-chips-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF7F7WJC4NJKXACQEFS7TASE4A</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市攀升 日经指数创历史新高 企业财报季临近]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，日本股市强劲上涨带动亚洲股市走高，投资者对人工智能相关板块普遍持乐观态度。与此同时，美联储独立性面临的不确定性阴云虽令美元承压，却利好黄金走势。【原文：A surge in Japanese shares led Asia higher on Tuesday amid investor bullishness over all things AI, while the cloud of uncertainty over Federal Reserve independence favoured gold even as it weighed on the dollar.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-global-markets-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FI574EQHFRK4NFIGZ44KCZKBA4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 02:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油价因伊朗供应中断担忧而上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二油价小幅走高，因市场对伊朗局势及潜在供应中断的担忧加剧，抵消了委内瑞拉原油供应可能增加的预期。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Tuesday, as heightened concerns surrounding Iran and potential supply disruptions outweighed the prospect of increased crude supply from Venezuela.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-gain-iran-supply-disruption-concerns-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGKT3ABHLFJPTODEIJC2H2AIGI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元汇率波动，因市场担忧美联储独立性面临威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二美元延续跌势，此前特朗普政府对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔启动刑事调查，此举威胁到美联储的独立性及市场对美国资产的信心。【原文：The dollar held to its losses on Tuesday after the Trump administration opened a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell, a move that threatens the central bank's independence and faith in U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/dollar-wobbles-markets-fret-about-threat-fed-independence-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCHXFKEPL5JK7CZED6YWSFJJTM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[默克公司表示，新的增长机遇将推动其收入在2030年代中期达到700亿美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[默克公司周一表示，已上调对新增长引擎的预期，预计到2030年代中期这些新兴业务将带来700亿美元收入。随着其重磅抗癌药物Keytruda面临日益激烈的市场竞争，该公司正加速推出更多新药。【原文：Merck said on Monday it has raised its outlook for new growth drivers, forecasting $70 billion in revenue from these fresh businesses by the mid-2030s, as it accelerates the launch of additional drugs ahead of looming competition to its blockbuster cancer therapy Keytruda.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merck-says-new-growth-opportunities-drive-revenue-70-billion-by-mid-2030s-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YPBSL5RPMVMSXDRWYVG5CR7I5U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SK海力士将在韩国投资近130亿美元建设芯片封装工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国SK海力士周二宣布，决定投资19万亿韩元（约合129亿美元）在韩国本土建设一座先进芯片封装工厂，以满足人工智能相关领域不断增长的存储芯片需求。【原文：South Korea's SK Hynix said on Tuesday it has decided to invest 19 trillion won ($12.90 billion) to build an advanced chip packaging plant in South Korea to meet rising memory chip demand related to artificial intelligence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sk-hynix-invest-nearly-13-bln-chip-packaging-plant-south-korea-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JXSPBY3NXVLSFGIU4OBUVBR7GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称微软将采取措施降低美国数据中心电力成本]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一表示，微软公司本周将进行"重大调整"，以确保美国消费者不会因数据中心的电力消耗而支付更高电费。特朗普政府正与其他科技公司就高额公用事业账单问题展开合作。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Monday that Microsoft will make "major changes" this week to ensure U.S. consumers do not pay more for electricity because of data centers' power consumption, and his administration was working with other technology companies on the issue of high utility bills.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-microsoft-make-changes-curb-data-center-power-costs-americans-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JUX2QR6TKBK6JC3EHYMD6QFDOA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:23:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[维京公司首席执行官称，减肥优惠的吸引力远超表面所见]]></title><description><![CDATA[减肥药开发商维京治疗公司首席执行官周一表示，制药商对减肥药交易的战略兴趣比表面看起来更广泛，因为他们正试图开拓这个潜在规模达1500亿美元的市场。【原文：Weight-loss drug developer Viking Therapeutics CEO said on Monday that strategic interest in weight-loss drug deals is broader than it appears, as drugmakers seek to tap into the potential $150 billion market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/appetite-weight-loss-deals-broader-than-visible-viking-ceo-says-2026-01-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VQRVVPQKKNNU7FBZHBRUF3PFDE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:19:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[艾伯维与美国达成协议，将削减药品价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯维公司周一宣布，已与美国总统特朗普政府达成三年协议，通过特朗普处方药计划为医疗补助项目提供低价药品，并承诺未来十年在美国投入1000亿美元用于研发。【原文：Abbvie reached a three-year agreement with U.S. President Donald Trump's administration to provide low prices in Medicaid through TrumpRx, and pledged $100 billion over the next decade for research and development in the U.S., the company said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/abbvie-us-reach-agreement-cut-drug-prices-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2FGYINATOJMTVPR4DDIVSOJFNI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞首席执行官计划开发针对肥胖症的药物，其消费市场有望如伟哥般蓬勃发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[辉瑞公司首席执行官阿尔伯特·博拉周一表示，该公司正为肥胖症药物开拓消费市场做准备，其规模将与1998年推出勃起功能障碍药物伟哥后出现的蓬勃业务相当。【原文：Pfizer is preparing for a consumer market for obesity drugs on par with the booming business it saw after it launched erectile dysfunction drug Viagra in 1998, CEO Albert Bourla said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pfizer-ceo-plans-soaring-consumer-market-obesity-drugs-akin-viagra-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DIUVPK3OW5OZRETSKCEGVPD5PQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:43:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司因收购机器人公司损失10亿美元，特拉华州最高法院裁定减损]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司成功说服特拉华州最高法院撤销了部分10亿美元的损害赔偿判决，该判决源于其违反2019年收购外科手术机器人制造商奥瑞斯健康公司的协议。【原文：Johnson & Johnson convinced Delaware's highest court to throw out part of a $1 billion damages award for breaching its 2019 agreement to buy Auris Health, a maker of surgical robots.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/johnson-johnsons-1-billion-loss-robotics-takeover-reduced-by-delaware-top-court-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7R3CSTIRU5JYTPLWCRIROZWCUU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:32:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国敦促合作伙伴和盟友增强关键矿物供应链的韧性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部表示，财政部长斯科特·贝森特周一与美国多个伙伴国和盟国的部长举行会议，敦促这些国家增强其供应链韧性。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent held a meeting on Monday with ministers from different U.S. partners and allies, urging those nations to increase their supply chain resiliency, the Treasury Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-urges-partners-allies-increase-critical-minerals-supply-chain-resiliency-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KQWXVBWZ7BKAPEFTCQ35L266FY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:09:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰选定美国关联投资者开发多布拉锂矿床]]></title><description><![CDATA[基辅周一宣布，一家与美国有关联的投资集团赢得了开发乌克兰多布拉锂矿的权利。此举既是吸引西方资本进入前沿经济的试金石，也是乌克兰深化与华盛顿关系的举措。【原文：A U.S.-linked investor group won the rights to develop Ukraine’s Dobra lithium deposit, Kyiv said on Monday, a test case for drawing Western capital into a frontline economy while trying to deepen ties with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraine-picks-us-linked-investors-develop-dobra-lithium-deposit-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZCB5INX43FIXPI63YKGIFVEF44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储威廉姆斯称货币政策在良好前景下定位得当]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行行长约翰·威廉姆斯周一表示，他预计2026年经济将保持健康，并暗示近期没有降息的理由。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams said Monday he expects a healthy economy in ​2026 and indicated he sees no near-term reason to cut interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/feds-williams-says-monetary-policy-well-positioned-amid-favorable-outlook-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5J4HF6CBT5LFNF3WT7XX4WTABY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车首席执行官表示，尽管行业出现回调，电动汽车仍是"最终目标"]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车首席执行官玛丽·巴拉表示，特朗普政府推动放宽燃油经济性法规的举措，对该汽车制造商业务的影响甚至超过其快速变化的贸易政策。【原文：General Motors CEO Mary Barra said the Trump administration’s push to loosen fuel-economy rules has affected the automaker’s business even more than its fast-changing trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-ceo-says-evs-still-end-game-despite-industry-pullback-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQQC3IFDB5M4DKJ6PAQGYTKKDQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚莱纳斯稀土公司首席执行官即将退休]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚莱纳斯稀土公司周二宣布，其首席执行官兼董事总经理阿曼达·拉卡兹在执掌公司12年后即将退休。【原文：Australia's Lynas Rare Earths said on Tuesday its chief executive officer and managing director, Amanda Lacaze, was retiring after 12 years at the helm.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australias-lynas-rare-earths-ceo-retire-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HORVKXDOJBMERFNPYKJPLXCREQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力旗下公司赢得美国海军9.88亿美元合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司周一宣布，其信息技术部门已获得一份价值9.88亿美元的合同，用于现代化改造美国海军舰队系统。【原文：General Dynamics said on Monday that its information technology unit has secured a $988 million contract to modernize the U.S. Navy's fleet systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-unit-wins-988-million-us-navy-contract-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BQJYIZTYZNINVNY5WVRIUJ5GGQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[惠誉评级称美联储独立性是美国主权评级的关键因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[惠誉评级周一表示，美联储的独立性是支撑其对美国AA+主权评级的关键因素。【原文：Fitch Ratings said on Monday it views the Federal Reserve's ​independence as a key supporting factor for its AA+ ‌U.S. sovereign rating.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fitch-ratings-says-fed-independence-is-key-factor-us-sovereign-rating-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2S7POSEIRBNYLI3CILIBVUTYRA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:28:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：特朗普跨越美联储卢比孔河，市场不以为意]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，投资者对特朗普政府威胁要对美联储主席杰罗姆·鲍威尔提起刑事指控的重大新闻置之不理，推动标普500指数创下历史新高，贵金属价格也飙升至新高峰。【原文：Investors on Monday brushed aside the dramatic news of the Trump administration's threat to criminally indict Fed Chair Jerome Powell, lifting the S&amp;P 500 to an all-time high, while precious metals also soared to new peaks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MJZJQPFUZOFVHXGGKJ7RJ2B44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称与伊朗有贸易往来的国家将面临25%的美国关税]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德·特朗普周一表示，任何与伊朗有贸易往来的国家，其对美出口商品都将面临25%的关税税率。此举正值华盛顿权衡如何应对伊朗局势之际——该国正经历数年来规模最大的反政府抗议活动。【原文：President Donald Trump said on Monday any country that does business with Iran will face a tariff rate of 25% on any trade with the U.S., as Washington weighs a response to the situation in Iran which is seeing its biggest anti-government protests in years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/trump-says-countries-doing-business-with-iran-face-25-tariff-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTB7XP2MBVIIZMTEUIGCP2RLFA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国撤销明确禁止对移民贷款歧视的政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国消费者金融保护局和司法部周一撤销了明确禁止贷款机构歧视移民和非公民的指导方针，此举可能削弱移民获取贷款的法律保障。【原文：The U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau and ​the Department of Justice withdrew guidance expressly prohibiting lenders from discriminating against immigrants and ‌non-citizens on Monday, potentially denting immigrants' legal ability to access loans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-withdraws-policy-expressly-barring-lending-bias-against-immigrants-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYOWB7M6KZOHRMKCUGJ2M6UH4Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:45:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西反垄断机构对WhatsApp商业工具展开调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西反垄断机构CADE周一表示，已就Meta旗下WhatsApp Business工具的新条款展开调查，并将在评估期间暂停该工具在巴西的新条款实施。【原文：Brazilian antitrust body CADE said on Monday it had opened an investigation into the new terms of Meta's WhatsApp Business tool, adding it would also suspend the tool's new terms in Brazil while it evaluates the case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/brazils-antitrust-body-opens-investigation-into-whatsapp-business-tool-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRFZC2L76JIENEH447ZWSVJAEE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》报道，Meta计划裁减Reality Labs部门约10%的员工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《纽约时报》周一报道，知情人士透露，Meta计划裁减其Reality Labs部门约10%的员工，该部门负责包括元宇宙在内的产品开发。【原文：Meta plans to cut around 10% of the employees in its Reality Labs division who work on products including the metaverse, the New York Times reported on Monday, citing three people with knowledge of the discussions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-plans-cut-around-10-employees-reality-labs-division-nyt-reports-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UBXC2ASDBZLFNEWTAGXW4WFFRE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行警告称，特朗普对信用卡利率设定的10%上限将损害消费者利益]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国银行和金融机构周一反对特朗普总统提出的信用卡利率上限提案，援引新数据显示该政策将导致数百万美国家庭和小企业丧失信贷渠道。【原文：U.S. banks and financial institutions on Monday pushed back against President Donald ‌Trump's proposed cap on credit card interest rates, citing new data that showed it would result in millions of American households and small businesses losing access to credit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/banks-warn-consumers-will-be-hurt-by-trumps-10-cap-credit-card-interest-rates-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RYEJYPWPTFJYBLMIKPIJJISN6I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官裁定奥斯特德公司可继续推进罗德岛海上风电项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周一裁定，允许丹麦海上风电开发商奥斯特德公司重启其即将完工的"革命风电"项目。该项目与另外四个项目上月被美国总统特朗普政府叫停。【原文：A federal judge on Monday cleared Danish offshore wind developer Orsted to resume work on its nearly finished Revolution Wind project, which U.S. President Donald Trump's administration halted along with four other projects last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-judge-rules-orsted-can-continue-work-rhode-island-offshore-wind-project-2026-01-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3UUWO2SWRJICJCYPLPCYXAW2LE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>