<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:44:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:44:43 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[KKR 和葡萄牙的 Quadrantis 将收购复星旗下峰值再保险的少数股权]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球投资公司 KKR 和葡萄牙私募股权公司 Quadrantis Capital 周二表示，将收购复星国际控股的匹克再保险公司的少数股权。【原文：Global investment firm KKR and Portuguese private equity firm Quadrantis Capital will acquire a minority stake in Fosun International majority-owned Peak Reinsurance Company, the parties said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kkr-portugals-quadrantis-buy-minority-stake-fosun-owned-peak-reinsurance-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBRLGL5BLJO3BPRR4D5JCAROAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:17:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势缓解，亚洲股市大涨，日经指数创纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，亚洲股市上涨，原因是世界前两大经济体之间的贸易紧张局势有望缓解，这提振了风险情绪，而真荣孝一成为日本下任首相的几近确定性使日经指数创下历史新高。【原文：Asian stocks rose on Tuesday as the prospect of easing trade tensions between the world's top two economies boosted risk sentiment, while the near-certainty of Sanae Takaichi becoming Japan's next prime minister sent the Nikkei to a record high.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3YWL45SWNBNCLD5HO3GQKZOSFM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印尼电信将在 21.6 亿美元的交易中分拆光纤连接批发业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度尼西亚电信公司（Telkom Indonesia）周二同意将其光纤连接批发业务部分分拆给子公司印度尼西亚电信基础设施公司（Telkom Infrastruktur Indonesia），交易价值为 35.787 万亿印尼盾（合 21.6 亿美元）。【原文：Telkom Indonesia agreed on Tuesday to partially spin off its wholesale fibre connectivity business to its subsidiary Telkom Infrastruktur Indonesia in a deal valued at 35.787 trillion rupiah ($2.16 billion).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/telkom-indonesia-spin-off-wholesale-fibre-connectivity-business-216-billion-deal-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2GSLEQABJRIP5HDBGYGVTAM4RA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元在议会投票选举下任首相前保持警惕]]></title><description><![CDATA[在日本国会当天晚些时候举行投票之前，日元周二持稳，这次投票几乎肯定会使强硬保守派的高市真奈成为日本首位女首相。【原文：The yen held steady on Tuesday, ahead of a parliament vote in Japan later in the day that is almost certain to see hardline conservative Sanae Takaichi become the country's first female prime minister.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-guard-ahead-parliament-vote-next-prime-minister-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UGI63R5U75K2RH5DHBKREWI4PE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:07:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[石油因供应过剩担忧而下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）表示他预计将达成一项贸易协议，但由于担心供应过剩以及全球两大石油消费国美国和中国之间的紧张局势对需求造成的风险，周二油价下跌。【原文：Oil prices fell on Tuesday on concerns about excess supply and risks to demand stemming from tensions between the U.S. and China, the world's top two oil consumers, even as President Donald Trump said he expected to reach a trade deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-declines-oversupply-fears-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFF2WUCQBJNKBG6SAQHSLZU5HE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国寄希望于澳大利亚矿商打破中国对关键矿产供应的控制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普和澳大利亚总理安东尼-阿尔巴内斯周一就确保关键矿物和稀土的稳定供应达成一致，因为美国正采取行动减少对中国供应的依赖。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump and Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese agreed on Monday to ensure a steady supply of critical minerals and rare earths, as the United States moves to reduce its reliance on Chinese supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-bets-australian-miners-break-chinas-grip-critical-minerals-supply-2025-10-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VXPGUHW4ZBMKRP5NAAAOB3KHQI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和澳大利亚将在关键矿产领域投资 20 亿美元，推进美国铝业公司的镓项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为周一签署的一项范围广泛的关键矿产协议的一部分，美国和澳大利亚向几家澳大利亚公司提供了财政支持，旨在对抗中国对该行业的控制。【原文：The United States and Australia have extended financial support to several Australian companies as part of a wide-ranging critical minerals agreement signed on Monday with an aim of countering China's hold over the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-australia-invest-2-billion-critical-minerals-advance-alcoa-gallium-project-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXVOG6XZ4VMOLMQ7JSLUW2MCNU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国银行正在寻找抵押品，以支持 200 亿美元的阿根廷救助计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周一报道，包括摩根大通、美国银行和高盛在内的一批美国银行对在没有担保或抵押的情况下向阿根廷贷款 200 亿美元犹豫不决。【原文：A group of U.S. banks, including JPMorgan Chase , Bank of America and Goldman Sachs , is hesitant to lend $20 billion to Argentina without guarantees or collateral, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-banks-hunting-collateral-back-20-billion-argentina-bailout-wsj-reports-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBJGGJGQYZJONHAZINQ7EF4D5E</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[飞利浦 66 和金德摩根希望新建输油管道，以加强美国西海岸的燃料供应]]></title><description><![CDATA[菲利普斯 66 和金德摩根公司周一开始为拟议中的输油管道系统征集托运人承诺，该系统将从得克萨斯州的炼油中心输送燃料，以加强亚利桑那州和加利福尼亚州的供应，因为炼油厂的接连关闭加剧了对供应的担忧。【原文：Phillips 66 and Kinder Morgan on Monday began soliciting shipper commitments for a proposed pipeline system that will move fuel from the Texas refining hub to bolster supplies in Arizona and California as a spate of refinery closures stokes supply concerns.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/phillips-66-kinder-morgan-eye-new-pipeline-bolster-us-west-coast-fuel-supply-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4GZ4XKOBFJLVBEA6DCWKRI4YXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:17:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[文件显示，Venture Global 准备将天然气引入 Plaquemines 液化天然气工厂的最后部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据周一提交的一份监管文件，Venture Global 已请求联邦监管机构允许其在周四之前将天然气引入其 Plaquemines 液化天然气工厂的最后一个区块。【原文：Venture Global has asked federal regulators for permission to introduce natural gas by Thursday into the final block of its Plaquemines LNG plant, according to a regulatory filing on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/venture-global-ready-introduce-natural-gas-into-final-part-plaquemines-lng-plant-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RW5OKLHVORLJDHWLHOQGPZA3K4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:14:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片紧缩：人工智能热潮如何刺激不那么时髦的存储器价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内高管和分析师表示，全球芯片制造商争相生产人工智能芯片，导致智能手机、电脑和服务器中使用的不太起眼的芯片供应吃紧，刺激了一些客户的恐慌性购买，导致芯片价格飙升。【原文：The global rush by chipmakers to produce AI chips is tightening supply of less glamorous chips used in smartphones, computers and servers, spurring panic buying by some customers and a surge in their prices, industry executives and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chip-crunch-how-ai-boom-is-stoking-prices-less-trendy-memory-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ERAY635XPVJ3DNYOXDZ4CFRYQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[马士基测试巴西乙醇混合物，以生产更清洁的船用燃料]]></title><description><![CDATA[丹麦船运公司马士基（Maersk）周一宣布，该公司正在测试一种巴西乙醇与甲醇和船用柴油（即 "船用燃料"）的混合燃料，用于船舶发动机，这是该公司为进一步实现运营脱碳所做努力的一部分。【原文：Danish shipping company Maersk is testing a blend of Brazilian ethanol with methanol and marine diesel - known as "bunker" - for its vessel engines as part of its efforts to further decarbonize operations, the company announced on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/maersk-tests-brazilian-ethanol-mix-make-cleaner-maritime-fuel-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZF2BPSFIHZIWTATCSEJG67G2OU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦住房与金融管理局（FHFA）局长称，特朗普政府正在权衡房利美和房地美最快于 2025 年底上市的可能性]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦住房金融局局长威廉-普尔特（William Pulte）周一表示，美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的政府正在 "择机评估 "房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）的公开发行，最早可能在2025年底。
"普尔特在 X 上说："特朗普总统做出了正确的决定，在他的第一个任期内没有让房地美和房利美上市，这次他正在择机评估上市事宜，最早可能在 2025 年底。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is "opportunistically evaluating" a public offering for Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, possibly as soon as end-2025, Federal Housing Finance Agency Director William Pulte said on Monday.
"President Trump made the right decision not to take Freddie and Fannie public during his first term and is opportunistically evaluating an offering this time around, which could be as early as the end of 2025," Pulte said on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-administration-weighing-fannie-freddie-offering-soon-end-2025-fhfa-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">26VHGJ7A7VJNVAO2GUNFODKZWM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:27:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[必和必拓铁矿石产量因维修工程影响而低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，必和必拓集团（BHP Group）第一季度铁矿石产量略低于预期，原因是计划中的维护（包括重建黑德兰港的一台设备）影响了西澳大利亚业务的生产。【原文：BHP Group's first-quarter iron ore output came in a little lower than estimates on Tuesday, as planned maintenance, including rebuilding of a piece of equipment at Port Hedland, weighed on production at its Western Australian operations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/bhps-first-quarter-iron-ore-output-falls-near-2-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5QZOZI3RKZNGRMWWXWVUKS77SI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ISS 建议投资者拒绝 CoreWeave 收购 Core Scientific 的交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[代理咨询公司机构股东服务公司（Institutional Shareholder Services）周一建议投资者投票否决人工智能公司 CoreWeave 收购基础设施公司 Core Scientific 的计划，该交易号称价值 90 亿美元。【原文：Proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services on Monday recommended investors vote down plans for AI company CoreWeave to buy infrastructure company Core Scientific in what was billed as a $9 billion deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/iss-recommends-investors-reject-coreweave-deal-core-scientific-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKYZH54UTNJ2BJRWJXEJ3U4WVA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[W.R. Berkley 第三季度利润因投资收益和稳定的承保而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[商业保险公司 W. R. Berkley 周一公布，受强劲的投资收益和稳定的承保业绩提振，第三季度利润有所增长。【原文：Commercial insurer W. R. Berkley reported a rise in third-quarter profit on Monday, boosted by robust investment gains and steady underwriting performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wr-berkley-third-quarter-profit-rises-investment-gains-steady-underwriting-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PUMHKI6DRVJHFNXTLSNY2XZNAU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普进口阿根廷牛肉的计划激怒了美国农民]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国农民周一批评了唐纳德-特朗普总统关于美国可能从阿根廷进口更多牛肉的建议，因为他们最近在向头号买家中国销售大豆方面输给了这个南美国家。【原文：U.S. farmers on Monday criticized President Donald Trump's suggestion that the country may import more beef from Argentina, after they recently lost out to the South American nation on soybean sales to top buyer China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-plan-import-argentine-beef-angers-us-farmers-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2HJLK25D6NIKLBOPJB2FINOJEI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：又一波 "逢低买入]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街和全球大多数股票基准指数周一大幅上涨，原因是对美国财报的乐观情绪和全球贸易紧张局势的缓和抵消了上周对泡沫资产价格、私人信贷市场和美国地区银行的部分担忧。【原文：Wall Street and most global equity benchmarks rose sharply on Monday, as optimism around U.S. earnings and easing global trade tensions offset some of last week's worries over frothy asset prices, private credit markets and U.S. regional banks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N3Y7DVX2SFM27ILLYYOHBVEEBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用动力公司从德国获得 35 亿美元侦察车合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用动力公司（General Dynamics）周一表示，其欧洲分部已获得一份价值约 30 亿欧元（35.0 亿美元）的合同，将为德国陆军侦察队提供下一代侦察车。【原文：General Dynamics said on Monday that its Europe unit has secured a contract for about 3 billion euros ($3.50 billion) to deliver next-generation reconnaissance vehicle for the German Army Reconnaissance Corps.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/general-dynamics-gets-35-billion-scout-vehicle-contract-germany-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KGVBT2SN4BNZ3FWXDQMEIEJM7Y</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zions Bancorp 季度利润因利息收入抵消贷款损失而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zions Bancorp 周一公布，尽管在两笔贷款上出现了巨额亏损，但在利息收入增加的帮助下，该银行第三季度利润仍有所增长，这使得该银行股价在盘后交易中上涨了 2.5%。【原文：Zions Bancorp reported a rise in third-quarter profit on Monday, helped by stronger income from interest, despite taking a hefty loss on two loans, sending shares of the bank up 2.5% in after-market trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/zions-bancorps-quarterly-profit-rises-interest-income-offsets-loan-loss-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWM57OLE3JOSZNEAJMZM5RVXAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:24:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在紧张局势持续之际，Impactive 挑选董事加入 WEX 董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[激进投资者 Impactive Capital 挑选了几位在银行业和支付领域有经验的董事候选人进入金融科技公司 WEX 董事会，这表明该公司打算继续推进计划中的代理权争夺战。【原文：Activist investor Impactive Capital has selected a handful of director candidates with experience in banking and payments to serve on financial technology company WEX's board, signaling its intent to push ahead with a planned proxy fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/impactive-picks-directors-sit-wex-board-amid-ongoing-tensions-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FWJQDPYJP5NYLFVBLMGESAAAEM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[代理公司 Glass Lewis 与 ISS 联合呼吁投票反对马斯克 1 万亿美元的薪酬方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[代理公司 Glass Lewis 建议特斯拉股东投票反对首席执行官埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）拟议的 1 万亿美元薪酬计划，几天前，ISS 也敦促投资者否决可能是有史以来授予公司首席执行官的最大薪酬计划。【原文：Proxy firm Glass Lewis has recommended that Tesla shareholders vote against the proposed $1 trillion pay package for CEO Elon Musk, days after ISS also urged investors to reject what might be the largest-ever compensation plan awarded to a company chief.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/proxy-firm-glass-lewis-joins-iss-urging-vote-against-musks-1-trillion-pay-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TDH5GIXNVJKFPBFJQZRUEHD2XM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[佛罗里达州总检察长就儿童安全问题向 Roblox 发出传票]]></title><description><![CDATA[佛罗里达州共和党总检察长詹姆斯-乌斯迈尔（James Uthmeier）说，他的办公室正在向 Roblox 公司发出刑事传票，称该视频游戏平台是 "掠夺者的温床"，会给儿童带来危险。【原文：Republican Florida Attorney General James Uthmeier said his office is issuing criminal subpoenas to Roblox Corp , calling the video gaming platform a "breeding ground for predators" that puts children at risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/florida-attorney-general-issues-subpoenas-roblox-over-child-safety-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IYTDOP4QYBK6ZM5KGARJ6Z6B2U</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国商业游说团敦促特朗普终止对华出口新限制措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个董事会成员包括甲骨文公司、亚马逊公司和埃克森美孚公司等美国公司的游说团体正在敦促特朗普政府立即中止一项规定，该团体称这项规定导致价值数十亿美元的美国出口中断，并将促使中国和其他国家将美国公司从其供应链中剔除。【原文：A lobbying group whose board includes U.S. firms like Oracle , Amazon.com and Exxon Mobil is urging the Trump administration to immediately suspend a rule it says halted billions of dollars' worth of U.S. exports and will prompt China and other countries to drop U.S. firms from their supply chains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/us-business-lobby-urges-trump-axe-new-curbs-exports-china-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4KF7NEICG5L2XDXIN32JLGLFFA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:21:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix的广告和游戏赌注成为焦点，投资者寻求明确的回报率]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 今年的股市涨幅高达 1200 亿美元，本周二它将面临一个关键的考验：证明其在广告和视频游戏领域的高成本投资能够支持增长，而正是这种增长让这家流媒体先驱成为华尔街的宠儿。【原文：Netflix's $120 billion stock market rally this year faces a crucial test on Tuesday: proving that its costly investments into advertising and video gaming can support the growth that made the streaming pioneer a Wall Street darling.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflixs-ad-gaming-bets-focus-investors-seek-clarity-pay-off-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHLTNYTPEVKULLCEV4CVO2ZMUI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:58:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行动迅速的 de Meo 如何与欧莱雅达成交易，缓解开云集团的压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kering 新任首席执行官卢卡-德-梅奥（Luca de Meo）很快就崭露头角。【原文：Kering's new CEO Luca de Meo didn’t take long to make his mark.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/how-fast-moving-de-meo-secured-loreal-deal-ease-kerings-strain-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GDTASKONXFN2JISOWQ4YBLGYB4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:52:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊云计算故障：在线服务受到冲击，恢复情况参差不齐]]></title><description><![CDATA[周一，亚马逊云计算部门的故障逐渐缓解，此前，银行、社交媒体公司和企业提供的许多在线服务都受到了干扰。【原文：An outage at Amazon's cloud computing unit was gradually easing on Monday, after disrupting many online services offered by banks, social media companies and businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/amazon-cloud-outage-online-services-hit-recovery-uneven-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2BMTUGDNZJC5ICRZR2SW4TYZE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:48:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大对来自美国和中国的部分钢铁和铝产品实行关税减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[一份政府文件显示，加拿大对从美国和中国进口的部分钢铁和铝产品提供了关税减免，以帮助受到贸易战两面夹击的国内企业。【原文：Canada offered tariff relief on some steel and aluminum products imported from the U.S. and China, a government document showed, in efforts to help domestic businesses battered by a trade war on two fronts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/canada-offers-tariff-relief-some-steel-aluminum-products-us-china-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CI5DSUEYMZNVBBW633PPYRCOIU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法国阿托斯公司销售额下滑，目标从 2026 年开始并购]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国 IT 集团 Atos 周一报告称，由于关键合同损失，该公司季度收入大幅下降，并表示从 2026 年起将仅以收购为目标。【原文：French IT group Atos reported a sharp drop in quarterly revenue on Monday, owing to key contract losses, and said it would only target acquisitions from 2026.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/frances-atos-posts-sales-dip-targets-ma-2026-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OCKRDRSDEJL3PHA7WCWFRFDZJM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:12:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克罗格公司将在 2025 年假日季招聘 1.8 万名员工，比去年减少]]></title><description><![CDATA[克罗格（Kroger）周一表示，随着美国食品杂货商为繁忙的假日季节做准备，其旗下公司正寻求招聘 18,000 多名员工，比去年减少约 7,000 人。【原文：Kroger said on Monday its family of companies are looking to hire over 18,000 associates as the U.S. grocer preps for the busy holiday season, about 7,000 fewer than last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/world-at-work/kroger-hire-18000-workers-2025-holiday-season-fewer-than-last-year-2025-10-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CX3AZPOIMFLAXDC3PAGKRODKAU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>