<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 11:08:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 11:07:59 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[国际商业机器公司（IBM）和思科公司概述了到 2030 年代初的量子计算机网络计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际商业机器公司（IBM）和思科系统公司（Cisco Systems）周四表示，他们计划长距离连接量子计算机，目标是在 2030 年底之前证明这一概念是可行的。【原文：IBM and Cisco Systems on Thursday said they plan to link quantum computers over long distances, with the goal of demonstrating the concept is workable by the end of 2030.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/ibm-cisco-outline-plans-networks-quantum-computers-by-early-2030s-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NWKZRPBZT5KFNMSOI4MJAZUXHU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 11:03:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[印度中央银行行长：对加密货币和稳定币持谨慎态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度储备银行行长周四表示，印度央行对加密货币和稳定币采取谨慎态度。【原文：India's central bank is adopting a cautious approach towards cryptocurrencies and stablecoins, the Reserve Bank of India governor said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/being-cautious-about-cryptocurrencies-stablecoins-india-cenbank-chief-says-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIX5DQOPXBKYBHJ6TPAEFOMUDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:38:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，KKR 旨在为新亚洲私募股权基金融资 150 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士透露，全球私募股权投资公司 KKR & Co 已启动其第五只亚洲私募股权投资基金的募资工作，寻求筹集 150 亿美元的资金，这将是该地区迄今为止规模最大的募资活动之一。【原文：Global private equity firm KKR & Co has kicked off fundraising for its fifth Asia private equity fund, seeking to raise $15 billion in what would be one of the region's largest fund raisings to date, three people with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/kkr-aims-raise-15-billion-new-asia-private-equity-fund-sources-say-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L2OTUIIWQRPGVMLHZG7D4DOYQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国告诉美国，希腊比雷埃夫斯港不出售]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国驻希腊大使馆表示，中国在希腊比雷埃夫斯港（欧洲最大港口之一）的控股权是非卖品，并谴责了新任命的美国驻希腊大使金伯利-安-吉尔弗约尔（Kimberly Ann Guilfoyle）的言论。【原文：China's controlling stake in the Greek port of Piraeus, one of the largest in Europe, is not for sale, the Chinese embassy in Greece said, denouncing comments by newly appointed U.S. ambassador to Greece Kimberly Ann Guilfoyle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/greeces-piraeus-port-not-sale-china-tells-us-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4MAT2E6BCJKNBJGGXHVA7QVD6Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:54:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩缓解人工智能泡沫担忧，美股期货跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达（Nvidia）的出色业绩平息了人们对人工智能泡沫的担忧，提振了科技股，而人们期待已久的就业报告也成为关注焦点。【原文：U.S. stock index futures jumped on Thursday after Nvidia's stellar results quelled some concerns around an AI bubble, boosting technology stocks, while a long-awaited jobs report was also in focus.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-stock-futures-jump-nvidia-results-ease-ai-bubble-concerns-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4WRMMDK5XFJXVCLBPZWX7KV5YE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西班牙法院命令 Meta 向数字媒体公司支付 5.5 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙法院以不正当竞争行为和违反欧盟数据保护法规为由，下令跨国科技公司 Meta 向西班牙数字媒体支付 4.79 亿欧元（5.52 亿美元）。【原文：A Spanish court has ordered that the multinational tech company Meta pay 479 million euros ($552 million) to Spanish digital media outlets for unfair competition practices and infringement of EU data protection regulation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/spanish-court-orders-meta-pay-550-mln-digital-media-companies-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RCEG2NMJQNISRGKSF5P6X2D7S4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Auterion 称莱茵金属入股将促进无人机软件集团的发展]]></title><description><![CDATA[Auterion 首席执行官洛伦茨-迈尔（Lorenz Meier）说，德国国防企业莱茵金属公司（Rheinmetall）成为这家美国无人机软件公司的 "重要 "股东，将有助于该公司增加订单量，但他补充说，这不会导致全面收购。【原文：Auterion CEO Lorenz Meier said having German defence player Rheinmetall on board as a "significant" shareholder in the U.S.-based drone software firm would help it grow its order book, adding that it would not lead to a full takeover.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/auterion-says-rheinmetall-stake-boost-drone-software-groups-growth-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DBXAZC4GDVLQNBFIF5MEWXD3FU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[台湾检方就芯片安全问题调查前台积电高管]]></title><description><![CDATA[台湾经济部长周三表示，台湾正在调查一名最近加入英特尔的台积电退休高管，因为当地媒体报道称他可能把这家芯片制造商的先进技术数据带到了新雇主那里。【原文：Taiwan is investigating a retired TSMC executive who recently joined Intel , the island's economy minister said on Wednesday, after local media reported that he may have taken the chipmaker's advanced technology data to his new employer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-prosecutors-investigate-ex-tsmc-executive-chip-security-concerns-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7PVGGUGIBPLBL5Y3LO7ZPRPCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:57:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，印度国内经济复苏为美国贸易协议谈判提供了空间]]></title><description><![CDATA[印度消息人士和分析师说，印度国内经济强劲，出口受到的打击小于预期，这为新德里与华盛顿谈判贸易协议提供了更多空间。【原文：India’s strong domestic economy and a smaller-than-expected hit to exports are giving New Delhi more room to negotiate a trade deal with Washington, which has imposed tariffs as high as 50% on imports from the country, Indian sources and analysts said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/resilient-domestic-economy-gives-india-space-negotiate-us-trade-deal-sources-say-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HADAQJRQW5KRXMEAPLRCDOZSB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国数据中心需求强劲，Halma上调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国健康与安全设备制造商哈尔玛公司周四上调了全年收入增长预期，此前该公司报告称，由于美国对其用于数据中心建设的光电子产品需求强劲，半年利润大幅增长。【原文：British health and safety device maker Halma raised its annual revenue growth forecast on Thursday after reporting a surge in half-year profit, fuelled by strong U.S. demand for its photonics products used in data centre construction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/halma-lifts-annual-revenue-forecast-strong-us-data-centre-demand-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XUWS5PSDIZKJFIZ74F66SZNUTU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:22:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[起亚美国公司因油箱泄漏召回逾25万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration）周四表示，起亚美国公司（Kia America）将在美国召回250,547辆K5汽车，原因是这些汽车的油箱损坏，存在起火风险。【原文：Kia America is recalling 250,547 K5 vehicles in the U.S. over a damaged fuel tank posing a fire risk, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/kia-america-recall-over-250000-us-vehicles-over-fuel-tank-leak-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EFDSV4BPTZJWRIEPP7DSUQTFXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美洲销售额增长，靴子制造商马腾博士减少上半年亏损]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国靴子制造商马腾斯博士周四公布上半年亏损收窄，主要是受美洲销售额增长的支撑，并维持了2026财年的业绩预期，尽管标明了美国关税的潜在影响。【原文：British bootmaker Dr Martens reported a narrower first-half loss on Thursday, primarily supported by higher sales in the Americas, and maintained its fiscal 2026 forecast despite flagging potential impact of U.S. tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/bootmaker-dr-martens-trims-first-half-loss-americas-sales-rise-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FR6BBDRZSJMPNOZYJ2GMHD44OQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 07:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[诺华主要抗癌药物带动销售增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士制药商诺华（Novartis）周四预计，经货币调整后，到2030年，该公司的销售额将每年增长5%至6%，原因是抗癌药物Kisqali和Scemblix的预计销售峰值较高，抵消了专利到期带来的损失。【原文：Swiss drugmaker Novartis on Thursday forecast sales growth of 5% to 6% per year to 2030, on a currency-adjusted basis, as higher forecast peak sales for cancer drugs Kisqali and Scemblix offset losses from expiring patents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novartis-targets-5-6-annual-sales-growth-until-2030-key-drugs-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CQILRF4BHJM2PODIL6WOKJETAE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 06:09:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间新闻英伟达缓解压力后，美国就业测试迫在眉睫]]></title><description><![CDATA[格雷戈尔-斯图尔特-亨特（Gregor Stuart Hunter）展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天：【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Gregor Stuart Hunter:】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-view-europe-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GELI27373ZPDVHRFUWWKS6LVTY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 05:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国经济可能在 9 月份以温和速度增加就业岗位]]></title><description><![CDATA[9 月份，美国就业增长可能温和回升，失业率则稳定在 4.3% 的四年高位附近，这与经济学家和政策制定者归咎于劳动力供需不足的劳动力市场低迷状况一致。【原文：U.S. job growth likely picked up moderately in September, while the unemployment rate held steady near a four-year high of 4.3%, consistent with sluggish labor market conditions that economists and policymakers have blamed on low supply and demand for workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-economy-likely-added-jobs-moderate-pace-september-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G4JG7VMMYBLEPC6UBA25ODDCD4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 05:04:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究显示，世界上最富有的国家正在退出全球发展努力]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四发表的一份研究报告显示，包括美国和日本在内的二十几个世界上最富有的国家正在从它们推动全球发展的行动中后撤，许多国家削减了援助预算和通过多边贷款机构提供的现金。【原文：Two dozen of the world's richest nations, including the United States and Japan, are pulling back from their global development push, a study published on Thursday shows, with many slashing aid budgets and cash funnelled through multilateral lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/climate-energy/worlds-richest-nations-are-pulling-back-global-development-efforts-study-show-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76T5VIH25VJSZLMK3MJL7AZZXI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 05:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[人工智能借贷狂潮促使投资者远离公司债券]]></title><description><![CDATA[科技巨额借贷和私人信贷紧张的迹象，使债券市场上的贷款人对全球评级最高的企业感到恐慌，这种趋势可能会推高融资成本，打击企业盈利，并给紧张的全球市场增添压力。【原文：A big tech borrowing bonanza and signs of strain in private credit are spooking bond market lenders to the world's top-rated businesses, in a trend that could jolt funding costs higher, hit corporate earnings and add stress to twitchy global markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-credit-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQT2LUT2IBNZVJL7AN7L62Z26Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 05:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行将于 12 月加息，但加息决定岌岌可危]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社的一项民意调查中，微弱多数的经济学家认为，日本央行将在即将到来的 12 月会议上提高利率，在日元近期下跌的支撑下，实现货币政策正常化的目标。【原文：The Bank of Japan will raise interest rates at its upcoming December meeting, according to a slim majority of economists in a Reuters poll, pushing through with its aim of normalising monetary policy, backed by the yen's recent decline.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/boj-set-hike-interest-rates-december-decision-knife-edge-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UDOE4AZRFVMSZBRTVLMQ52ZOXE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 04:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌在台湾成立新的人工智能工程中心]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司周四在台湾开设了美国以外最大的人工智能（AI）基础设施硬件工程中心，台湾总统称这是对台湾作为值得信赖的技术合作伙伴的信任。【原文：Alphabet's Google on Thursday opened in Taiwan its biggest artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure hardware engineering centre outside of the U.S., in what Taiwan's president said was a show of confidence in the island as a trustworthy technology partner.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/google-opens-new-ai-engineering-centre-taiwan-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BFVQA3G53FNR3OII4VCWLP2HR4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:51:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中金公司计划收购两家竞争对手，中资券商股价攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[在中国国际金融有限公司（中金公司）表示将收购两家竞争对手之后，中国券商股价周四上涨，这激起了人们对中国 1.6 万亿美元证券业进一步整合的预期。【原文：Shares in Chinese brokerages gained on Thursday after China International Capital Corp (CICC) said it would acquire two rivals, stoking expectations of further consolidation in the country's $1.6 trillion securities industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/shares-chinese-brokerages-climb-ciccs-plan-acquire-two-rivals-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNVF4GLJNFPEVGHJKVDF3U33I4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩亮眼带动科技股上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，科技公司股价在亚洲大涨，此前芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）的丰厚收益平息了投资者对人工智能泡沫的担忧，并为科技股带动的涨势注入了新的活力，推动全球股指在今年创下历史新高。【原文：Shares of technology companies surged in Asia on Thursday, after bumper earnings from chipmaker Nvidia quelled investor fears of an AI bubble and breathed new life into a tech-led rally that has propelled global stock indexes to record highs this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tech-shares-turbocharged-by-nvidias-stellar-earnings-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7GJPTYNJQVJXRK4IZ6DPPV54DU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[转折点还是泡沫？英伟达首席执行官看好人工智能变革，怀疑论者却在计算风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[英伟达公司首席执行官黄仁勋说，他没有看到人工智能泡沫，而是看到了一个转折点。【原文：Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang says he does not see an AI bubble, but rather a tipping point.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/tipping-point-or-bubble-nvidia-ceo-sees-ai-transformation-while-skeptics-count-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RUHIREA3RNOKBMZ2INTXJRPAYQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰任命史蒂夫-休斯（Steve Hughes）为行政总裁兼澳大利亚和新西兰银行业务主管]]></title><description><![CDATA[汇丰银行发言人周四表示，该行已任命史蒂夫-休斯（Steve Hughes）为澳大利亚和新西兰地区首席执行官兼银行业务主管，任期自 2026 年 1 月 1 日起。【原文：HSBC has appointed Steve Hughes as CEO and head of Banking for Australia and New Zealand, effective January 1, 2026, a company spokesperson said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/hsbc-appoints-steve-hughes-ceo-head-australia-new-zealand-banking-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BOGYQIX34BPCFAULLZO6GGXQYA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国连续两个月未进口美国大豆，巴西到货量增长 29]]></title><description><![CDATA[10 月份，中国连续第二个月没有从美国进口大豆，尽管总进口量因从南美的采购而飙升至历史新高，买家的目的是在与华盛顿的贸易紧张局势中避免供应中断。【原文：China imported no soybeans from the U.S. for a second straight month in October even as total imports surged to a record high on purchases from South America, with buyers aiming to avert supply disruptions amid trade tensions with Washington.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-imports-no-us-soybeans-second-month-brazil-arrivals-up-29-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCREHO5IAJOL7K4PVC2TT2B4DQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国会要求澳大利亚互联网监管机构提供证词]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会一个委员会要求澳大利亚互联网监管机构就该国的互联网法律作证，称她是 "著名的全球网络攻击狂热分子"，"威胁到美国公民的言论"。【原文：A U.S. congressional committee called on Australia's internet regulator to testify about the country's laws governing the internet, calling her a "noted zealot for global takedowns" who "threatens speech of American citizens."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/us-congress-seeks-testimony-australias-internet-regulator-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24CKACYENFP55IPXSIML5NBTIQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚央行仔细研究可能左右政策的三个因素]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚一位高级官员周四表示，澳大利亚央行正在研究三个可能影响政策的问题，包括企业是否改变了定价方式以及货币政策的传导渠道是否发生了变化。【原文：Australia's central bank is examining three issues that could influence policy, including whether firms have changed how they set prices and whether the transmission channels for monetary policy have changed, a senior official said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-central-bank-scrutinising-three-factors-that-could-sway-policy-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVMEK7EBQBKCFBVSCO3CSDTL6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国制裁豁免期限临近，石油反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[油价周四走高，从上一交易日的跌势中回升，原因是市场评估了美国提出的结束乌克兰战争的最新建议，并准备在美国规定的最后期限前停止与俄罗斯两大石油公司的业务往来。【原文：Oil prices edged higher on Thursday, recovering from losses in the previous session, as markets assessed the latest U.S. proposals to end the war in Ukraine and prepared for a U.S. deadline to cease operations with two major Russian oil firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-rebounds-deadline-us-sanctions-waiver-looms-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EQUNH7WM3ZJTXFN6DARGTCTZNA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:49:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息押注减退，日元下滑，美元跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于美联储会议纪要显示美国 12 月降息的可能性较小，美元在周四创下六周来最大涨幅后一路走高，而日元则因押注日本不会立即出手阻止日元走软而暴跌。【原文：The dollar was riding high on Thursday after notching its sharpest gain in six weeks as Fed minutes made a December U.S. rate cut seem less likely, while the yen tumbled on bets that Japan would not immediately step in to stem its weakness.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/yen-slumps-dollar-jumps-rate-cut-bets-recede-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YCNEVRHAIJMFJHPKHOLXM6ZGZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，Netflix 对华纳兄弟的竞购将包括影院发行]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，Netflix 已通知华纳兄弟 Discovery 管理层，如果收购成功，将继续在影院上映该公司的电影。【原文：Netflix has informed Warner Bros. Discovery management that it would continue releasing the studio's films in theaters if its acquisition of the company succeeds, Bloomberg News reported on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/netflixs-warner-bros-bid-will-include-theater-releases-bloomberg-news-reports-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Y2JKQ4PR5PBTP7YVNYRIOZHC4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩超预期，就业数据可期，股市大幅反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四早盘，由于投资者对英伟达（Nvidia）创下市场最高收益欢呼雀跃，一股宽松的反弹席卷亚洲市场，并提振了股市，而美元则因交易员为推迟公布的就业数据做好准备而上涨。【原文：A relief rally swept across Asian markets and lifted stocks in early trading on Thursday as investors cheered Nvidia's market-topping earnings, while the dollar rose as traders braced for the release of delayed jobs data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-pix-2025-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V6SLKIEBJNOAHKWZD5HFM6CH5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:13:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>