<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 06:06:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 06:06:51 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：在英伟达之前，英国通胀将占主导地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stella Qiu 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Stella Qiu】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ADOAUWTYC5N3VGRY6YXAKBSYYQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 05:32:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参加初创企业展的企业家希望 2025 年资金瓶颈能得到缓解]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲最大的初创企业活动之一 Slush 周三在芬兰举行，科技创业者和投资者将聚焦融资条件是否会放宽、唐纳德-特朗普赢得大选的影响以及人工智能驱动的增长前景。【原文：Tech entrepreneurs and investors meet in Finland on Wednesday at Slush, one of Europe's largest start-up events, with a focus on whether funding conditions will ease, the impact of Donald Trump's election victory and the prospects for AI-driven growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/entrepreneurs-start-up-show-hopeful-funding-bottlenecks-ease-2025-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PMAFM6HVEJKMNMEDZDS7HLDCJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 05:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家：Inditex 增加从印度出发的快速时尚航班以避免运输延误]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贸易数据、行业专家和投资者称，Zara 所有者 Inditex 已大幅增加使用空运将服装从印度的工厂运到西班牙的物流中心，以避免运输延误。【原文：Zara owner Inditex has sharply increased its use of air freight to bring clothes from factories in India to its logistics hub in Spain to avoid shipping delays, according to trade data, industry experts, and investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/inditex-boosts-fast-fashion-flights-india-avoid-shipping-delays-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HO3CURTUIBKJTIPB2GMETONK5Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 05:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，特朗普将于周三就财政部职位面试沃什和罗文]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道，美国当选总统唐纳德-特朗普定于周三对前美联储理事凯文-沃什（Kevin Warsh）和阿波罗全球管理公司首席执行官马克-罗文（Marc Rowan）就财政部长一职进行面试。【原文：U.S. President-elect Donald Trump is scheduled to interview former Federal Reserve Governor Kevin Warsh and Apollo Global Management CEO Marc Rowan on Wednesday for the post of Treasury Secretary, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-interview-warsh-rowan-treasury-job-wednesday-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMOV5T3VEBP2DJEYQVEK2LQF3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 04:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国基金下调 ETF 费用，繁荣市场价格战升级]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国主要基金公司周三宣布下调一批股票交易基金（ETF）的费用，从而加剧了这个规模达 4000 亿美元、迅速扩张的市场的价格竞争。【原文：Major Chinese fund companies announced a reduction in fees for a batch of equity exchange-traded funds (ETFs) on Wednesday, intensifying price competition in the rapidly expanding $400 billion sector of the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-funds-cut-etf-fees-escalating-price-war-booming-market-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CMRIMQLRWBM6JKDAXYTK7UUTYY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 03:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普贸易 "势头减弱，避险情绪升温，美元跌至一周低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[美元兑主要货币汇率周三跌至一周低点，从一周高点回落的跌势有望延续三天，因为市场在唐纳德-特朗普当选后的疯狂反弹之后正在喘息。【原文：The U.S. dollar slipped to a one-week low versus major peers on Wednesday, looking to extend a three-day decline from a one-week peak as the market catches its breath following the frantic rally in the wake of Donald Trump's election.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-sags-one-week-low-after-safety-bid-trump-trade-momentum-wanes-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDOILZ437JLZJD6J6FA3CISYLY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 03:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币首次突破 9.4 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的社交媒体公司正在洽谈收购加密货币交易公司 Bakkt，这增加了人们对即将上任的特朗普政府建立一个对加密货币友好的制度的希望，比特币因此升至 94,000 美元以上的历史新高。【原文：Bitcoin rose to a record high above $94,000 as a report that Donald Trump's social media company was in talks to buy crypto trading firm Bakkt added to hopes of a cryptocurrency-friendly regime under the incoming Trump administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-breaches-94000-first-time-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PGSGBAHHNLW5L6ZTOYXDHHJ3I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 02:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称澳大利亚关键基础设施面临网络威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚表示，去年每十起网络安全事件中就有一起涉及关键基础设施，国家支持的行为体利用不断发展的技术手段将澳大利亚政府、基础设施和企业作为攻击目标，澳大利亚对此表示担忧。【原文：Australia said it was concerned that one in ten cybersecurity incidents last year involved critical infrastructure, with state-sponsored actors targeting the country's government, infrastructure and businesses using evolving tradecraft.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/australia-critical-infrastructure-faces-cyber-threats-report-says-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JMURWNN7DRJB3EBN7MC3KGG6HY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 02:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰战事升级，中国需求出现改善迹象，石油微幅上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在乌克兰战争升级和中国原油进口增长迹象的影响下，石油价格上涨，而美国原油库存的增加抑制了油价的整体涨幅。【原文：Oil edged up on Wednesday amid an escalation in the Ukraine war and signs of growing Chinese crude imports, while rising U.S. crude stocks checked overall price gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-nudges-up-escalating-ukraine-war-signs-improving-china-demand-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L75DQL57B5KFXC6KTCHTVKVP3Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英伟达业绩公布前亚洲股市谨慎，美元回吐涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市表现谨慎，因为投资者期待人工智能宠儿英伟达（Nvidia）的财报，而该公司的财报令人失望的风险很高。【原文：Asian shares were cautious on Wednesday as investors looked ahead to earnings results from AI darling Nvidia where the risk of disappointment is high, while the dollar gave back a little of its recent bumper gains.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5KGRWNARQZIOJNCSQJHXAZTFJ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:45:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政府报告显示，澳大利亚男女薪酬差距略有缩小]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚政府周三发布的一份报告称，澳大利亚的男女薪酬差距已略有缩小，但女性雇员每年的平均收入仍比男性同事少 28,425 澳元（18,590 美元）。【原文：The gender pay gap in Australia has narrowed marginally though women employees on average still earned A$28,425 ($18,590) less each year than their male colleagues, a government report said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/gender-pay-gap-narrows-marginally-australia-government-report-shows-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RN2TWGRKHBLJJIANSGV2UJGCBE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:34:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚顶级银行联手打击银行支付中的欺诈和骗局]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列数字欺诈检测初创公司 BioCatch 周三表示，澳大利亚主要银行已与 BioCatch 合作启动了一个反欺诈项目试点，旨在减少银行支付中的欺诈行为。【原文：Major Australian banks have partnered with BioCatch in launching a pilot of an anti-scam project, aimed at reducing frauds in banking payments, the Israeli digital fraud detection startup said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/top-aussie-banks-join-hands-combat-fraud-scam-banking-payments-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z26OD55EUNI4DBWTWGSML4WMKY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:34:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥就特朗普关税对美国公司的影响发出警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥最高经济官员周二淡化了对与唐纳德-特朗普政府进行贸易谈判的担忧，称对美国公司的潜在影响可能会让即将上任的美国总统重新考虑征收大规模关税的问题。【原文：Mexico's top economy officials on Tuesday downplayed concerns about trade talks with Donald Trump's administration, saying the potential impact on American companies could give the incoming U.S. president second thoughts about levying massive tariffs.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-warns-about-trump-tariff-impact-us-companies-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SYYJW6DEZNJA7G3C3PLWXRZB2Y</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称康卡斯特将继续实施分拆有线电视频道的计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[消息人士称，康卡斯特正在推进分拆旗下 NBC 环球有线电视网络（包括 MSNBC 和 CNBC）的计划，从而摆脱曾经的核心业务，而这一业务已成为流媒体视频革命的牺牲品。【原文：Comcast is moving forward with plans to spin off its NBCUniversal cable television networks including MSNBC and CNBC, sources say, shedding a once core part of the business that has been a casualty of the streaming video revolution.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/comcast-proceed-with-plans-spin-off-its-cable-channels-sources-say-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFXLHAOC3NLHVKWNEUUDJYJTXM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国一如预期维持贷款基准利率不变]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周三维持基准贷款利率月度定盘价不变，符合市场预期，此前贷款机构为振兴经济活动，在上个月大幅下调了贷款利率。【原文：China left benchmark lending rates unchanged at the monthly fixing on Wednesday, in line with market expectations, after lenders slashed the rates by bigger-than-expected margins last month to revive economic activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-leaves-lending-benchmark-lprs-unchanged-expected-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3PRDUZYWNJKL3OWM5TPABWAKMU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:13:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿里巴巴定价 50 亿美元双币种债券交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国最大的电子商务公司阿里巴巴周三表示，已对美元债券和人民币债券进行了定价，这是该公司在双币种债券交易中计划融资 50 亿美元的一部分。【原文：Alibaba , China's biggest e-commerce company, said on Wednesday it has priced both its US-dollar-denominated and yuan-denominated bonds as part of the $5 billion it had aimed to raise in the dual currency bond deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/alibaba-prices-5-billion-dual-currency-bond-deal-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W7QZ4PDPVBOGDHZGQNYJDRDYGE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据报道，Seven & i 的创始家族计划在本年度完成收购，之后股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[据媒体报道，日本零售商 Seven &amp; i Holdings 的创始家族计划在本财年（截至 3 月）内将其私有化，该公司股价在周三的东京早盘交易中跳涨逾 9%。【原文：Shares in Seven &amp; i Holdings jumped more than 9% in early Tokyo trading on Wednesday following a media report that the founding family behind the Japanese retailer was aiming to take it private within this financial year ending in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/seven-i-shares-soar-after-report-founding-family-aims-complete-buyout-this-fy-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INPFEOEX6ZJPBGXWNWTYF4BIQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:42:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[索尼谈判消息传出后，角川股价大涨 16]]></title><description><![CDATA[在路透社报道索尼正在洽谈收购这家集出版、动漫和游戏于一身的公司一天之后，角川的股价在周三的东京早盘交易中大涨 16%。【原文：Kadokawa's shares jumped 16% in early Tokyo trading on Wednesday, a day after Reuters reported Sony was in talks to acquire the publishing, anime and gaming powerhouse.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/kadokawa-shares-jump-16-after-news-sony-talks-2024-11-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FUHFHUM2I5JHDPEP5FSEZPWHVA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:38:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司首席执行官称精神航空会谈进展顺利，但面临工业挑战]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲飞机制造商空中客车公司（Airbus）负责人表示，最终完成收购陷入困境的美国航空结构供应商 Spirit Aerosystems 公司部分股权的谈判进展顺利，但将其纳入空中客车公司 "并非轻而易举"。【原文：The head of European planemaker Airbus said talks to finalise the takeover of part of troubled U.S. aerostructures supplier Spirit Aerosystems were going smoothly but that bringing it into Airbus would "not be a walk in the park".】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-ceo-says-spirit-aero-talks-going-well-industrial-challenges-lie-ahead-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X3TVX3FZYRMCXBA3AXCX7AZCUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 23:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在 T-Mobile 表示不打算停止合作后，诺基亚美股股价上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在美国上市的诺基亚公司股价在延时交易中跳涨约 5%，此前 T-Mobile 公司表示，它没有计划停止与这家芬兰公司的合作，以回应分析师报告中声称的这种可能性。【原文：U.S.-listed shares of Nokia jumped around 5% in extended trading on Tuesday after T-Mobile said it has no plans to stop working with the Finnish company in a response to an analyst report claiming such a possibility.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/nokias-us-shares-rise-after-t-mobile-says-no-plans-stop-partnership-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4H32LX46UBI77MZQAFHNYGJOEI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[辉瑞公司要求从证交会和解协议中收回 7500 万美元的申请败诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二驳回了辉瑞公司的请求，即收回美国证券交易委员会与亿万富翁史蒂文-科恩（Steven A. Cohen）的对冲基金 SAC Capital 在一起内幕交易案中达成和解后剩余的约 7,520 万美元。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday rejected Pfizer's bid to recoup about $75.2 million left over from a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission settlement with billionaire Steven A. Cohen's hedge fund SAC Capital in an insider trading case.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/pfizer-loses-bid-recoup-75-million-left-over-sec-settlement-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WAXI55PBVFOJHJTO6FC6XP7SEQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞购美俄恐慌消退，英伟达守夜即将结束]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KPY3A633OZJALDRWQRGH76IAZE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高通公司预计五年内汽车和 PC 芯片收入将达 120 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高通公司周二在纽约举行的投资者活动上表示，预计到 2029 财年，汽车芯片收入将达到 80 亿美元，个人电脑芯片销售额将达到 40 亿美元。【原文：Qualcomm expects $8 billion in automotive chip revenue and $4 billion in PC chip sales by fiscal 2029, it said at an investor event held in New York on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/qualcomm-expects-12-bln-revenue-autos-pc-chips-five-years-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4DLAQ4UGJO5TMAHK7FJ6Q3SPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[司法部称戴尔和 Iron Bow 公司就多收军队费用的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周二表示，戴尔科技公司（Dell Technologies）和铁弓科技公司（Iron Bow Technologies）已同意各支付 200 多万美元，以解决美国政府对它们在一份计算合同中向陆军多收费用的指控。【原文：Dell Technologies and Iron Bow Technologies have agreed to pay more than $2 million each to resolve allegations by the U.S. government they overcharged the Army on a computing contract, the Justice Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/dell-iron-bow-settle-charges-they-overcharged-army-doj-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFMYEFBC4JNYRLFC7IYCB65JHM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国海军上将：乌克兰和中东冲突蚕食美国防空储备]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国驻亚太地区美军最高将领周二表示，乌克兰和中东的冲突正在蚕食美国的防空系统储备。【原文：Conflicts in Ukraine and the Middle East are eating into U.S. stockpiles of air defenses, the top U.S. admiral overseeing American forces in the Asia-Pacific region said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ukraine-middle-east-conflicts-eating-into-us-air-defense-stocks-us-admiral-says-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y42QN6A36BLEVKCBEGD26BOJUA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）在 "大流行病 "后的趋势中举步维艰，最终陷入破产境地]]></title><description><![CDATA[精神航空公司（Spirit Airlines）本有望成为大流行病后旅游业的大赢家之一。但是，在变化了的商业和经营环境中，这家免票价的先驱者始终没有找到自己的翅膀。【原文：Spirit Airlines was expected to be one of the big travel industry winners after the pandemic. But the no-frills pioneer never found its wings in a changed business and operating landscape.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-airlines-struggle-navigate-post-pandemic-trends-lands-it-bankruptcy-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OWDF4ANGJ5KAFNNPK6LTXJSFBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 20:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[参议员称特朗普不能无视要求字节跳动在明年之前剥离 TikTok 的法律]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议院司法小组委员会主席周二表示，当选总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）不能无视一项法律，该法律要求总部位于中国的 TikTok 在明年初之前剥离 1.7 亿美国人使用的短视频应用。【原文：The chair of a U.S. Senate Judiciary subcommittee said on Tuesday that President-elect Donald Trump cannot ignore a law requiring Chinese-based TikTok to divest the short video app used by 170 million Americans by early next year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/senator-says-trump-cannot-ignore-law-requiring-bytedance-divest-tiktok-by-next-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FMSBZOYRRRP4FLTVOZTNMD6Y6I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 19:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持的工作室 Promise 将开始利用人工智能制作电影和连续剧]]></title><description><![CDATA[Promise 公司由前新闻集团总裁彼得-切宁（Peter Chernin）和风险投资公司安德森-霍洛维茨（Andreessen Horowitz）支持，将使用生成式人工智能工具制作电影和连续剧。【原文：Promise, backed by former News Corp President Peter Chernin and venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, will produce films and series using generative AI tools, the company said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/andreessen-horowitz-backed-studio-promise-start-producing-movies-series-using-ai-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">STV4VPJBEJKTRODFURK3MLQXVA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stellantis 推出支持灵活电动汽车和混合动力汽车生产的技术]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stellantis 正准备利用新的汽车系统来应对动荡的电动汽车转型，该系统将支持汽油、混合动力和电动车型的组装，在唐纳德-特朗普重返白宫后，该系统的灵活性将变得尤为重要。【原文：Stellantis is preparing to navigate the turbulent electric-vehicle transition with a new vehicle system that will support assembly of gasoline, hybrid and electric models, providing flexibility that will be especially important with Donald Trump returning to the White House.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/stellantis-unveils-technology-support-flexible-ev-hybrid-auto-production-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5EQ2CVFSJMKBJLA7SWRME74F4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:19:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储施密德称利率还不确定能下降多少]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰弗里-施密德（Jeffrey Schmid）周二表示，尽管美国央行的首次降息是对通胀率正在回归2%目标的信心投票，但利率能下降到什么程度仍不确定。【原文：It remains uncertain how far interest rates can fall, though the initial reductions made by the U.S. central bank are a vote of confidence that inflation is returning to its 2% target, Kansas City Fed President Jeffrey Schmid said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-schmid-says-it-is-uncertain-how-far-interest-rates-can-fall-2024-11-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GNSZ6Q377BOYVM22ZHDEYGZXTE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 18:14:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>