<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:45:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:45:05 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，CATL 可能为 50 亿美元的香港上市提供低于 10% 的折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位直接知情人士透露，中国电池巨头 CATL 拟在香港上市融资约 50 亿美元，其潜在投资者已被告知，该公司股票可能会以低于深圳上市股票 10% 的折扣出售。【原文：Prospective investors in Chinese battery giant CATL's Hong Kong listing to raise about $5 billion have been told the stock may be sold at a discount of less than 10% to the company's Shenzhen-listed shares, according to three sources with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/catl-likely-offer-less-than-10-discount-5-billion-hong-kong-listing-sources-say-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">D6GS2SBJTZLAFBEVVZX7GXB6IQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:29:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国贸易沙皇成为美国关税谈判的焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国家主席习近平的长期亲信何立峰将于周六与美国官员举行会谈，旨在打破世界前两大经济体之间的贸易僵局。【原文：Opposite U.S. officials for talks on Saturday aimed at breaking a trade deadlock between the world's top two economies will be He Lifeng, a longtime confidant of Chinese President Xi Jinping who has slowly cultivated a reputation as a key fixer.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-trade-tsar-limelight-us-tariff-talks-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QVPXLX5YGZNGJKWAKJB45YFHRY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:29:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储会议前美元走低，亚洲货币趋于平静]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，在美联储召开会议决定对不确定的经济采取何种政策之前，美元汇率趋于稳定，亚洲的主要投资者继续从美国资产中套现。【原文：The dollar steadied on Wednesday before a Federal Reserve meeting to determine policy for an uncertain economy and as major investors in Asia continued cashing out of U.S. assets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/dollar-languishes-ahead-fed-meeting-asian-currencies-calmer-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZS3WMQ7Y5MNPLPHE7BEDTJV44</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:44:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 The Information 报道，OpenAI 计划削减对微软的收入分成]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周二报道，OpenAI 已告知投资者，它将与微软分享较小部分的收入。【原文：OpenAI has told investors it will share a smaller fraction of revenue with Microsoft , The Information reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/openai-plans-slash-revenue-share-microsoft-information-reports-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OGOQGJUPDJPXBAJ3UH6R4JST64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:04:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[监管机构称中国资本市场面临美国关税压力]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国证监会主席周三表示，美国的关税政策给中国资本市场带来了巨大压力，将有力推动长期资金进入股市。【原文：The head of China's securities regulator said on Wednesday that U.S. tariff policy has brought great pressure to China's capital markets and will forcefully promote long-term capital into the stock market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/chinas-capital-markets-under-pressure-us-tariffs-regulator-says-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JBNQ6L2NXBJ27KWB7P77O7GEDE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SK 集团董事长崔龙洙就 SK 电讯公司大规模数据泄漏事件道歉]]></title><description><![CDATA[SK 集团董事长崔泰源周三就韩国最大的移动运营商 SK 电讯公司（SK Telecom）发生大规模数据泄露事件道歉，该事件引起了 2300 万用户对个人和财务信息可能被盗的担忧。【原文：SK Group Chairman Chey Tae-won apologised on Wednesday for a massive data leak at South Korea's largest mobile carrier, SK Telecom, which has caused concern among its 23 million users over the possible theft of personal and financial information.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/sk-group-chairman-chey-apologises-massive-data-leak-sk-telecom-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RM5LQRLUYJOFRK4PFQZDHBNGKU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:44:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国央行下调 7 天期逆回购利率，5 月 8 日起生效]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行周三表示，将降低七天期逆回购协议的借贷成本，在与美国贸易紧张局势加剧的情况下，中国政府加大了货币宽松政策的力度，以支持整体经济。【原文：China's central bank said on Wednesday it would lower the borrowing cost of its seven-day reverse repurchase agreements, as Beijing stepped up monetary easing to support the broad economy in the face of intensifying trade tensions with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/china-cbank-cuts-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-effective-may-8-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BN5K6KE5UVK4JFWDDJXL6DRHTI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国央行在美国贸易会议前放宽政策]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国央行行长周三提出了降息和向银行系统注入流动性等货币政策宽松措施，旨在减轻与美国的贸易战所带来的影响。【原文：China's central bank governor on Wednesday flagged interest rate cuts and a liquidity injection into the banking system, among other monetary policy easing measures aimed at mitigating the impact of a trade war with the United States.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-central-bank-governor-says-will-cut-banks-reserve-requirement-ratio-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IJTQXKJMAVP4VMWEFGBCUPNWQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:31:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在美国推出 Model Y 长距离后轮驱动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉网站周二显示，特斯拉已在美国推出 Model Y 长距离后轮驱动车型，定价为 44,990 美元。【原文：Tesla has launched its Model Y Long Range Rear-Wheel drive in the U.S., pricing it at $44,990, its website showed on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-launches-model-y-long-range-rear-wheel-drive-us-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DY2AFIBNRJNR5AQ5CXANOYSJQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:19:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国期货因中国贸易谈判而反弹]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，美国股指期货反弹，亚洲货币上涨，因为投资者对中美两国贸易高官将于周末在瑞士举行会晤的消息表示欢迎，认为这是缓和贸易战的一个机会。【原文：U.S. stock futures bounced and Asian currencies rose on Wednesday, as investors welcomed news of a meeting between top U.S. and Chinese trade officials, set for the weekend in Switzerland, as a chance to tone down the trade war.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F5BTS6DOFKO7ASHH3BZLMPESQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰就业增长放缓，工资通胀加剧了更多降息押注]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰第一季度的就业增长速度疲软，失业率维持在 4 年半以来的低点附近，工资通胀也有所放缓，这进一步加强了人们对本月晚些时候以及全年降息的预期。【原文：New Zealand's employment grew at a soft pace in first quarter with the jobless rate holding around 4-1/2-year lows and wage inflation moderating, reinforcing bets for more interest rate cuts later this month and throughout the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealands-softer-jobs-growth-wage-inflation-reinforce-bets-more-rate-cuts-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MAX6BZHB2VO4ZIG7HRE3PL2ZNE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲和中国需求增加、美国产量减少的迹象导致石油上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，油价上涨，原因是有迹象表明美国产量减弱，欧洲和中国的需求增加，在本周早些时候油价跌至新低后出现了买家。【原文：Oil prices rose on Wednesday on signs of weakening production in the U.S. and higher demand in Europe and China as buyers emerged after prices fell to new lows earlier in the week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-up-signs-more-europe-china-demand-less-us-output-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CTMUQ26TVBMM7CNLVX3YZY3BLQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西法官阻止贷款机构 BRB 签署收购 Banco Master 的协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一份法院命令，巴西法官周二阻止国营银行巴西商业银行（BRB）签署从同业银行 Banco Master 收购资产的最终合同。【原文：A Brazilian judge on Tuesday blocked state-run bank BRB from signing the definitive contract to buy assets from fellow lender Banco Master, according to a court order seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/brazil-judge-blocks-lender-brb-signing-purchase-banco-master-2025-05-07/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KTIDUHZAFLWXKD7R5T3BII7RE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:28:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚监管机构在麦格理银行合规失败后对其展开进一步打击]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚证券和投资委员会（ASIC）周三对麦格理集团旗下的麦格理银行的澳大利亚金融服务执照施加了附加条件，理由是该银行存在大量严重的合规违规行为。【原文：The Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) on Wednesday imposed additional conditions on the Australian financial services licence of Macquarie Bank, owned by Macquarie Group , citing numerous serious compliance failures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/australian-regulator-launches-further-crackdown-macquarie-bank-after-compliance-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C4Q4YLEM4VN3HNNZXFVUU7AFXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:46:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国官员：美英贸易协定取得进展]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位英国官员周二表示，美国和英国在贸易协议谈判方面取得了良好进展，该协议可能包括降低钢铁和汽车关税配额，但由于美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）和美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）发出的信号相互矛盾，协议达成的时间仍然存疑。【原文：The U.S. and Britain have made good progress in negotiating a trade deal that would likely include lower tariff quotas on steel and autos, a UK official said on Tuesday, but the timing of a deal remains in doubt amid conflicting signals from U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and President Donald Trump.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-uk-make-headway-trade-pact-british-official-says-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y6SKQA5ILVMFXAZ5RTRLZWE5RM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大华银行第一季度净利润同比稳定，低于预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[新加坡大华银行（United Overseas Bank）周三公布的第一季度净利润为 14.9 亿新元（11.6 亿美元），与去年同期持平，主要原因是手续费收入创历史新高，贷款增长强劲。【原文：Singapore's United Overseas Bank reported on Wednesday S$1.49 billion ($1.16 billion) in net profit for the first quarter, flat from a year earlier, due to factors including record fee income and robust loan growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/uobs-first-quarter-net-profit-stable-year-misses-expectations-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37DFLBFOIVIZXOG7OWMJLOA5DE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员宣布两党推动改变美联储监督机构的遴选方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位参议员周二宣布了一项立法，将改变美联储内部监察机构的遴选方式。【原文：Two senators announced legislation on Tuesday that would change how the Federal Reserve’s in-house watchdog is selected.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-senators-announce-bipartisan-push-change-how-fed-watchdog-selected-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UNS64BSWGJJC3DBO6YDSGSMWI4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:11:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行退出，私人信贷公司盯上香港房地产新基金]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着估值下降和银行减少风险敞口，一些私人信贷公司正在介入投资香港的大型商业地产和开发商，并计划在全球最昂贵的房地产市场之一发行新基金。【原文：As valuations fall and banks pare exposure, some private credit firms are stepping in to invest in large commercial properties and developers in Hong Kong with plans for new fund launches for one of the world's most expensive real estate markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/private-credit-firms-eye-new-funds-hong-kong-property-banks-step-aside-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KNZ45BNINZM6HDJ4XCRT3WGLIE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员调查泰森食品公司工厂使用童工的指控]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国参议员乔希-霍利（Josh Hawley）周二表示，他对泰森食品公司展开了调查，因为该肉类公司的一名前雇员指控有儿童在该公司的一家加工厂工作。【原文：U.S. Senator Josh Hawley said on Tuesday he launched an investigation into Tyson Foods after a former employee of the meat company alleged that children worked at one of its processing plants.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/us-senator-investigates-claims-child-labor-tyson-foods-plant-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LEVR3AMRSJPX5DBUT6Z7EJG2FA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 22:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚国民银行上半年现金收益增长 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[澳大利亚最大的商业银行澳大利亚国民银行（National Australia Bank）周三表示，受贷款量增长和减值费用降低的影响，上半年现金收益增长了 1%。【原文：National Australia Bank , the country's biggest business lender, said on Wednesday its first-half cash earnings rose 1%, helped by growth in lending volumes and lower impairment charges.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/national-australia-banks-first-half-cash-earnings-rise-1-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KCSZTDUY7JLEXH623UYU3EGIAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 22:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝森特和格里尔本周将在瑞士会见中国官员]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长斯科特-贝森特（Scott Bessent）和美国贸易代表贾米森-格里尔（Jamieson Greer）周二表示，他们将于本周晚些时候在瑞士会见中国最高经济官员，这标志着就唐纳德-特朗普总统的关税攻击进行的潜在谈判迈出了第一步。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer will meet with China's top economic official later this week in Switzerland, the two U.S. agencies said on Tuesday, marking an initial step in potential negotiations over President Donald Trump's tariff assault.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/bessent-greer-meet-with-chinese-officials-switzerland-this-week-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">24CU55GS45KNRFK7ASNE4O2ITU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 22:07:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[针对以色列国家安全局的 Meta 诉讼案让人们对网络间谍世界有了难得的了解]]></title><description><![CDATA[以色列 NSO 集团周二被加利福尼亚州的一个联邦陪审团判处 1.68 亿美元的罚款，原因是该公司劫持了 WhatsApp 的服务器，代表外国间谍机构入侵 Meta 旗下聊天平台的用户。此案结束了美国社交媒体巨头与监控公司之间长达六年的斗争。它也让人们对间谍软件行业的内部运作有了不同寻常的了解。【原文：Israel's NSO Group was handed a $168 million penalty by a federal jury in California on Tuesday for hijacking the servers of WhatsApp in order to hack users of the Meta-owned chat platform on behalf of foreign spy agencies. The case caps a six-year battle between the American social media giant and the surveillance firm. It has also cast a unusual amount of light on the inner workings of the spyware industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/meta-suit-against-israels-nso-offered-rare-insight-into-world-cyberespionage-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JVNDNK4UG5O5DHMJTOQPYKY45U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:52:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[永利度假村公布的季度业绩不佳，原因是旗下各产业发展放缓]]></title><description><![CDATA[永利度假村周二公布的第一季度业绩不及华尔街预期，原因是其豪华度假村业务不振。【原文：Wynn Resorts posted first-quarter results that missed Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, owing to sluggish business across its luxury resorts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/wynn-resorts-posts-downbeat-quarterly-results-due-slowdown-across-its-properties-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SUOSOCZI45JIXD3ZUSLDBLK5MA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:41:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 与 NSO 之间的法庭冲突以间谍软件公司败诉 1.68 亿美元告终]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 公司周二表示，该公司赢得了对以色列监控公司 NSO 1.68 亿美元的裁决，为美国最大的社交网络平台与世界上最知名的间谍软件公司之间长达六年的掰手腕比赛画上了句号。【原文：Meta Platforms won a $168 million verdict against the Israeli surveillance firm NSO, the company said Tuesday, capping a six-year arm wrestling match between America's biggest social networking platform and the world's best known spyware company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/society-equity/court-clash-between-meta-nso-ends-168-million-defeat-spyware-firm-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OKEKVRNARBJH7AVU5Z3ACVWRUI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[达美航空必须面对乘客对大规模电脑故障的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[联邦法官周二裁定，达美航空公司必须面对乘客提出的集体诉讼，这些乘客称，在去年 7 月发生大规模计算机故障后，达美航空公司在延误或取消航班后拒绝提供全额退款。【原文：Delta Air Lines must face a proposed class action by passengers who said it refused to offer full refunds after delaying or canceling their flights following a massive computer outage last July, a federal judge ruled on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/delta-must-face-passenger-lawsuit-over-massive-computer-outage-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ADKTKCXKVPVTC7CDW3XOBMV7E</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:32:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国希望航空公司削减纽瓦克机场的航班，以缓解目前的困境]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部部长肖恩-达菲（Sean Duffy）周二表示，自 4 月 28 日以来，新泽西纽瓦克国际机场已有数百个航班中断，美国运输部正与航空公司合作削减该机场的航班，并增加空中交通人员。【原文：The U.S. Transportation Department is working with airlines to cut flights at New Jersey's Newark International Airport and boost air traffic staffing after hundreds of flights have been disrupted since April 28, Secretary Sean Duffy said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-wants-airlines-cut-flights-newark-reduce-ongoing-woes-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LGF5Z5MUARIKJNDEYS4QVMGRPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔认为五月份对决定巴西新投资至关重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[安赛乐米塔尔在巴西的负责人周二告诉路透社，随着当前投资周期的临近结束，5 月份对于钢铁制造商安赛乐米塔尔决定是否继续在巴西进行新的投资至关重要。【原文：The month of May will be crucial for steelmaker ArcelorMittal to decide whether it will move forward with fresh investments in Brazil, its head in the country told Reuters on Tuesday, as it approaches the end of its current investment cycle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/arcelormittal-sees-may-critical-decision-new-brazil-investments-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QMKC5QU6YVODRAPVPNMESKXCUY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[金融科技需求强劲，杰克-亨利第三季度利润上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周二，杰克-亨利联合公司（Jack Henry & Associates）公布的第三季度利润增长了约 28%，这主要得益于市场对这家金融技术公司产品和服务的强劲需求。【原文：Jack Henry & Associates posted about a 28% rise in third-quarter profit on Tuesday, helped by strong demand for the financial technology company's products and services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jack-henrys-third-quarter-profit-rises-strong-fintech-demand-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XN4RYYLXTZKETDP4ITL5G4MNRM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:21:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TPG 和 Corpay 拟以 22 亿美元收购 AvidXchange]]></title><description><![CDATA[全球另类资产管理公司 TPG 周二表示，将与 Corpay 合作，以 22 亿美元的全现金交易收购支付解决方案公司 AvidXchange。【原文：Global alternative asset manager TPG will partner Corpay to buy payments solution firm AvidXchange for $2.2 billion in an all-cash deal, the companies said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/tpg-corpay-buy-avidxchange-22-billion-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GF7NQCHY55JATALH4GNJ3FER6M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 公司被判赔偿间谍软件公司 NSO 集团 1.68 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体巨头 Meta Platforms 周二表示，它已从以色列间谍软件公司 NSO 集团获得 1.68 亿美元的赔偿，因为该监控公司被认定对入侵其系统负有责任。【原文：Social media giant Meta Platforms said on Tuesday it has been awarded $168 million in damages from the Israeli spyware firm NSO group after the surveillance company was found liable for hacking its systems.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/meta-awarded-168-million-damages-spyware-firm-nso-group-2025-05-06/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PSIMTZG44VNDFPMW3X3F4GTGM4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>