<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Business&Technews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 04:40:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/T3njJ3k8/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business&Tech]]></title></image><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 04:40:17 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲 英伟达财报成为焦点]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rae Wee 对欧洲和全球市场未来一天的展望【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Rae Wee】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/global-markets-view-europe-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SJG6PVU4FBOTLI6W7GMVFI2MGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 04:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社称，日产计划融资 70 亿美元，英国政府提供部分支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周三报道，日本汽车制造商日产汽车公司正考虑通过发行可转换证券和债券以及由英国政府担保的银团贷款来筹集超过1万亿日元（约合70亿美元）的资金。【原文：Japanese automaker Nissan is considering raising more than 1 trillion yen ($7 billion) by issuing convertible securities and bonds, as well as a syndicated loan guaranteed by the UK government, Bloomberg News said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/nissan-plans-7-billion-funding-backed-partly-by-uk-government-bloomberg-news-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OOSY7IBYORMZPJRYEWCZRW4MRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洞察：印度对中国间谍活动的警惕震撼了监控行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[官方文件和公司电子邮件显示，最近几周，全球监控设备制造商与印度监管机构就有争议的新安全规定发生了冲突，新规定要求闭路电视摄像机制造商提交硬件、软件和源代码，供政府实验室评估。【原文：Global makers of surveillance gear have clashed with Indian regulators in recent weeks over contentious new security rules that require manufacturers of CCTV cameras to submit hardware, software and source code for assessment in government labs, official documents and company emails show.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/indias-alarm-over-chinese-spying-rocks-surveillance-industry-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JHYXJKREZIQXFDUNTPOFOS23I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 03:32:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚洲股市和美元因乐观数据和科技乐观情绪而攀升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，亚洲股市延续了华尔街的反弹势头，美元也因美国经济迹象良好和科技股盈利强劲的猜测而保持涨势。【原文：Asian shares continued a rally from Wall Street and the dollar held gains on Wednesday on promising economic signs in the United States and speculation of strong tech earnings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-wrapup-1-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6WSRPGD5PRNLJGZS3FTHPS4LZI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:40:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[超长期日本国债收益率在 40 年期国债拍卖前从三周低点回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三，日本长期国债收益率从三周低点攀升，投资者密切关注 40 年期国债拍卖，以寻找需求复苏的迹象。【原文：Long-dated Japanese government bond yields climbed off three-week lows on Wednesday, with investors closely monitoring a 40-year bond auction for indications of a recovery in demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/super-long-jgb-yields-rise-3-week-lows-ahead-40-year-bond-auction-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W767KXZ7KRI3HFLV6CX2CXE3SU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰央行降息 25 个基点，在全球风险上升的背景下加大宽松力度]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰央行将基准利率下调了 25 个基点至 3.25%，并表示宽松周期将比三个月前预测的略有加深，这凸显了美国贸易政策的急剧转变对经济增长带来的日益增长的风险。【原文：New Zealand's central bank cut its benchmark rate by 25 basis points to 3.25% and flagged a slightly deeper easing cycle than it forecast three months ago, underlining the growing risks to economic growth from a sharp shift in U.S. trade policies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-central-bank-cuts-cash-rate-by-25-bps-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7MYUIQ7PDVIY3CS3CBZ5VAM4NA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元在日本国债拍卖前震荡，美元持稳]]></title><description><![CDATA[日元在周三的震荡交易中摇摆不定，因为债券市场的动荡使主要经济体的财政健康状况成为关注焦点，而美元则在上一交易日因经济数据向好而强劲收盘后企稳。【原文：The Japanese yen wobbled in volatile trading on Wednesday as ructions in the bond market kept the spotlight on the fiscal health of major economies while the U.S. dollar steadied after a strong end to the previous session due to upbeat economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/yen-drifts-ahead-japan-bond-auction-dollar-steady-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3GJ2T42GVPPVFDKTH7YSDQPDI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[澳大利亚 4 月份消费者通胀率保持稳定，核心通胀率略有上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于保险和假日费用的上涨抵消了汽油价格的下降，澳大利亚 4 月份消费者物价涨幅高于预期，而核心通胀率略有上升，报告结果令人略感失望。【原文：Australian consumer prices in April rose above forecasts as higher insurance and holiday costs offset a drop in petrol, while core inflation edged up in a slightly disappointing report.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australia-april-consumer-prices-rise-24-yy-above-forecasts-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">33RW25VGJRJ7ZO64HDZXH3KCFE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:49:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[公布创纪录利润后，中国小米股价将上涨 2.3]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国小米公司公布了创纪录的第一季度收入和利润，并表示其从智能手机向家电等高端产品的转变已见成效，该公司股价周三将上涨 2.3%。【原文：Shares of China's Xiaomi were set to rise 2.3% on Wednesday after it reported a record first-quarter revenue and profit and said its shift towards higher-end products from smartphones to home appliances was already paying off.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shares-chinas-xiaomi-set-rise-23-after-reporting-record-profit-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EZDH34KVLNNTROS4Y6NGL6QGAE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:28:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国禁止雪佛龙公司出口委内瑞拉原油，油价稳步上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周三早盘，油价上扬，原因是美国根据对雪佛龙公司在委内瑞拉资产的新授权，禁止该公司从委内瑞拉出口原油，从而引发了供应收紧的前景。【原文：Oil prices ticked up in early trading on Wednesday as the U.S. barred Chevron from exporting crude from Venezuela under a new authorization on its assets there, raising the prospect of tighter supply.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-inch-up-us-bans-chevron-exporting-venezuelan-crude-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZZZ52B5OCRIE3IBS7UZNMDOKGM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席威廉姆斯呼吁在通胀偏离目标时采取强有力的应对措施]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联储主席约翰-威廉姆斯（John Williams）周三表示，当通胀开始偏离目标时，央行必须做出 "相对强烈的反应"。【原文：New York Federal Reserve President John Williams said on Wednesday central banks must "respond relatively strongly" when inflation begins to deviate from their target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/feds-williams-calls-strong-response-if-inflation-deviates-target-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3WCOJN67LNOE3AOIPPR2WQVTDQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 01:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《Valor》报道，巴西 Azul 公司将申请破产保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《Valor Economico》援引消息人士的话报道，巴西 Azul 航空公司最快将于周二在美国申请破产保护。【原文：Brazilian airline Azul is set to file for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the United States as soon as Tuesday, newspaper Valor Economico reported, citing sources.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazils-azul-file-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection-valor-reports-2025-05-28/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CDSRGVAG5M6JPAT62THF2GB2U</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[朝日新闻》称日本拟在关税谈判中购买美国芯片产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[朝日新闻》援引一位不愿透露姓名的消息人士的话报道称，日本已提议在与美国正在进行的关税谈判期间购买价值数十亿美元的美国半导体产品。【原文：Japan has proposed purchasing billions of dollars worth of U.S. semiconductor products during ongoing tariff negotiations with the United States, the Asahi newspaper reported, citing an unidentified source.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japan-proposes-buy-us-chip-products-tariff-talks-asahi-says-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F3UUIZVQFILFHDROKMVJFQCYI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 23:59:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本日经指数摆脱特朗普关税影响，年底前有望上涨约 5%：路透社民意调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社调查，股票策略师认为，随着阻碍日经指数上涨的美国贸易政策不确定性继续消除，日本日经平均股价将在年底前攀升约 5%，但短期内可能会出现波动。【原文：Japan's Nikkei share average will climb about 5% by end-year as uncertainties over U.S. trade policies that have been holding the index back continue to clear up, although volatility is likely in the near term, according to equity strategists in a Reuters poll.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/japans-nikkei-seen-rising-about-5-by-year-end-shaking-off-trump-tariff-impact-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DZWRE2XKCRLH3BNBOHXRLSB2YU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 23:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称美国将保留对房利美和房地美分拆的监督和担保]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周二表示，美国政府将保留对房利美（Fannie Mae）和房地美（Freddie Mac）的抵押贷款担保和监督职能，因为他正致力于将美国抵押贷款融资公司上市。
特朗普在 "真相社交 "网站上发文称："我正在努力将这些了不起的公司上市，但我想明确一点，美国政府将保留其隐含的担保，我作为总统将坚定地坚持监督这些公司的立场。【原文：U.S. President Donald Trump said on Tuesday that the U.S. government will retain its mortgage guarantees and oversight role for Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac as he works to take the U.S. mortgage finance firms public.
"I am working on TAKING THESE AMAZING COMPANIES PUBLIC, but I want to be clear, the U.S. Government will keep its implicit GUARANTEES, and I will stay strong in my position on overseeing them as President," Trump said in a post on Truth Social.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/trump-says-us-retain-oversight-guarantees-fannie-mae-freddie-mac-spinoff-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">APY2UJQSSBJYLGKPB5BLBG4Q5Y</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，美国勉强授权雪佛龙保留在委内瑞拉的资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周二透露，特朗普政府已授权美国石油生产商雪佛龙公司（Chevron）保留在委内瑞拉的资产，包括与委内瑞拉国家石油公司（PDVSA）的合资石油公司股份。【原文：The Trump administration has issued a narrow authorization for U.S. oil producer Chevron to keep assets in Venezuela, including its stakes in oil joint ventures with state company PDVSA, two sources with knowledge of the decision said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-grants-chevron-narrow-authorization-keep-assets-venezuela-sources-say-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TAGO75JT4ZK5HANXG6UG7H6KYU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用磨坊本季度因结构调整支出 7000 万美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用磨坊公司（General Mills）周二表示，作为 Cheerios 谷物食品生产商重组工作的一部分，该公司将在本季度计提约 7000 万美元的费用，主要是遣散费用。【原文：General Mills said on Tuesday it would record a charge of about $70 million in its current quarter, mainly reflecting severance expenses, as part of the Cheerios cereal maker's restructuring efforts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/general-mills-flags-70-million-charge-current-quarter-restructuring-efforts-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72GIABDEXRJ4VALYKKEXECOZYQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[交易日：日本扩大长债宽松范围]]></title><description><![CDATA[交易日【原文：TRADING DAY】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/global-markets-trading-day-graphic-pix-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TNGGJKHR35KCHKXT5VPSYXZ3UQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，通用汽车将投资至少 8 亿美元在纽约工厂生产发动机]]></title><description><![CDATA[据两位熟知内情的消息人士透露，通用汽车公司将在纽约的一家推进器工厂投资至少 8 亿美元，以提高那里的发动机产量。【原文：General Motors is investing at least $800 million at a New York propulsion plant to increase engine production there, according to two sources familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-invest-least-800-million-engine-production-new-york-facility-sources-say-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TUOLOCOX5BIQROIMEM4CWSFVPM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:53:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[半导体 ETF 期权在英伟达业绩公布前表现谨慎]]></title><description><![CDATA[当人工智能芯片制造商英伟达（Nvidia）周三公布业绩时，期权市场的交易员们正准备迎接整个行业的波动，主要半导体 ETF 的防御性期权合约吸引了大量交易。【原文：Traders in the options markets are bracing for industry-wide volatility when AI-chipmaker Nvidia reports results on Wednesday, with defensive options contracts on a major semiconductor ETF drawing heavy trading.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/semiconductor-etf-options-show-caution-ahead-nvidia-results-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZYY4AJOGVPHHAIEDY5GFBQ6WA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州最大的公用事业公司高管表示，对数据中心的兴趣猛增 40% 以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[加利福尼亚州最大的电力公司 PG&amp;E 的一位高管周二告诉路透社记者，今年该州北部数据中心开发商提出的供电要求猛增了 40% 以上。【原文：PG&amp;E , California's largest electric utility, has seen a jump of more than 40% this year in requests for power supplies from data center developers across the northern part of the state, an executive with the company told Reuters on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/biggest-california-utility-sees-more-than-40-jump-data-center-interest-executive-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GIM4WRXJ5ZMQHMAFET2ZZMVNR4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官禁止特朗普下令起诉与罗伯特-穆勒有关联的律师事务所]]></title><description><![CDATA[一名联邦法官周二否决了针对律师事务所威玛黑尔（WilmerHale）的行政命令，这是唐纳德-特朗普总统以压倒性多数否决其惩罚他认为是其政府敌人的公司的第三项裁决。【原文：A federal judge on Tuesday struck down an executive order targeting law firm WilmerHale, in the third ruling to overwhelmingly reject President Donald Trump's efforts to punish firms he perceives as enemies of his administration.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-judge-blocks-trump-order-against-law-firm-wilmerhale-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DCGWMVP43JJFNH6XHVLTGKDTGY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:38:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国汽车市场价格战引发行业洗牌担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国汽车行业的价格战愈演愈烈，加剧了人们对全球最大汽车市场将出现长期预期的大洗牌的担忧。【原文：An intensifying auto industry price war in China has stoked fears of a long-anticipated shake-out in the world’s largest car market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/china-auto-market-price-war-stokes-fears-industry-shake-out-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QZIRZGMUMVMCDKWZB2PQDLBAVU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新堡垒能源公司披露纳斯达克通知]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国液化天然气公司新堡垒能源（New Fortress Energy）周二表示，该公司收到了纳斯达克的通知，称其没有向美国证券交易委员会提交季度报告，不符合证券市场的上市规则。【原文：U.S. LNG company New Fortress Energy on Tuesday said it received a notice from Nasdaq on non-compliance with the stock market's listing rule for not submitting its quarterly reports with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/new-fortress-energy-discloses-notice-nasdaq-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MYF4SSJVKZL4HJVW7ENRCJP2AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:29:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司将以 44 亿美元收购思尔沃思技术公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[摩托罗拉解决方案公司周二表示，将以 44 亿美元的价格收购无线无线电制造商 Silvus Technologies。【原文：Motorola Solutions said on Tuesday it would acquire wireless-radio maker Silvus Technologies for $4.4 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/motorola-solutions-buy-silvus-technologies-44-billion-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VF5GLQFR4NKNXL2VIRQ77X474U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[BBVA 到 2030 年将在墨西哥投资 52 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[西班牙对外银行（BBVA）周二发表声明称，该银行计划到 2030 年在墨西哥投资超过 1,000 亿比索（51.9 亿美元）。【原文：Spanish bank BBVA plans to invest more than 100 billion pesos ($5.19 billion) in Mexico through 2030, it said in a statement on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bbva-invest-52-billion-mexico-through-2030-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FAZ3LORCQZLTZEYI4GPUU7CKWM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[花旗银行波兰分行将向 Velobank 出售消费银行业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团周二表示，其波兰分部已同意将波兰的消费银行业务出售给 Velobank，这家华尔街巨头多年来退出非核心零售银行市场的努力已接近尾声。【原文：Citigroup said on Tuesday its Polish unit has agreed to sell its consumer banking business in the country to Velobank, as the Wall Street giant nears the end of a years-long effort to exit non-core retail banking markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citis-polish-unit-sell-consumer-banking-business-velobank-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5F7PIUIYIFOD5HELMVOSQRDATQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥认为 USMCA 审查将于 9 月底或 10 月初开始]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥经济部长马塞洛-埃布拉德（Marcelo Ebrard）周二表示，墨西哥预计将于今年第四季度初正式开始对与美国和加拿大签订的三边贸易协定进行审查。【原文：Mexico expects a planned review of the trilateral trade pact with the U.S. and Canada to formally begin at the beginning of the fourth quarter this year, Economy Minister Marcelo Ebrard said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-sees-usmca-review-starting-late-september-or-early-october-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JCRZVYSVTJMI3PZXZT4CJV62FM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:09:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Semafor 报道，马斯克的 Neuralink 公司以 90 亿美元的估值筹集现金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 Semafor 周二援引知情人士的话报道，埃隆-马斯克的大脑植入公司 Neuralink 以 90 亿美元的估值融资 6 亿美元。【原文：Elon Musk's brain implant company Neuralink raised $600 million at a valuation of $9 billion, Semafor reported on Tuesday, citing people with knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/musks-neuralink-raises-cash-9-billion-valuation-semafor-reports-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T2MGL5KDPZMSBLWYZ625LTSJXY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社：美国警告倍耐力可能因中国投资者而受到出售限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博社周二报道，美国已警告倍耐力，由于担心其中国投资者对这家轮胎制造商的影响，安装了其数据收集技术的汽车的销售可能会受到限制。【原文：The United States has warned Pirelli that sales of vehicles fitted with its data-collecting technology could be restricted due to concerns over the influence on the tyremaker of its Chinese investor, Bloomberg reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-warns-pirelli-possible-sale-restrictions-over-chinese-investors-bloomberg-2025-05-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MPCDCRYR4FIJVMZCNA32R6EW7M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>